{"code":"200","data":[{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5173\u4e8e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b \u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u6e05\u5206\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u53d1\u73b0\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u786e\u8ba4\u4e3a\u8bef\u6536\u5dee\u9519\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7b2c\u4e09\u65b9\u6e05\u5206\u670d\u52a1\u5916\u5305\u5546\u5728\u6e05\u5206\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u949e\u5238\u4e2d\u53d1\u73b0\u4e86\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u6bd4\u7167\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u3001\u5047\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u6536\u7f34\u65b9\u5f0f\u4f7f\u7528\u4e13\u7528\u6536\u7f34\u888b\u5c01\u88c5\uff0c\u5e76\u76d6\u597d\u5916\u5305\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u540d\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8d85\u8fc7\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u65f6\u6548\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u53ef\u4ee5\u62d2\u7edd\u53d7\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u79c1\u81ea\u5904\u7406\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u4f7f\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u91cd\u65b0\u6d41\u5165\u5e02\u573a\u7684\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u59041000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\"}]","id":"511930726","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5047\u786c\u5e01\u5e94\u6309\u76f8\u5e94\u9762\u989d\u3001\uff08\uff09\u679a\u4e3a\u4e00\u76d2\uff08\u888b\uff09,\u8fdb\u884c\u4fdd\u7ba1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001200\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001500\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012000\"}]","id":"511930727","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u968f\u673a\u5206\u5e03\u4e8e\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\uff0c\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u7167\u5c04\u4e0b\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\uff08  \uff09\u548c\uff08  \uff09\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\u8272\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511930728","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u987b\u5728\u56fe\u6837\uff08\uff09\u660e\u663e\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6807\u6ce8\u6e05\u6670\u53ef\u8fa8\u7684\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e0a\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e0b\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5de6\u4fa7\"}]","id":"511930729","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f2a\u9020\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u51fa\u552e\u4f2a\u9020\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u4f2a\u9020\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u800c\u8fd0\u8f93\uff0c\u5c1a\u4e0d\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u5904\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u62d8\u7559\u3001\uff08\uff09\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300115\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930730","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8fce\u63a5\u65b0\u4e16\u7eaa\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u7684\u6c34\u5370\u4e3a\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u672a\u8bbe\u7f6e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9f99\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5929\u5b89\u95e8\u57ce\u697c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930731","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u72485\u300110\u548c20\u6b27\u5143\u4e0e\u7b2c1\u7248\u76f8\u540c\u9762\u989d\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u53d6\u6d88\u548c\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930732","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u654f\u611f\u4e8b\u4ef6\u53d1\u751f\u540e\uff08\uff09\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\uff0c\u5c06\u654f\u611f\u4fe1\u606f\u62a5\u9001\u81f3\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511930733","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\uff08    \uff09\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u4e86\u7b2c\u4e00\u5957\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011984\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011979\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011989\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011988\u5e74\"}]","id":"511930734","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2014\u5e748\u670820\u65e5\uff0c\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u5ba2\u6237\u6301\u4e00\u5f20\u7591\u4f3c\u5047\u5e01\u3001\u62a4\u7167\u548c\u53d6\u6b3e\u51ed\u8bc1\u5230\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u7f51\u70b9\u6295\u8bc9\uff0c\u79f0\u5176\u57282014\u5e748\u67081\u65e5\u5728\u8be5\u7f51\u70b9\u53d6\u6b3e\u673a\u4e0a\u53d6\u51fa\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u5728\u63a5\u5230\u5ba2\u6237\u6295\u8bc9\u540e\uff0c\u7f51\u70b9\u67dc\u5458\u8ba4\u5b9a\u8be5\u7591\u4f3c\u5047\u5e01\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u6839\u636e\u76f8\u5173\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8be5\u7f51\u70b9\u53ef\u4ee5\u8d85\u8fc7\u529e\u7406\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d7720\u65e5\u4e3a\u7531\u62d2\u7edd\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7f51\u70b9\u4ee5\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8981\u6c42\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e0d\u8fdf\u4e8e2014\u5e74\u5e95\u5b9e\u73b0\u53d6\u6b3e\u673a\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\uff0c\u672a\u5347\u7ea7\u8be5\u53d6\u6b3e\u673a\u4e3a\u7531\u62d2\u7edd\u53d7\u7406\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e0d\u4e88\u53d7\u7406\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\uff0c\u4e0d\u5e94\u6536\u7f34\uff0c\u800c\u5e94\u8be5\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u9000\u56de\u539f\u6301\u6709\u4eba\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7f51\u70b9\u67dc\u5458\u5e94\u5f53\u6bd4\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u5173\u4e8e\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u548c\u5047\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u5904\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u4e88\u4ee5\u5c01\u5b58\uff0c\u6682\u4e0d\u5728\u7eb8\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u4e0a\u52a0\u76d6\u5370\u7ae0\"}]","id":"511930735","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u884c\u540d\u4e0b\u65b9\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\u5370\u5237\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5185\u542b\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u53ef\u4f9b\u673a\u8bfb\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5168\u606f\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7279\u79cd\u6807\u8bb0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u7279\u5f81\"}]","id":"511930736","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e5\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\uff08  \uff09\u6cb9\u58a8\u5370\u5237\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5f53\u7528\u5f69\u8272\u590d\u5370\u673a\u590d\u5370\u65f6\uff0c\u7528\u8fd9\u79cd\u6cb9\u58a8\u5370\u5237\u7684\u56fe\u6848\u4f1a\u53d1\u751f\u989c\u8272\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u4f7f\u590d\u5370\u51fa\u6765\u7684\u8272\u8c03\u4e0e\u539f\u6765\u7684\u8272\u8c03\u5b8c\u5168\u4e0d\u540c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9632\u590d\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u5916\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u78c1\u6027\"}]","id":"511930737","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5370\u7ae0\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u5370\u7ae0\u89c4\u683c\u4e3a5cm*2.5cm\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5370\u7ae0\u4e0a\u65b9\u4e3a\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5b57\u6837\uff0c\u4e0b\u65b9\u4e3a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7f16\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5370\u7ae0\u4f7f\u7528\u7ea2\u8272\u6cb9\u58a8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e3a\u65b0\u5f00\u4e1a\u673a\u6784\u5236\u4f5c\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5370\u7ae0\u65f6\uff0c\u5e94\u62a5\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5907\u6848\"}]","id":"511930738","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u6388\u6743\u8bc1\u4e66\u7684\u89c4\u683c\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300154.6cm*38.3cm\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300154.6cm*39.3cm\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300153.6*38.3cm\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300153.6*39.3cm\"}]","id":"511930739","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u81ea2003\u5e7410\u6708\u53d1\u884c20\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u7248\u949e\u7968\u5f00\u59cb\uff0c\u65b0\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\uff0c\u4e0d\u540c\u9762\u989d\u5747\u5728\u6b63\u9762\u5370\u5236\u4e86\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u81ea\u7531\u8c61\u5f81\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5176\u4e2d10\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u81ea\u7531\u8c61\u5f81\u56fe\u6848\u662f(\u00a0 )\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u9e70\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e94\u89d2\u661f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u706b\u70ac\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u81ea\u7531\u5973\u795e\u50cf\"}]","id":"511930740","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u73e0\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\"}]","id":"511930741","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u6388\u6743\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u5047\u5e01\u9274\u5b9a\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u672a\u516c\u793a\u5916\u5e01\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u4e1a\u52a1\u8303\u56f4\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5e94\u6309\u7167\uff08   \uff09\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5904\u4ee5\uff08    \uff09\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\u7b2c\u56db\u5341\u516d\u6761\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u7b2c\u56db\u5341\u56db\u6761\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u7b2c\u4e09\u5341\u56db\u6761\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\u7b2c\u56db\u5341\u516d\u6761\u3001\u00a050\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a200\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511930742","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e\u7533\u8bf7\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u7684\u53d7\u7406\u5355\u4f4d\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d7\u7406\u5355\u4f4d\u5fc5\u987b\u662f\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\u6240\u5728\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5730\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d7\u7406\u5355\u4f4d\u5fc5\u987b\u662f\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\u6240\u5728\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u7701\u3001\u81ea\u6cbb\u5dde\u3001\u76f4\u8f96\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53d7\u7406\u5355\u4f4d\u662f\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\u6240\u5728\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u603b\u884c\"}]","id":"511930743","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5370\u5236\u3001\u53d1\u552e\u4ee3\u5e01\u7968\u5238\uff0c\u4ee5\u4ee3\u66ff\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5728\u5e02\u573a\u4e0a\u6d41\u901a\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5e94\u5f53\u8d23\u4ee4\u505c\u6b62\u8fdd\u6cd5\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08 \uff09\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300120\"}]","id":"511930744","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u90e8\u5206\u80f6\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5448\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u8367\u5149\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6a59\u8272\"}]","id":"511930745","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6309\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u5206\u7c7b\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\uff1b\u8367\u5149\u9632\u4f2a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8367\u5149\u9632\u4f2a\uff1b\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\uff1b\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8367\u5149\u9632\u4f2a\uff1b\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930746","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u4ece\u54ea\u5e74\u5f00\u59cb\u4f7f\u7528\u7ea2\u5916\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011990\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011996\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011998\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012003\u5e74\"}]","id":"511930747","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u72485\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u8fb9\u9f7f\u6570\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300136\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300148\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300164\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300172\"}]","id":"511930748","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012019\u724820\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u4e0b\u65b9\u51f9\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u662f\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u201cRMB20\u201d\u548c\u201c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u201d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u201cRMB20\\\"\u548c\u201d\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u201d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u201c20\u201d\u548c\u201c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u201d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u201c20\u201d\"}]","id":"511930749","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u7684\u7f16\u53f7\u7f16\u53f7\u89c4\u5219\u4e3a\u201c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7f16\u7801\u201d+\u201c\u5e74\u4efd\u201d\u201c\u4e1a\u52a1\u6d41\u6c34\u53f7\u201d\uff0c\u81f3\u5c11\uff08  \uff09\u4f4d\u6570\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300120\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300121\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300122\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300124\u4f4d\"}]","id":"511930750","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u5e74\u7248\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u5238\u7684\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u795e\u517d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u795e\u517d\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5706\u7403\"}]","id":"511930751","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5c3a\u5bf8\u5f62\u72b6\u53d1\u751f\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u7968\u5e45\u5bbd\u8fb9\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u683c\u76f8\u5dee  \uff08    \uff09 %\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511930752","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u5956\u52b1\u7ecf\u8d39\u5ba1\u6279\u7ed3\u679c\uff0c\u5e94\u4ee5\uff08   \uff09\u5f62\u5f0f\u544a\u77e5\u7533\u8bf7\u5355\u4f4d\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u53d1\u653e\u901a\u77e5\u5355\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7535\u8bdd\u901a\u77e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53cd\u5047\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u6b63\u5f0f\u53d1\u6587\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u53d1\u653e\u544a\u77e5\u4e66\u300b\"}]","id":"511930753","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5177\u6709\u4e2d\u56fd\u4f20\u7edf\u5386\u53f2\u6587\u5316\u7279\u8272\u548c\u6c11\u65cf\u7279\u8272\u7684\uff08\uff09\u7eb9\u9970\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u7684\u6f06\u5668\u82b1\u7eb9\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c11\u6570\u6c11\u65cf\u7684\u6311\u7ee3\u82b1\u7eb9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9752\u94dc\u5668\u4e0a\u7684\u9955\u992e\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4f20\u7edf\u74f7\u5668\u7684\u82b1\u7eb9\"}]","id":"511930754","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f2f\u66f2\u633a\u5ea6\u5c0f\u4e8e0.03\u7684100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u591a\u4e2a\u7f3a\u89d2\uff0c\u7f3a\u89d2\u9762\u79ef\u7d2f\u8ba1\u8fbe25mm\u00b2\u768450\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7f3a\u59316mm\u00b2\u3001\u7968\u9762\u7f3a\u59314mm\u00b2\u7684100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5370\u5237\u533a\u57df\u51fa\u73b0\u5355\u4e2a\u6c61\u6e0d\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e70mm\u00b2\u7684\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"}]","id":"511930755","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\u5370\u5236\u7684\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u8be5\u56fe\u6848\u5206\u5e03\u5728\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u80cc\u9762\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e24\u8005\u7686\u662f\"}]","id":"511930756","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6643\u52a82004\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\u65f6\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u89c2\u5bdf\u5230\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u5e26\u4e0a\u7684\u56fe\u6587\u53d1\u751f\u4ec0\u4e48\u53d8\u5316\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ece\u7f8e\u56fd\u9e70\u53d8\u4e3aUSA\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4ece\u81ea\u7531\u949f\u53d8\u4e3a100\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eceUSA\u53d8\u4e3a\u4e94\u89d2\u661f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eceUSA\u53d8\u4e3a100\"}]","id":"511930757","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\uff0c\u8b66\u65b9\u67e5\u83b7\u4e00\u8d77\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u6848\u4ef6\u5e76\u6293\u83b7\u4e3b\u8981\u6d89\u6848\u4eba\u5458\uff0c\u67e5\u83b7\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01130\u4e07\u5143\u3002\u8be5\u6848\u4ef6\u7684\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u989d\u5e94\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u4e07\u5143\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300113\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110.3\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30018.4\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300118\"}]","id":"511930758","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u603b\u9762\u989d\u5728\uff08   \uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u201c\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u6570\u989d\u7279\u522b\u5de8\u5927\u201d\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e09\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e94\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5341\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e8c\u5341\u4e07\u5143\"}]","id":"511930759","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8d2d\u4e70\u4f2a\u9020\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6216\u8005\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u4f2a\u9020\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u800c\u6301\u6709\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\uff0c\u5c1a\u4e0d\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u5904\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u62d8\u7559\u3001\uff08\uff09\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300115\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130\u65e5\u30011\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930760","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u9996\u53d1\u9762\u989d\u662f\uff08  \uff09.","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511930761","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u589e\u5f3a\u4e86\u7ea2\u5916\u914d\u5bf9\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u6548\u679c\uff0c\u4e0e2005\u5e74\u7248\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\uff08\uff09\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7684\u7ea2\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u901a\u8fc7\u663e\u793a\u5668\u53ef\u89c1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u9762\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\u7acb\u67f1\uff1b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u56e2\u82b1\u56fe\u6848\uff1b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u80cc\u9762\u7684\u51f9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u6bdb\u6cfd\u4e1c\u5934\u50cf\"}]","id":"511930762","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c2010\u7248100\u5143\u6e2f\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ef4\u591a\u5229\u4e9a\u6e2f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5b8b\u7e82\u5370\u7ae0\u548c\u5370\u5237\u7535\u8def\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u72ee\u5b50\u5c71\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9999\u6e2f\u56de\u5f52\u8b66\u5bdf\u4e50\u961f\u6e38\u884c\"}]","id":"511930763","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011999\u5e74\u724850\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\uff08     \uff09\u6709\u78c1\u6027\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a2a\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511930764","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u73b0\u91d1\u5904\u7406\u673a\u5177\u6295\u5165\u4f7f\u7528\u4e4b\u524d\uff0c\u5e94\u8fdb\u884c\u9274\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u68c0\u6d4b\u3002\u5bf9\u5df2\u7ecf\u6295\u5165\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u73b0\u91d1\u5904\u7406\u673a\u5177\u5e94\u5efa\u7acb\u673a\u5177\u7ef4\u62a4\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\uff0c\u6bcf\u534a\u5e74\u8fdb\u884c\u4e00\u6b21\u9274\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u62bd\u6837\u68c0\u6d4b\uff0c\u62bd\u68c0\u7387\u4e0d\u5f97\u4f4e\u4e8e\u73b0\u91d1\u5904\u7406\u673a\u5177\u603b\u91cf\u7684\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30010.05\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30010.1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30010.15\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015%\uff0c\u81f3\u5c11\u6bcf\u4e2a\u578b\u53f7\u4e00\u53f0\"}]","id":"511930765","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53d8\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u51fa\u552e\u53d8\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u53d8\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u800c\u8fd0\u8f93\uff0c\u60c5\u8282\u8f7b\u5fae\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u5904\uff08\uff09\u65e5\u4ee5\u4e0b\u62d8\u7559\u3001\uff08\uff09\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300115\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\u30012\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130\u30012\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930766","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\u53cc\u8272\u5f02\u6027\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u6700\u65e9\u5e94\u7528\u4e8e\uff08     \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8fce\u63a5\u65b0\u4e16\u7eaa\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011999\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u5238\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u5238\"}]","id":"511930767","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012019\u724850\u5143\u548c2005\u724850\u5143\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7279\u5f81\u4e00\u81f4\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012015\u7248100\u5143\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u524d\u56db\u4f4d\u4e3a\u6697\u7ea2\u8272\uff0c\u540e\u516d\u4f4d\u4e3a\u9ed1\u8272\uff0c\u9ed1\u8272\u90e8\u5206\u6709\u78c1\u6027\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012005\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7279\u5f81\u4e00\u81f4\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012005\u724850\u5143\u548c100\u5143\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7279\u5f81\u4e00\u81f4\u3002\"}]","id":"511930768","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u72481\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5185\u6709\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6848\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\uffe5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\uffe5\u548c1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001RMB\u548c1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001RMB\"}]","id":"511930769","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67d0\u5ba2\u6237\u5230\u67dc\u9762\u5151\u6362\u6b8b\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u51713\u5f20100\u5143\u5238\u548c2\u5f2050\u5143\u5238\u3002\u901a\u8fc7\u6d4b\u91cf\uff0c1\u5f20100\u5143\u5238\u80fd\u8fa8\u522b\u9762\u989d\uff0c\u7968\u9762\u5269\u4f59\u4e94\u5206\u4e4b\u56db\uff1b1\u5f20100\u5143\u5238\u80fd\u8fa8\u522b\u9762\u989d\uff0c\u7968\u9762\u5269\u4f59\u4e8c\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\uff1b\u67091\u5f20100\u5143\u5238\u5448\u6b63\u5341\u5b57\u5f62\u7f3a\u5c11\u56db\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\uff1b2\u5f2050\u5143\u5238\uff0c\u5305\u62ec\u4e0e\u7968\u9762\u539f\u6837\u8fde\u63a5\u7684\u70ad\u5316\u3001\u53d8\u5f62\u90e8\u5206\u5269\u4f59\u56db\u5206\u4e4b\u4e09\uff0c\u4e0d\u5305\u62ec\u4e0e\u7968\u9762\u539f\u6837\u8fde\u63a5\u7684\u70ad\u5316\u3001\u53d8\u5f62\u90e8\u5206\u5269\u4f59\u4e09\u5206\u4e4b\u4e8c\uff0c\u5ba2\u6237\u7684\u6b8b\u635f\u5e01\u53ef\u5151\u6362\u7684\u91d1\u989d\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001400\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001350\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001300\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001250\"}]","id":"511930770","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0a\u7684\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u662f\uff08\uff09\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u82b1\u5349\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53e4\u94b1\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eba\u7269\u56fe\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930771","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u63a5\u6536\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u6848\u4ef6\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u9009\u53d6\u6bcf\u4e2a\u5238\u522b\u4e0d\u540c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\uff08\uff09\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\u8f6c\u5165\u5173\u6ce8\u7c7b\u5047\u5e01,\u4e0d\u8db3\u65f6\u5e94\u5168\u90e8\u8f6c\u5165\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\"}]","id":"511930772","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u4f7f\u7528\u4e13\u7528\u5c01\u88c5\u888b\u89c4\u683c\uff08    \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300118cm(\u957f\uff09*13cm\uff08\u5bbd\uff09*2cm\uff08\u9ad8\uff09\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300119cm(\u957f\uff09*14cm\uff08\u5bbd\uff09*2cm\uff08\u9ad8\uff09\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120cm(\u957f\uff09*13cm\uff08\u5bbd\uff09*1.5cm\uff08\u9ad8\uff09\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300122cm(\u957f\uff09*14cm\uff08\u5bbd\uff09*1.5cm\uff08\u9ad8\uff09\"}]","id":"511930773","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e00\u5904\u8131\u58a8\uff0c\u8131\u58a8\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e\uff08    \uff09\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300160mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300180mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001100mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300170 mm\u00b2\"}]","id":"511930774","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5404\u7c7b\u7ecf\u8425\u4e3b\u4f53\u5e94\u672c\u7740\u4f9d\u6cd5\u5408\u89c4\u8bda\u4fe1\u7ecf\u8425\u3001\u5c0a\u91cd\u516c\u4f17\uff08\uff09\u3001\u7ef4\u62a4\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\u5730\u4f4d\u7684\u539f\u5219\uff0c\u534f\u5546\u89e3\u51b3\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u81ea\u7531\u9009\u62e9\u6743\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u81ea\u4e3b\u51b3\u5b9a\u6743\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u81ea\u7531\u51b3\u5b9a\u6743\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u81ea\u4e3b\u9009\u62e9\u6743\"}]","id":"511930775","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01 \u7eb8\u5e01\u300b\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4e00\u5f20\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u635f\u574f\u4e3a\uff08     \uff09\u90e8\u5206\uff08\u542b\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c\u901a\u8fc7\u7c98\u8d34\u7b49\u65b9\u5f0f\uff0c\u6309\u539f\u6837\u8fde\u63a5\u7684\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511930776","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u67dc\u9762\u529e\u7406\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u5411\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u51fa\u5177\u7684\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u4e0a\u5e94\u52a0\u76d6\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\uff08\u00a0 \u00a0 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u884c\u653f\u516c\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u6233\u8bb0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e1a\u52a1\u516c\u7ae0\u00a0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u7ae0\"}]","id":"511930777","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u548c\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u4e24\u8005\u7684\u5173\u7cfb\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u76f8\u4e92\u4fc3\u8fdb\uff0c\u957f\u671f\u5171\u5b58\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5f7c\u6b64\u7ade\u4e89\uff0c\u548c\u8c10\u53d1\u5c55\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u517c\u5bb9\u5171\u751f\uff0c\u548c\u8c10\u53d1\u5c55\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u517c\u5bb9\u5171\u751f\uff0c\u534f\u8c03\u53d1\u5c55\"}]","id":"511930778","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\uff08   \uff09\u5238\u522b\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u5851\u6599\u4f5c\u4e3a\u5370\u5236\u57fa\u6750\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8fce\u63a5\u65b0\u4e16\u7eaa\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53d1\u884c70\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"}]","id":"511930779","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u5e26\uff0c\u524d\u540e\u6643\u52a8\u4e0e\u5de6\u53f3\u6643\u52a8\u949e\u7968\u65f6\uff0c\u5b89\u5168\u5e26\u4e0a\u7684\u56fe\u6587\u5206\u522b\u51fa\u73b0\uff08 \uff09\u73b0\u8c61","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001A. \u4e0a\u4e0b\u79fb\u52a8\u3001\u4e0a\u4e0b\u79fb\u52a8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5de6\u53f3\u79fb\u52a8\u3001\u5de6\u53f3\u79fb\u52a8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5de6\u53f3\u79fb\u52a8\u3001\u4e0a\u4e0b\u79fb\u52a8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5de6\u53f3\u79fb\u52a8\u3001\u4e0d\u79fb\u52a8\"}]","id":"511930780","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u603b\u9762\u989d\u57282000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e0d\u6ee130000\u5143\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u5e01\u91cf\u5728200\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e0d\u8db33000\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u7684\u5904\uff08  \uff09\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff08  \uff09\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u4e94\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e94\u5341\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012\u300110\"}]","id":"511930781","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u7248100\u3001200\u6b27\u5143\u4e0e\u7b2c1\u7248100\u3001200\u6b27\u5143\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e3b\u8272\u8c03\u548c\u7968\u5e45\u76f8\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e3b\u8272\u8c03\u548c\u7968\u5e45\u5747\u4e0d\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e3b\u8272\u8c03\u76f8\u540c\uff0c\u7968\u5e45\u4e0d\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e3b\u8272\u8c03\u4e0d\u540c\u540c\uff0c\u7968\u5e45\u76f8\u540c\"}]","id":"511930782","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u72481\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u76f4\u5f84\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u6beb\u7c73\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300119\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300122.25\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300125\"}]","id":"511930783","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f7f\u7528\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u5de5\u5177\u7684\uff08\u4e0d\u652f\u6301\u4f7f\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\uff09\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u540c\u65f6\u6ee1\u8db3\u9664\uff08\uff09\u5916\u7684\u5176\u5b83\u6761\u4ef6\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ecf\u81ea\u613f\u3001\u5e73\u7b49\u3001\u516c\u5e73\u3001\u8bda\u4fe1\u534f\u5546\u4e00\u81f4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u901a\u8fc7\u4e92\u8054\u7f51\u7b49\u4fe1\u606f\u7f51\u7edc\u65b9\u5f0f\u3001\u65e0\u4eba\u9500\u552e\u65b9\u5f0f\u63d0\u4f9b\u5546\u54c1\u6216\u8005\u670d\u52a1\u3001\u5c65\u884c\u6cd5\u5b9a\u804c\u8d23\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e0d\u5177\u5907\u6536\u53d6\u73b0\u91d1\u6761\u4ef6\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ee5\u660e\u663e\u65b9\u5f0f\u516c\u793a\u652f\u4ed8\u65b9\u5f0f\"}]","id":"511930784","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842003\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u201c\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u201d\u662f\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u82b1\u8fb9\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u201c\u4e2d\u201d\u5b57\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5706\u5f62\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u745e\u517d\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511930785","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"F\u7cfb\u5217\u768450\u82f1\u9551\u7eb8\u5e013D\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u7167\u5c04\u4e0b\uff0c\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5448\u73b0\uff08  \uff09\u8367\u5149\u53cd\u5e94\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511930786","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u4f1a\u8ba1\u7532\uff0c\u4f19\u540c\u53e6\u4e00\u94f6\u884c\u51fa\u7eb3\u5458\u4e59\u7b49\u4eba\uff0c\u5148\u540e4\u6b21\u4ece\u5e7f\u5dde\u7b49\u5730\u8d2d\u56de\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0110\u4f59\u4e07\u5143\u3002\u4ed6\u4eec\u968f\u4e4b\u7528\u4e00\u90e8\u5206\u5047\u5e01\u6362\u53d6\u771f\u5e01\u725f\u5229\uff0c\u4e0d\u4e45\u88ab\u53ca\u65f6\u67e5\u83b7\u5e76\u8ffd\u7f34\u4e86\u5927\u90e8\u5206\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u5219\u4ed6\u4eec\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u5982\u4f55\u5904\u7f5a?\uff08   \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ee5\u91d1\u878d\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u3001\u4ee5\u5047\u5e01\u6362\u53d6\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u4e00\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4ee5\u91d1\u878d\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\u548c\u91d1\u878d\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u4ee5\u5047\u5e01\u6362\u53d6\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u4e24\u7f6a\u5e76\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4ee5\u91d1\u878d\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ee5\u91d1\u878d\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u4ee5\u5047\u5e01\u6362\u53d6\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\"}]","id":"511930787","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u53ca\u5176\u4ed6\u9ed1\u8272\u51f9\u5370\u56fe\u6587\u4e2d\u542b\u6709\uff08  \uff09 \u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u78c1\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ea2\u5916\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8367\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\"}]","id":"511930788","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u67e5\u83b7\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u3001\u6301\u6709\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u5e76\u6293\u83b7\u4e3b\u8981\u6d89\u6848\u4eba\u5458\u7684\uff0c\u67e5\u83b7\u5047\u5e01\u9762\u989d\u603b\u8ba1150\u4e07\u5143\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u83b7\u5f97\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u989d\u4e3a\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110.5\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300118\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930789","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u81ea2003\u5e7410\u6708\u53d1\u884c20\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u7248\u949e\u7968\u5f00\u59cb\uff0c\u65b0\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u9996\u6b21\u52a0\u5165\u4e86\u7ec6\u81f4\u80cc\u666f\u989c\u8272\uff0c\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u989c\u8272\u88ab\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u9762\u503c\u4f7f\u7528\uff0c\u5176\u4e2d50\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u52a0\u5165\u4e86(\u00a0 )\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u84dd\u8272\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\u3001\u6843\u8272\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a59\u8272\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6de1\u7d2b\u8272\"}]","id":"511930790","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u80f6\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a59\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"}]","id":"511930791","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0110\u5143\u7684\u7eb9\u9970\u7075\u611f\u6765\u6e90\u4e8e\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ef0\u97f6\u6587\u5316\u5e99\u5e95\u6c9f\u5f69\u9676\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6566\u714c\u83ab\u9ad8\u7a9f\u85fb\u4e95\u5f69\u7ed8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9752\u82b1\u7f20\u679d\u83b2\u7eb9\u74f6\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9752\u94dc\u5668\u9955\u992e\u7eb9\u94d9\"}]","id":"511930792","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u90e8\u95e8\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\uff08  \uff09\u5bf9\u6837\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u68c0\u67e5\u4e00\u6b21\uff0c\u786e\u4fdd\u8d26\u5b9e\u76f8\u7b26","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6bcf\u534a\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e00\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e24\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6bcf\u5b63\u5ea6\"}]","id":"511930793","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e5\u5143\u8fd0\u7528\u7684\u5168\u606f\u56fe\u6848\u53d8\u6362\u89d2\u5ea6\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u89c1\uff08 \uff09\u76f8\u4e92\u8f6c\u6362\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6a31\u82b1\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3001\u65e5\u672c\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u6807\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a31\u82b1\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3001\u4eba\u7269\u8096\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a31\u82b1\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6a31\u82b1\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3001\u65e5\u5143\u7b26\u53f7\"}]","id":"511930794","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u7684\u51f9\u5370\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\u5728\uff08\uff09\u4f4d\u7f6e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5934\u50cf\u8fb9\u7f18\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u4e0b\u65b9\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e2d\"}]","id":"511930795","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2003\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\uff0c\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u53d1\u949e\u673a\u6784\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u76f8\u540c\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u7edf\u4e00\u8272\u8c03\uff0c\u6bd4\u59821000\u5143\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3b\u8272\u8c03\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5496\u5561\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u9ec4\u8272\"}]","id":"511930796","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u975e\u94f6\u884c\u652f\u4ed8\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5145\u5206\u8003\u8651\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u4e0e\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u7684\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u505a\u597d\u5bf9\u670d\u52a1\u5bf9\u8c61\u7684\u63d0\u793a\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u8981\u6c42\u6216\u8bf1\u5bfc\u5176\u4ed6\u5355\u4f4d\u3001\u4e2a\u4eba\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u6216\u91c7\u53d6\u6b67\u89c6\u6027\u63aa\u65bd\u6392\u65a5\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u901a\u8fc7\u5404\u79cd\u5f62\u5f0f\u5ba3\u4f20\u65e0\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u6216\u6b67\u89c6\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u6982\u5ff5\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ade\u4e89\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6392\u4ed6\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u517c\u5bb9\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e92\u8865\u6027\"}]","id":"511930797","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u5916\u5e01\u662f\u6307\u5728\uff08\u00a0 \u00a0\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5176\u4ed6\u56fd\u5bb6\u6216\u5730\u533a\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u7684\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u81ea\u7531\u5151\u6362\u8d27\u5e01\u548c\u7279\u522b\u63d0\u6b3e\u6743\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6211\u56fd\u5883\u5185\uff08\u6e2f\u3001\u6fb3\u3001\u53f0\u5730\u533a\u9664\u5916\uff09\u53ef\u6536\u5151\u7684\u5176\u4ed6\u56fd\u5bb6\u6216\u5730\u533a\u7684\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6211\u56fd\u5883\u5185\u53ef\u5b58\u53d6\u3001\u5151\u6362\u7684\u5176\u4ed6\u56fd\u5bb6(\u5730\u533a)\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u7684\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\"}]","id":"511930798","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\u7533\u8bf7\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7684\uff0c\u5230\u67e5\u8be2\u53d7\u7406\u5355\u4f4d\u586b\u5199\u63d0\u4ea4\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e2a\u4e0d\u662f\u5fc5\u987b\u643a\u5e26\u7684\u6750\u6599\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\u7684\u6709\u6548\u8bc1\u4ef6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u6216\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u529e\u7406\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u8bc1\u660e\u6750\u6599\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u529e\u7406\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u67dc\u5458\u4fe1\u606f\"}]","id":"511930799","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5355\u5411\u5956\u52b1\u8d39\u7528\uff08   \uff09\uff0c\u7531\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5730\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u5ba1\u6279","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300120000\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300130000\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300150000\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300160000\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511930800","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0a\u4e0b\u6643\u52a8F\u724850\u82f1\u9551\u65f6\uff0c\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e0a\u7684\u56fe\u6848\u53d8\u5316\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5de6\u53f3\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\u4e0e\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4ea4\u66ff\u51fa\u73b0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e0a\u4e0b\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e0e\u82f1\u9551\u540d\u79f0\u4ea4\u66ff\u51fa\u73b0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e0a\u4e0b\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e0e\u5973\u738b\u8096\u50cf\u4ea4\u66ff\u51fa\u73b0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5de6\u53f3\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\u53d8\u4e3a\u82f1\u9551\u540d\u79f0\u4ea4\u66ff\u51fa\u73b0\"}]","id":"511930801","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u5f53\u81ea\u53d7\u7406\u9274\u5b9a\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08\uff09\u5185\u5b8c\u6210\u9274\u5b9a\u5e76\u51fa\u5177\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\u3002\u56e0\u60c5\u51b5\u590d\u6742\u4e0d\u80fd\u5728\u89c4\u5b9a\u671f\u9650\u5185\u5b8c\u6210\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5ef6\u957f\u81f3\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u4f46\u5e94\u5f53\u4ee5\u4e66\u9762\u5f62\u5f0f\u5411\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u6216\u8005\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u8bf4\u660e\u539f\u56e0\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\uff0c5\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u5929\uff0c5\u5929\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\uff0c30\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300115\u65e5\uff0c30\u65e5\"}]","id":"511930802","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53e4\u94b1\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u53ca\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511930803","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u544a\u77e5\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\u53ef\u81ea\u6536\u5230\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u53ef\u7533\u8bf7\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30017\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\"}]","id":"511930804","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u4f7f\u7528\uff08\uff09\u56e2\u82b1\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u83ca\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8377\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6708\u5b63\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6c34\u4ed9\"}]","id":"511930805","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2003\u7cfb\u5217\u6e2f\u5e01\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u52381000\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u4e3a\uff08    \uff09\u56fe\u6848\u3002\u00a0\u00a0","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u98de\u9f99\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51e4\u51f0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9ca4\u9c7c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9e92\u9e9f\"}]","id":"511930806","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u65b9\u53cc\u8272\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u5176\u51a0\u5b57\u548c\u524d\u4e24\u4f4d\u6570\u5b57\u4e3a\uff08  \uff09\u8272\uff0c\u540e\u516d\u4f4d\u6570\u5b57\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u8272\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6697\u7ea2\u3001\u9ed1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ed1\u3001\u6697\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6697\u7ea2\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ed1\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511930807","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6709\u4f7f\u7528\u54ea\u79cd\u6cb9\u58a8\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u6cb9\u58a8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u73e0\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\"}]","id":"511930808","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u8f831999\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u786c\u5e01\uff0c\u8c03\u6574\u4e86(   )\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8272\u6cfd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u9020\u578b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u9020\u578b\"}]","id":"511930809","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u72485\u6b27\u5143\u548c10\u6b27\u5143\u5728\u77ed\u6ce2\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u6b63\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\u7684\u5c0f\u5706\u5708\u548c\u5927\u4e94\u89d2\u661f\u5206\u522b\u53d8\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u8272","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\u548c\u6a59\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u548c\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9ec4\u548c\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6a59\u548c\u7eff\"}]","id":"511930810","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\u989c\u8272\u5728\uff08  \uff09\u81f3\uff08  \uff09\u95f4\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u8272\uff0c\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\uff0c\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u91d1\u8272\uff0c\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u8272\uff0c\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511930811","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7ad6\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u4e3a\u9ed1\u8272\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011999\u7248100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012005\u7248100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012019\u724810\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012015\u7248100\u5143\"}]","id":"511930812","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\uff08  \uff09\u5143\u53ca\u4ee5\u4e0a\u9762\u989d\u5fc5\u987b\u5168\u989d\u673a\u68b0\u6e05\u5206\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\"}]","id":"511930813","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u529e\u7406\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u5047\u5e01\u4e1a\u52a1\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u4e13\u7528\u51ed\u8bc1\u3001\u8bc1\u4e66\u3001\u5370\u7ae0\u3001\u88c5\u5177\u5171\uff08\uff09\u7c7b\uff08\uff09\u79cd\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30014\u30018\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u30016\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014\u30017\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30013\u30018\"}]","id":"511930814","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u91c7\u53d6\u4ee3\u7406\u884c\u540e\u53f0\u6e05\u5206\u4e0e\u8bb0\u5f55\u5b58\u50a8\u65b9\u5f0f\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u4e8b\u5148\u534f\u8bae\u7ea6\u5b9a\u65b9\u5f0f\uff0c\u5411\u4ee3\u7406\u884c\u63d0\u51fa\u68c0\u7d22\u8981\u6c42\uff0c\u7531\u4ee3\u7406\u884c\u5728\uff08   \uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u672c\u884c\u63d0\u4ea4\u68c0\u7d22\u7ed3\u679c\uff0c\u901a\u8fc7\u8bb0\u5f55\u7f51\u70b9\u5411\u5ba2\u6237\u53cd\u9988\u7ed3\u679c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30014\"}]","id":"511930815","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u771f\u4f2a\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\u7684\uff0c\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u63d0\u51fa\u4e66\u9762\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u5f53\uff08 \uff09\u56de\u590d\u80fd\u5426\u53d7\u7406\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u65e0\u6545\u62d2\u7edd\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5373\u65f6\"}]","id":"511930816","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\uff08\uff09\u8272\u81f3\uff08\uff09\u8272\u4e4b\u95f4\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511930817","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u5728\uff08\uff09\u8272\u81f3\uff08\uff09\u8272\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511930818","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u53cc\u8272\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u7279\u5f81\u662f\u901a\u8fc7\uff08  \uff09\u800c\u6210\u7684\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7535\u8111\u55b7\u58a8\u6253\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u5370\u5237\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u78c1\u7c89\u78c1\u5316\u5b9a\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u6cb9\u58a8\u5370\u5237\"}]","id":"511930819","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6b27\u5143\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u6807\u51c6\u4ee3\u7801\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001EURO\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001EUR\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001EYP\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001EYPO\"}]","id":"511930820","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7684\u76f2\u6587\u6807\u8bb0\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u7684\u54ea\u4e2a\u4f4d\u7f6e\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5de6\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\"}]","id":"511930821","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1996\u7248\u548c2004\u724850\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u53d1\uff08 \uff09\u5149","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7c89\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7c89\u7ea2\u548c\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u548c\u9ec4\"}]","id":"511930822","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u5bf9\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u8fdb\u884c\u8c03\u67e5\u53d6\u8bc1\u7ec8\u7ed3\u540e\uff0c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u5f53\u64b0\u5199\u8c03\u67e5\u62a5\u544a\uff0c\u4e0a\u62a5\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\u884c\u9886\u5bfc\u5ba1\u9605\u3002\u4e0b\u5217\u90a3\u4e00\u9879\u5185\u5bb9\u4e0d\u662f\u8c03\u67e5\u62a5\u544a\u7684\u8981\u70b9\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u88ab\u8c03\u67e5\u3001\u68c0\u67e5\u5f53\u4e8b\u4eba\u7684\u57fa\u672c\u60c5\u51b5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ecf\u8c03\u67e5\u6838\u5b9e\u7684\u8fdd\u6cd5\u4e8b\u5b9e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u672a\u67e5\u5b9e\u7684\u8fdd\u6cd5\u4e8b\u5b9e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u63d0\u51fa\u5904\u7406\u610f\u89c1\"}]","id":"511930823","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u4e8e\u6bcf\u5e74\u5e74\u521d\u6309\u7167\uff08\u00a0 \u00a0\uff09\u4e3a\u57f9\u8bad\u5468\u671f\u5236\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u5185\u73b0\u91d1\u4ece\u4e1a\u4eba\u5458\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u77e5\u8bc6\u4e0e\u6280\u80fd\u57f9\u8bad\u8ba1\u5212\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u5e74\u00a0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\u5e74\u00a0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u5e74\u00a0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5e74\u00a0\"}]","id":"511930824","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u82f1\u9551\u7eb8\u5e01\u54ea\u4e9b\u9762\u989d\u6709\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u548c10\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u548c50\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u548c20\u82f1\u9551\"}]","id":"511930825","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u65b0\u589e\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5168\u606f\u5f00\u7a97\u5f0f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u8367\u5149\u7279\u5f81\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u8367\u5149\u6761\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6848\u548c\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3001\u8367\u5149\u6761\u7801\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u548c\u51f9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u8367\u5149\u7279\u5f81\u3001\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511930826","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u68c0\u6d4b\u65b9\u6cd5\u662f\u5206\u522b\u5728\u6b63\u9762\u548c\u80cc\u9762\u5404\u9009\u53d6\uff08   \uff09\u4e2a\u975e\u5370\u5237\u65e0\u6c34\u5370\u533a\u91c7\u6837\u70b9\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511930827","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\uff08JR\/T 0154\u20142017)\u4e2d\u8981\u6c42\u975e\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7528\u65e0\u62d2\u949e\u4ed3\u7684\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u8bef\u8bc6\u7387\u4e3a\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30010.0002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30010.0003\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30010.0004\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30010.0005\"}]","id":"511930828","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u53d7\u7406\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\uff0c\u5e94\u81ea\u53d7\u7406\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u529e\u7ed3\u3002\u5982\u4e0d\u80fd\u53ca\u65f6\u529e\u7ed3\u7684\uff0c\u7ecf\u6709\u5173\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\u6838\u6279\u540e\u53ef\u5ef6\u957f\u81f3\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\u300130\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300115\u300130\"}]","id":"511930829","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u5173\u4e8e\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u529e\u6cd5\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8868\u8ff0\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7531\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4f9d\u6cd5\u8fdb\u884c\u9274\u5b9a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7531\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u8fdb\u884c\u9274\u5b9a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7531\u4e8e\u5176\u7279\u6b8a\u6027\uff0c\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7531\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u8fdb\u884c\u9274\u5b9a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5177\u4f53\u529e\u6cd5\u53e6\u884c\u5236\u5b9a\"}]","id":"511930830","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"22.\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\uff08JR\/T 0154\u20142017)\u4e2d\u8981\u6c42\u81ea\u52a9\u7eb8\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u8bef\u8bc6\u7387\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30010.0002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30010.0003\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30010.0004\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30010.0005\"}]","id":"511930831","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u5f00\u5c55\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\u76d1\u63a7\u4e0b\u5b9e\u65bd\uff0c\u76d1\u63a7\u8bb0\u5f55\u4fdd\u5b58\u671f\u9650\u4e0d\u5f97\u5c11\u4e8e\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u6708\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30016\"}]","id":"511930832","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e2d\u6700\u65e9\u4f7f\u7528\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\u7684\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u662f\uff08    \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012005\u7248100\u5143\u5238\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012015\u7248100\u5143\u5238\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8fce\u63a5\u65b0\u4e16\u7eaa\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"}]","id":"511930833","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u6570\u636e\u6587\u4ef6\u5206\u4e3a\u4e24\u4e2a\u5c42\u7ea7\u5176\u4e2d\u7b2c\u4e00\u5c42\u7ea7\u662f\uff08   \uff09\u6587\u4ef6\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001FSN\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001FCN\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001FSM\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001FVN\"}]","id":"511930834","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u56e0\u706b\u70e7\u9020\u6210\u591a\u51fa\u70ad\u5316\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u70ad\u5316\u9762\u79ef\u8d85\u8fc7\uff08    \uff09\u65f6\u53ef\u5224\u5b9a\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110 mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300115mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300116 mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300118mm\u00b2\"}]","id":"511930835","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u771f\u4f2a\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u81ea\u6536\u7f34\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d773\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\uff0c\u6301\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u76f4\u63a5\u6216\u8005\u901a\u8fc7\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u63d0\u51fa\u4e66\u9762\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u3002\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u5f53\uff08\uff09\u56de\u590d\u80fd\u5426\u53d7\u7406\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u65e0\u6545\u62d2\u7edd\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5373\u65f6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\"}]","id":"511930836","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6b27\u5143\u949e\u7968\uff08\uff09\u7684\u53f7\u7801\u4e3a\u78c1\u6027\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u78c1\u6027\u9274\u522b\u4eea\u53ef\u5bf9\u6b64\u8fdb\u884c\u9274\u522b\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0a\u89d2\"}]","id":"511930837","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u76ee\u524d\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u7684\u7f8e\u5143\u73b0\u949e\u6700\u5927\u9762\u503c\u4e3a(  )\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001500\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001100\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110000\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511930838","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5404\u5206\u884c\u3001\u8425\u4e1a\u7ba1\u7406\u90e8\u3001\u7701\u4f1a\u57ce\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u5355\u9879\u5956\u52b1\u8d39\u7528\u5ba1\u6279\u6743\u9650\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u4e07\u5143\u81f320\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\u4e07\u5143\u81f315\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u4e07\u5143\u81f320\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30013\u4e07\u5143\u81f315\u4e07\u5143\"}]","id":"511930839","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u767d\u6c34\u5370\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5de6\u4e0a\u65b9\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53f3\u4e0a\u65b9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5de6\u4e0b\u65b9\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53f3\u4e0b\u65b9\"}]","id":"511930840","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5927\u5934\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\uff08 \uff09\u5b57\u6bcd\u8868\u793a\u8868\u793a\u5e74\u7248\u53f7\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7b2c2\u4e2a\u524d\u7f00\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7b2c1\u4e2a\u524d\u7f00\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7b2c1\u4e2a\u540e\u7f00\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7b2c2\u4e2a\u540e\u7f00\"}]","id":"511930841","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e00\u4e2a\u573a\u666f\u6ca1\u6709\u88ab\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u5c40\u8ba4\u5b9a\u4e3a\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u7684\u91cd\u70b9\u573a\u666f\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6709\u6536\u8d39\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u653f\u5e9c\u90e8\u95e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u65c5\u6e38\u666f\u70b9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u516c\u5171\u4ea4\u901a\u573a\u6240\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5e02\u6c11\u56fe\u4e66\u9986\"}]","id":"511930842","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u7f16\u53f7\u89c4\u5219\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7f16\u7801+\u5e74\u4efd+\u6708\u4efd+\u4e1a\u52a1\u6d41\u6c34\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7f16\u7801+\u4e1a\u52a1\u6d41\u6c34\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7f16\u7801+\u5e74\u4efd+\u4e1a\u52a1\u6d41\u6c34\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7f16\u7801+\u5e74+\u6708+\u65e5+\u4e1a\u52a1\u6d41\u6c34\u53f7\"}]","id":"511930843","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\u5370\u5236\u7684\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u8be5\u56fe\u6848\u5206\u5e03\u5728\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u80cc\u9762\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u90fd\u6709\"}]","id":"511930844","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ea2\u84dd\u7ea4\u7ef4\u65bd\u653e\u4f4d\u7f6e\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ec5\u6b63\u9762\u968f\u673a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4ec5\u80cc\u9762\u968f\u673a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u968f\u673a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u672a\u65bd\u653e\"}]","id":"511930845","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2016\u5e749\u6708\u82f1\u56fd\u53d1\u884c\u4e86\u65b0\u7248\u5c0f\u9762\u989d\u5851\u6599\u5e01\uff0c\u5176\u9762\u989d\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011\u82f1\u9551\"}]","id":"511930846","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u6709\u78c1\u6027\u5e76\u53ef\u4f9b\u673a\u8bfb\u662f\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u548c\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511930847","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5370\u5236\u673a\u6784\u548c\u53d1\u884c\u673a\u6784\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u7279\u52e4\u5c40\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u8054\u90a6\u50a8\u5907\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u8d22\u653f\u90e8\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u82b1\u65d7\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u5370\u5236\u5c40\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u8054\u90a6\u50a8\u5907\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u5370\u5236\u5c40\u3001\u7f8e\u56fd\u7279\u52e4\u5c40\"}]","id":"511930848","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1996\u5e74\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u5176\u989c\u8272\u53d8\u5316\u4e3a\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u53d8\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u53d8\u9ed1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\u53d8\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53e4\u94dc\u53d8\u7eff\"}]","id":"511930849","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4f7f\u7528\u4e3a\u76ee\u7684\uff0c\u4f2a\u9020\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4ee5\uff08\uff09\u5b9a\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e0d\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u7531\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u5904\u5341\u4e94\u65e5\u4ee5\u4e0b\u62d8\u7559\u3001\u4e00\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u975e\u6cd5\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u5904\u4e94\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8bc8\u9a97\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511930850","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u65e5\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u5bf9\u5370\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u5bf9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ee5\u4e0a\u8bf4\u6cd5\u90fd\u4e0d\u5bf9\"}]","id":"511930851","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5173\u4e8e\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u8bb8\u53ef\u6279\u51c6\u6587\u4ef6\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f9d\u6cd5\u53d6\u5f97\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u8bb8\u53ef\u8bc1\u4e0d\u5f97\u8f6c\u8ba9\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u6d82\u6539\u3001\u5012\u5356\u3001\u51fa\u79df\u3001\u51fa\u501f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u8bb8\u53ef\u6279\u51c6\u6587\u4ef6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u65f6\u8981\u6c42\u6ce8\u660e\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u540d\u79f0\u548c\u8bb8\u53ef\u6279\u51c6\u6587\u4ef6\u53f7\uff0c\u4f46\u4e0d\u8981\u6c42\u6ce8\u660e\u4ea7\u54c1\u5236\u4f5c\u5355\u4f4d\u540d\u79f0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u5e94\u5f53\u6309\u7167\u8bb8\u53ef\u6279\u51c6\u6587\u4ef6\u6838\u51c6\u7684\u8303\u56f4\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u5e76\u4e0e\u7533\u8bf7\u4e8b\u9879\u4fdd\u6301\u4e00\u81f4\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u88ab\u6279\u51c6\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u53ea\u80fd\u5355\u9762\u4f7f\u7528\uff0c\u4fdd\u8bc1\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4e2d\u4eba\u7269\u5934\u50cf\u3001\u56fd\u5fbd\u7684\u539f\u6709\u6bd4\u4f8b\"}]","id":"511930852","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8fce\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u53ef\u89c12005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5f00\u7a97\u90e8\u5206\u8bbe\u6709\uff08\uff09\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001RMB100\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001100\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u00a5100\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001CNY100\"}]","id":"511930853","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u4e00\u6b21\u6027\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e01\uff08\uff09\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\u548c\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u548c\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u53d1\u6587\u53e6\u6709\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u4e24\u8005\u8f83\u5c0f\u8005\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u7acb\u5373\u62a5\u544a\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u548c\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\"}]","id":"511930854","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6b27\u5143\u949e\u7968\uff08  \uff09\u7684\u53f7\u7801\u4e3a\u78c1\u6027\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u78c1\u6027\u9274\u522b\u4eea\u53ef\u5bf9\u6b64\u8fdb\u884c\u9274\u522b","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"}]","id":"511930855","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1993\u5e74\u72481000\u65e5\u5143\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u7f29\u5fae\u5370\u5237\u6587\u5b57\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001NIPPON GINKO\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001NIPPON 1000\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011000 yen\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u65e5\u672c\u94f6\u884c\u5238\"}]","id":"511930856","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5bf9\u5916\u4ed8\u51fa\u6b8b\u7f3a\u3001\u6c61\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ef\u5bf9\u5176\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08\uff09\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c1\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c2\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511930857","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u82f1\u9551\u7eb8\u5e01\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5185\u5bb9\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u82f1\u683c\u5170\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u6807\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\"}]","id":"511930858","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a2a\u7ad6\u53cc\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511930859","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6211\u56fd\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u6700\u65e9\u8fd0\u7528\u5728\uff08 \uff09\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u4e0a\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8f9b\u4ea5\u9769\u547d90\u5468\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6cf0\u5c71\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7b2c29\u5c4a\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514b\u8fd0\u52a8\u4f1a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u201c\u548c\u201d\u5b57\u4e66\u6cd5\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\"}]","id":"511930860","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u591a\u4e2a\u7f3a\u89d2\uff0c\u7f3a\u89d2\u9762\u79ef\u7d2f\u8ba1\u5927\u4e8e\uff08    \uff09\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300130mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300140mm\u00b2\"}]","id":"511930861","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u5355\u9879\u5956\u52b1\u8d39\u7528\u8d85\u8fc7\uff08  \uff09\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u603b\u884c\u5ba1\u6279\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300130\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u4e07\u5143\"}]","id":"511930862","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5bf9\u4e8e\u7b26\u5408\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u6761\u4ef6\u7684\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5728\u53d7\u7406\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u529e\u7ed3\u3002\u5982\u6709\u7279\u6b8a\u60c5\u51b5\u9700\u8981\u5ef6\u957f\u529e\u7406\u65f6\u95f4\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u5ef6\u957f\u81f3\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u300115\"}]","id":"511930863","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5173\u4e8e\u8d27\u5e01\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e00\u9009\u9879\u662f\u9519\u8bef\u7684\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u4e2d\u7684\u201c\u8d27\u5e01\u201d\uff0c\u5305\u62ec\u5728\u56fd\u5185\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3001\u5728\u56fd\u5185\u53ef\u5151\u6362\u7684\u5883\u5916\u8d27\u5e01\uff0c\u4ee5\u53ca\u6b63\u5728\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u5883\u5916\u8d27\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6839\u636e\u300a\u5211\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u5e76\u51fa\u552e\u6216\u8005\u8fd0\u8f93\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4f9d\u7167\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\u3002\u636e\u6b64\uff0c\u884c\u4e3a\u4eba\u4f2a\u9020\u7f8e\u5143\uff0c\u5e76\u8fd0\u8f93\u4ed6\u4eba\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u6b27\u5143\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u6309\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c06\u4f4e\u989d\u7f8e\u5143\u7684\u7eb8\u5e01\u52a0\u5de5\u6210\u9ad8\u989d\u82f1\u9551\u7684\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5bf9\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u5e01\u52a0\u5de5\u5904\u7406\uff0c\u4f7f100\u5143\u9762\u989d\u53d8\u4e3a50\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7684\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u53d8\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\"}]","id":"511930864","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u65e5\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7eb8\u5f20\u5448\u6de1\u9ec4\u8272\uff0c\u5e76\u542b\u6709\u65e5\u672c\u7279\u6709\u7684\uff08 \uff09\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8695\u4e1d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5251\u9ebb\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e09\u6860\u6811\u76ae\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5408\u6210\u7ea4\u7ef4\"}]","id":"511930865","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u4e00\u9879\u65b0\u6280\u672f\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u591a\u8272\u63a5\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u63a5\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511930866","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u7167\u5c04\u4e0b\uff0c1996\u5e74\u7248\u53ca\u4ee5\u540e\u5404\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\uff08\u00a0\u00a0\uff09\u4f1a\u6709\u8367\u5149\u53cd\u5e94\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8fde\u53f7\u00a0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eba\u7269\u8096\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930867","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u724850\u5143\u5238\u6240\u4f7f\u7528\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u6280\u672f\u662f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u52a8\u611f\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511930868","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2016\u5e749\u670813\u65e5\u82f1\u56fd\u592e\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u9996\u5f20\u5851\u6599\u949e\u9762\u989d\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u82f1\u9551\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\"}]","id":"511930869","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67e5\u83b7\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u534a\u6210\u54c1\u6309\u5176\u9762\u989d\u7684\uff08\uff09\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5168\u989d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u534a\u989d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56db\u5206\u4e4b\u4e09\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u56db\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\"}]","id":"511930870","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6279\u91cf\u7eb8\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u80fd\u591f\u8fde\u7eed\u591a\u5f20\u81ea\u52a8\u9274\u522b\u7eb8\u5e01\u771f\u5047\u3001\u9274\u522b\u901f\u5ea6\u4e0d\u4f4e\u4e8e\uff08  \uff09\u7684\u673a\u5177\uff0c\u5305\u62ec\u81ea\u52a9\u7eb8\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u548c\u975e\u81ea\u52a9\u7eb8\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001300\u5f20\\\/\u5206\u949f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001500\u5f20\\\/\u5206\u949f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001600\u5f20\\\/\u5206\u949f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001700\u5f20\\\/\u5206\u949f\"}]","id":"511930871","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65b0\u7248\u82f1\u955110\u5143\u5851\u6599\u949e\uff0c\u8367\u5149\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\u7d2b\u5149\u706f\u4e0b\u53ef\u89c1\uff08   \uff09\u8272\u548c\uff08   \uff09\u8272\u83f1\u5f62\u56fe\u6848\u7ec4\u6210\u7684\u8367\u5149\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u201c10\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7d2b\u8272\u548c\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\u548c\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u8272\u548c\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u767d\u8272\u548c\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511930872","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u89c1\u5f69\u72485\u7f8e\u5143\u4e2d\u5171\u6709\uff08  \uff09\u4e2a\u9762\u989d\u6c34\u5370\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e2a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\u4e2a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u4e2a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30014\u4e2a\"}]","id":"511930873","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u501f\u7528\u4e0d\u5f97\u8d85\u8fc7\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300130\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300130\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300160\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300160\u65e5\"}]","id":"511930874","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67d0\u5730\u516c\u5b89\u7834\u83b71\u8d77\u5047\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u6848\u4ef6\uff0c\u67e5\u83b7\u9762\u503c10\u5143\u7684\u5047\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e011\u4e07\u679a\uff0c\u6848\u53d1\u5f53\u65e5\u8be5\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u5e02\u573a\u4ef7\u683c\u8fbe\u523015\u5143\uff0c\u8be5\u6848\u4ef6\u6848\u503c\u4e3a\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300115\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300112\u4e07\u5143\"}]","id":"511930875","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u90e8\u5206\u5047\u5e01\u5728\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u533a\u57df\u6d82\u62b9\u78c1\u6027\u6cb9\u58a8\u7684\u76ee\u7684\u662f\u6b3a\u9a97_______\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u7fa4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u73b0\u949e\u5904\u7406\u8bbe\u5907\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e24\u8005\u7686\u662f\"}]","id":"511930876","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\u5217\u51fa\u4e86\uff08  \uff09\u9879\u7eb8\u5e01\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u548c\uff08   \uff09\u9879\u786c\u5e01\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300113\u300118\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300118\u300113\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300113\u300111\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300111\u300113\"}]","id":"511930877","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5730\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u5355\u9879\u5956\u52b1\u8d39\u7528\u5ba1\u6279\u6743\u9650\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300115\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511930878","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\uff08  \uff09\u662f\u949e\u7968\u5370\u5237\u5e94\u7528\u5386\u53f2\u6700\u957f\u3001\u6700\u666e\u53ca\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51f9\u7248\u5370\u5237\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930879","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u62d2\u7edd\u3001\u963b\u6320\u3001\u9003\u907f\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u68c0\u67e5\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u8c0e\u62a5\u3001\u9690\u533f\u3001\u9500\u6bc1\u76f8\u5173\u8bc1\u636e\u6750\u6599\u7684\uff0c\u6709\u5173\u6cd5\u5f8b\u3001\u884c\u653f\u6cd5\u89c4\u6709\u5904\u7f5a\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\uff0c\u4f9d\u7167\u5176\u89c4\u5b9a\u7ed9\u4e88\u5904\u7f5a\uff1b\u6709\u5173\u6cd5\u5f8b\u3001\u884c\u653f\u6cd5\u89c4\u672a\u4f5c\u5904\u7f5a\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e88\u4ee5\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08\u00a0\u00a0 \uff09\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u00a0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511930880","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u79cd\u60c5\u51b5\u4e0d\u9002\u7528\u73b0\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u90e8\u95e8\u7834\u83b7\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u6848\u4ef6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5de5\u5546\u884c\u653f\u90e8\u95e8\u67e5\u83b7\u5927\u91cf\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6d77\u5173\u90e8\u95e8\u7f34\u83b7\u5927\u91cf\u8fc7\u5173\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u90e8\u95e8\u7834\u83b7\u4f2a\u9020\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6848\u4ef6\"}]","id":"511930881","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u89c1\uff08 \uff09\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001CNY100\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001RMB100\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001100\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u00a5100\"}]","id":"511930882","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u65b9\u5370\u6709\u6c49\u8bed\u62fc\u97f3\u548c\uff08\uff09\u5c11\u6570\u6c11\u65cf\u6587\u5b57\u7684\u201c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8499\u3001\u85cf\u3001\u56de\u3001\u7ef4\u56db\u79cd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8499\u3001\u85cf\u3001\u7ef4\u3001\u58ee\u56db\u79cd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8499\u3001\u6ee1\u3001\u85cf\u3001\u7ef4\u56db\u79cd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8499\u3001\u85cf\u3001\u56de\u3001\u6ee1\u56db\u79cd\"}]","id":"511930883","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u72af\u7f6a\u6570\u989d\uff0c\u6309\u7167\uff08    \uff09\u4e2d\u56fd\u5916\u6c47\u4ea4\u6613\u4e2d\u5fc3\u516c\u5e03\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5bf9\u8be5\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u4e2d\u95f4\u4ef7\u6298\u5408\u6210\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u8ba1\u7b97\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6848\u53d1\u5f53\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e0a\u7f34\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u7acb\u6848\u65e5\"}]","id":"511930884","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u662f\u6211\u56fd\u7684\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u662f\u6211\u56fd\u5883\u5185\uff08\uff09\u7684\u652f\u4ed8\u624b\u6bb5\uff0c\u4efb\u4f55\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u4e2a\u4eba\u4e0d\u5f97\u62d2\u6536\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6700\u666e\u53ca\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6700\u57fa\u7840\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6700\u6839\u672c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6700\u4fbf\u6377\"}]","id":"511930885","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e00\u7248100\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5168\u606f\u6807\u8bc6\u5728\u7968\u9762\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\"}]","id":"511930886","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u8f831999\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930887","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2008\u5e74\u53d1\u884c\uff08   \uff09\u7968\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\u589e\u52a0\u6de1\u7d2b\u8272\uff0c\u5e76\u9010\u6e10\u878d\u5165\u63a5\u8fd1\u949e\u7968\u8fb9\u7f18\u7684\u989c\u8272\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f69\u72485\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5f69\u724850\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5f69\u724810\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5f69\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511930888","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u82f1\u9551\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7ec4\u5408\u4e2d\u6709\u4e00\u4e2a\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5355\u8272\u5f02\u5f62\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u5f02\u5f62\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u7b49\u9ad8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5355\u8272\u5f02\u5f62\"}]","id":"511930889","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u987b\u5728\u56fe\u6837\u4e2d\u90e8\u660e\u663e\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6807\u6ce8\u6e05\u6670\u53ef\u8fa8\u7684\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\uff0c\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u957f\u5ea6\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u5206\u522b\u4e0d\u4f4e\u4e8e\u56fe\u6837\u957f\u5ea6\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u7684\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e8c\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001B.\u4e09\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56db\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e94\u5206\u4e4b\u4e8c\"}]","id":"511930890","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u7248100\u5143\u80cc\u9762\u4e0b\u65b9\u7684\u51f9\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001RMB\uff0cRMB100\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001RMB100\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001RMB100\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001100\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"}]","id":"511930891","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u72485\u300110\u548c20\u6b27\u5143\u589e\u52a0\u7684\u4e00\u9879\u91cd\u8981\u89e6\u89c9\u7279\u5f81\u662f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u4e0a\u4e0b\u8fb9\u6709\u82e5\u5e72\u7ec4\u51f8\u8d77\u7684\u77ed\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u5404\u6709\u4e00\u7ec4\u51f8\u8d77\u7684\u77ed\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u53f3\u8fb9\u5404\u6709\u82e5\u5e72\u51f8\u8d77\u7684\u77ed\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0a\u548c\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u5404\u6709\u4e00\u7ec4\u51f8\u8d77\u7684\u77ed\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511930892","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5173\u4e8e\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f()","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u662f\u5370\u5237\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u822a\u5929\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u4e0e2015\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5f20\u542b\u6709\u7684\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u989c\u8272\u76f8\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7b2c\u4e8c\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u548c2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u542b\u6709\u7684\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u989c\u8272\u76f8\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u662f\u6240\u6709\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e4b\u4e00\"}]","id":"511930893","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"04\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u4e0e96\u7248\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u54ea\u4e2a\u5238\u522b\u7684\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5927\u5e45\u8c03\u6574\u4e86\u4f4d\u7f6e\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511930894","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u65f6\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u60c5\u5f62\u53ef\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u4fe1\u606f\u586b\u5199\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u540c\u4e00\u680f\u5185\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u76f8\u540c\u5e01\u79cd\u3001\u7248\u522b\u3001\u5238\u522b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u76f8\u540c\u5e01\u79cd\u3001\u7248\u522b\u3001\u5238\u522b\uff0c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u8fde\u53f7\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u76f8\u540c\u5e01\u79cd\u3001\u7248\u522b\u3001\u5238\u522b\uff0c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u524d6\u4f4d\u76f8\u540c\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9664\u76f8\u540c\u5e01\u79cd\u3001\u7248\u522b\u3001\u5238\u522b\uff0c\u4e14\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u5b8c\u5168\u4e00\u81f4\u5916\u5747\u4e0d\u80fd\u586b\u5199\u5728\u7edf\u4e00\u680f\"}]","id":"511930895","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u800c\u6301\u6709\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\uff0c\u6570\u989d\u7279\u522b\u5de8\u5927\u7684\uff0c\u5904\u5341\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u6216\u8005\u6ca1\u6536\u8d22\u4ea7\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u4e07\u300150\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\u4e07\u300110\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u4e07\u300120\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012\u4e07\u300120\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930896","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u7279\u6b8a\u6b8b\u7f3a\u6c61\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\u4e00\u5f0f\uff08 \uff09\u8054","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511930897","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7684\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5177\u6709\u54ea\u79cd\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff08\uff09\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8367\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u78c1\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9690\u5f62\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\"}]","id":"511930898","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u82f1\u9551\u4e2d\u7684\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u989c\u8272\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u9ec4\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511930899","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5236\u4f5c\u5546\u54c1\u65f6\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u4f7f\u7528(    )\u548c\u8d27\u5e01\u5355\u4f4d","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u56fd\u5fbd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u7269\u5934\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u201c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u201d\u884c\u540d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u56e2\u82b1\"}]","id":"511930900","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u7684\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u91c7\u7528\uff08\uff09\u65b9\u5f0f\u5370\u5237\u800c\u6210\u7684\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u51f9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u80f6\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5e73\u677f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e1d\u5370\"}]","id":"511930901","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u5e74\u7248\u30012005\u5e74\u7248\u53ca2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u4e00\u9879\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e3a\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eba\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511930902","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u65b0\u589e\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6587\u96d5\u523b\u6280\u672f\uff0c\u5176\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001RMB\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u00a5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001CNY\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u00a5\u30011\"}]","id":"511930903","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u57281996\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u4e2d\u54ea\u79cd\u9762\u989d\u6ca1\u6709\u5e94\u7528\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5143\"}]","id":"511930904","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e00\u884c\u4e3a\u53ef\u4ee5\u6784\u6210\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7532\u7528\u603b\u9762\u989d1\u4e07\u5143\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u53c2\u52a0\u8d4c\u535a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7532(\u7cfb\u94f6\u884c\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458)\u5229\u7528\u804c\u52a1\u4e0a\u7684\u4fbf\u5229\uff0c\u4ee5\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u6362\u53d6\u8d27\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7532\u5728\u4e0e\u4ed6\u4eba\u7b7e\u8ba2\u7ecf\u6d4e\u5408\u540c\u65f6\uff0c\u4e3a\u663e\u793a\u81ea\u5df1\u7684\u7ecf\u6d4e\u5b9e\u529b\uff0c\u5c06\u603b\u9762\u989d20\u4e07\u5143\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u5192\u5145\u771f\u5e01\u51fa\u793a\u7ed9\u5bf9\u65b9\u770b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7532\u5c06\u603b\u9762\u989d10\u4e07\u5143\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u8fd0\u8f93\u5230\u5317\u4eac\u3002\"}]","id":"511930905","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0110\u5143\u4e0a\u7684\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u5728\u81ea\u7136\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\uff08\uff09\u8272\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u706f\u4e0b\u5448\uff08\uff09\u8272\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ed1\u3001\u7eff\"}]","id":"511930906","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u987b\u5728\u56fe\u6837\u4e2d\u90e8\u660e\u663e\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6807\u6ce8\u6e05\u6670\u53ef\u8fa8\u7684\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u60c5\u5f62\u9664\u5916\uff1a","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u539f\u6bd4\u4f8b\u5355\u9762\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5728\u6709\u5f62\u8f7d\u4f53\u4e0a\u4f7f\u7528\u5404\u8fb9\u957f\u653e\u5927\u6bd4\u4f8b\u4e3a\u539f\u8fb9\u957f1.25\u500d\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5728\u6570\u5b57\u8f7d\u4f53\u4e0a\u4f7f\u7528\u5206\u8fa8\u738730\u50cf\u7d20\\\/\u5398\u7c73\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\"}]","id":"511930907","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u724850\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u8f831999\u5e74\u724850\u5143\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u79cd\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930908","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5218\u67d0\u8d2a\u56fe\u5c0f\u4fbf\u5b9c\uff0c\u5c061\u4e07\u7f8e\u5143\u5916\u6c47\u4ee56.5\u4e07\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\u4ef7\u683c\u51fa\u552e\u7ed9\u5468\u67d0\u3002\u56de\u5bb6\u540e\u53d1\u73b06.5\u4e07\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e2d\u67093\u4e07\u5143\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u62a5\u8b66\u540e\u516c\u5b89\u5c06\u5468\u67d0\u6293\u83b7\u3002\u5468\u67d0\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u4ee5\uff08  \uff09\u5b9a\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51fa\u552e\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511930909","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u8054\u90a6\u50a8\u5907\u94f6\u884c\u5238\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u4eba\u50cf\u4e24\u4fa7\u5206\u522b\u5370\u6709\u5370\u7ae0\uff0c\u5176\u4e2d\u5de6\u4fa7\u4e3a\u8054\u90a6\u50a8\u5907\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u5370\uff0c\u53f3\u4fa7\u4e3a\uff08\u00a0\u00a0\uff09\u7f8e\u56fd\u56fd\u5e93\u5370\u7ae0","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u68d5\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"}]","id":"511930910","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u4f5c\u51fa\u7684\u6709\u5173\u6536\u7f34\u5177\u4f53\u884c\u653f\u884c\u4e3a\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5728\u6536\u5230\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08\uff09\u5185\u5411\u76f4\u63a5\u76d1\u7ba1\u8be5\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7684\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7533\u8bf7\u884c\u653f\u590d\u8bae\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u4f9d\u6cd5\u63d0\u8d77\u884c\u653f\u8bc9\u8bbc\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300130\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300160\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300130\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300160\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"}]","id":"511930911","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5206\u652f\u884c\u6536\u5230\u603b\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6279\u590d\u540e\uff0c\u5e94\u53ca\u65f6\u5728\u53cd\u5047\u5b50\u7cfb\u7edf\u4e2d\u767b\u8bb0\u3001\u5206\u89e3\u6279\u590d\uff0c\u751f\u6210\uff08 \uff09\u53d1\u9001\u9500\u6bc1\u884c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6279\u590d\u8868\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u8f6c\u6279\u590d\u8868\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6279\u590d\u300b\"}]","id":"511930912","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u4e2d\u5bf9\u7834\u83b7\u4f2a\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5370\u5236\u7a9d\u70b9\uff0c\u6700\u9ad8\u5956\u52b1\u6807\u51c6\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u4e07\u5143\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300118\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300125\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130\"}]","id":"511930913","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u8bef\u4ed8\u4e8610000\u5143\u5047\u65e5\u5143\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u53ef\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7f5a\u6b3e1000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e0d\u4e88\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\"}]","id":"511930914","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"50\u82f1\u9551\u52a8\u6001\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u8272\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a59\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\"}]","id":"511930915","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\uff08JR\/T 0154\u20142017)\u4e2d\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u7eb8\u5e01\uff08banknote\uff09\u662f\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u4f9d\u6cd5\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u3001\u4ee5\uff08 \uff09\u4e3a\u57fa\u7840\u5370\u5236\u7684\u3001\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7eb8\u5f20\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u91d1\u5c5e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5851\u6599\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7279\u5b9a\u627f\u8f7d\u7269\"}]","id":"511930916","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e9b\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e2019\u72481\u5143\u5238\u7968\u9762\u7684\u8c03\u6574\u8303\u56f4\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d6\u6d88\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5de6\u4fa7\u589e\u52a0\u88c5\u9970\u7eb9\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53d6\u6d88\u4e86\u53f3\u4fa7\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8c03\u6574\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u6837\u5f0f\"}]","id":"511930917","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53e4\u94b1\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5929\u5b89\u95e8\u57ce\u697c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u548c\u5e73\u9e3d\"}]","id":"511930918","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6a2a\u7ad6\u53cc\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a2a\u7ad6\u5f02\u5f62\u53cc\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511930919","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u7b2c\u4e09\u65b9\u6e05\u5206\u670d\u52a1\u5916\u5305\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u57f9\u8bad\u6548\u679c\u3001\u5c97\u4f4d\u8003\u6838\u7531\uff08 \uff09\u8d1f\u8d23\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7b2c\u4e09\u65b9\u6e05\u5206\u670d\u52a1\u5916\u5305\u516c\u53f8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e0e\u7b2c\u4e09\u65b9\u6e05\u5206\u670d\u52a1\u5916\u5305\u516c\u53f8\u5171\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7b2c\u4e09\u65b9\u6e05\u5206\u670d\u52a1\u5916\u5305\u516c\u53f8\u6240\u5728\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"}]","id":"511930920","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5355\u4f4d\u6216\u4e2a\u4eba\u5370\u5236\u3001\u53d1\u552e\u4ee3\u5e01\u7968\u5238\uff0c\u4ee5\u4ee3\u66ff\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5728\u5e02\u573a\u4e0a\u6d41\u901a\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ef\u8d23\u4ee4\u5176\u505c\u6b62\u8fdd\u6cd5\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300120\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930921","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u7684\u65e5\u5e38\u529e\u4e8b\u673a\u6784\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u529e\u516c\u5ba4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u79d8\u4e66\u5904\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u8054\u7edc\u5904\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u5de5\u4f5c\u7ec4\"}]","id":"511930922","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u884c\u4e3a\u4eba\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u4f7f\u7528\u7684,\u4ee5\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\uff08 \uff09\uff1b\u4f46\u884c\u4e3a\u4eba\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u53c8\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\uff0c\u4ee5\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\u548c\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u3001\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\uff1b\u4ece\u8f7b\u5904\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4ece\u8f7b\u5904\u7f5a\uff1b\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\uff1b\u6570\u7f6a\u5e76\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ece\u8f7b\u5904\u7f5a\uff1b\u6570\u7f6a\u5e76\u7f5a\"}]","id":"511930923","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ece\u7968\u5e45\u770b\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5404\u5238\u522b\u7684\u7968\u5e45\u5bbd\u5206\u4e3a_______\u6863\uff0c\u7968\u5e45\u957f\u5219\u6309\u7968\u9762\u5927\u5c0f\u4ece100\u5143\u5238\u52305\u5143\u5238\uff0c\u4ee5_______\u6beb\u7c73\u4e3a\u7ea7\u5dee\u9012\u51cf\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30014\u30016\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u30015\"}]","id":"511930924","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e5\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110000\u65e5\u5143\"}]","id":"511930925","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5f20\u575a\u97e7\u8010\u78e8\uff0c\u5176\u4e3b\u8981\u6210\u5206\u4e3a(  )\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u68c9\u548c\u9ebb\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u68c9\u548c\u805a\u5408\u7269\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u68c9\u3001\u4e1d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u68c9\u548c\u4e09\u6860\u6811\u76ae\u3000\"}]","id":"511930926","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\uff08\uff09\u8272\u81f3\uff08\uff09\u8272\u4e4b\u95f4\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511930927","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u662f\u4ece\uff08  \uff09\u7248\u5f00\u59cb\u91c7\u7528\u5168\u57cb\u5f0f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7684\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011988\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011990\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011996\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012003\"}]","id":"511930928","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\u4ea7\u54c1\u9762\u5e02\uff08\uff09\u5c06\u4ea7\u54c1\u7167\u7247\u53ca\u8bf4\u660e\u4ea7\u54c1\u5236\u4f5c\u5355\u4f4d\u3001\u89c4\u683c\u6750\u8d28\u3001\u5ba3\u4f20\u65b9\u5f0f\u7b49\u60c5\u51b5\u7684\u6750\u6599\u62a5\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u5907\u6848\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u524d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u524d3\u4e2a\u6708\u5185\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u540e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u540e3\u4e2a\u6708\u5185\"}]","id":"511930929","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u7b2c\u4e00\u5957\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u662f(    )","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u897f\u85cf\u81ea\u6cbb\u533a\u6210\u7acb20\u5468\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u6210\u7acb30\u5468\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56fd\u9645\u513f\u7ae5\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7b2c13\u5c4a\u51ac\u5b63\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514b\u8fd0\u52a8\u4f1a\"}]","id":"511930930","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012005\u5e74\u7248\u30012015\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6a2a\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u78c1\u6027\u7684\u8bf4\u6cd5\uff0c\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u4e2d\u53ea\u6709\u540e6\u4f4d\u9ed1\u8272\u90e8\u5206\u6709\u78c1\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u4e2d\u53ea\u6709\u524d4\u4f4d\u6697\u7ea2\u8272\u90e8\u95e8\u6709\u78c1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a2a\u53f7\u780110\u4f4d\u5b57\u6bcd\u3001\u6570\u5b57\u5747\u65e0\u78c1\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u4e2d10\u4f4d\u5b57\u6bcd\u3001\u6570\u5b57\u5747\u6709\u78c1\u6027\"}]","id":"511930931","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\uff08 \uff09\u673a\u6784\u8d1f\u8d23\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u5de5\u4f5c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5404\u5206\u884c\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7701\u4f1a\uff08\u9996\u5e9c\uff09\u57ce\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u526f\u7701\u7ea7\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5730\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\u4ee5\u4e0a\"}]","id":"511930932","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u6545\u610f\u635f\u6bc1\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u7ed9\u4e8e\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u4ee5\uff08  \uff09\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u5343\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511930933","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u65b0\u589e\u5fae\u7f29\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5176\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e94\u89d2\u661f\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001wu\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001RMB\"}]","id":"511930934","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u65b0\u589e\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\uff0c\u5176\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001RMB\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u00a5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001CNY\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u00a5\u30011\"}]","id":"511930935","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"20\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u5f2f\u66f2\u633a\u5ea6\u5c0f\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\uff08     \uff09\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30010.02\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30010.03\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30010.04\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30010.05\"}]","id":"511930936","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e5\u672c\u94f6\u884c\u7eb8\u5e01\u9996\u6b21\u4ee5\u5973\u6027\u5f62\u8c61\u4f5c\u4e3a\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001D\u72482000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001E\u72485000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001D\u72485000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001E\u724810000\u65e5\u5143\"}]","id":"511930937","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5bf9\u4e8e\u4e3b\u52a8\u4e0a\u4ea4\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\u4e00\u5f0f\u4e09\u4efd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u4e8e\u9274\u5b9a\u6ca1\u6536\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\u4e00\u5f0f\u4e09\u4efd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5bf9\u4e8e\u56de\u7b3c\u5238\u4e2d\u5939\u6742\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\u4e00\u5f0f\u4e8c\u4efd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5bf9\u4e8e\u4e3b\u52a8\u4e0a\u4ea4\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u548c\u56de\u7b3c\u5238\u4e2d\u5939\u6742\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\u4e00\u5f0f\u4e8c\u4efd\"}]","id":"511930938","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9999\u6e2f\u4e09\u5bb6\u53d1\u949e\u884c2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u52a8\u611f\u53d8\u8272\u56fe\u6848\u4e2d\u90fd\u5305\u542b\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d1\u949e\u884c\u6807\u8bc6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u884c\u540d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\"}]","id":"511930939","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e8c\u724820\u6b27\u5143\u7684\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u770b\u5230\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b27\u7f57\u5df4\u5973\u795e\u5934\u50cf 20\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001euro 20\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u20ac20\"}]","id":"511930940","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u72af\u7f6a\u6570\u989d\u4ee5\uff08       \uff09\u8ba1\u7b97","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u679a\u6570\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u521d\u59cb\u53d1\u552e\u4ef7\u683c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u73b0\u884c\u5e02\u573a\u4ef7\u683c\"}]","id":"511930941","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6643\u52a8\u7b2c2\u72485\u300110\u548c20\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\uff0c\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u7684\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\u5448\u73b0\u51fa\u7684\u989c\u8272\u53d8\u5316\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u53d8\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ed1\u53d8\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7fe0\u7eff\u53d8\u6df1\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\u53d8\u9ed1\"}]","id":"511930942","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u3001\u4ee5\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u6362\u53d6\u8d27\u5e01\uff0c\u60c5\u8282\u8f83\u8f7b\u7684\uff0c\u5904\u4e09\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u6216\u8005\u62d8\u5f79\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u6216\u8005\u5355\u5904\uff08\uff09\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff08\uff09\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e07\uff0c10\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011\u4e07\uff0c3\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011\u4e07\uff0c5\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012\u4e07\uff0c20\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930943","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u53ef\u5448\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u8367\u5149\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7d2b\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a58\u9ec4\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"}]","id":"511930944","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4f9d\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u5bf9\u8d27\u5e01\u8fdb\u884c\uff08   \uff09\uff0c\u5bf9\u5047\u5e01\u8fdb\u884c\uff08    \uff09\uff0c\uff08    \uff09\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5411\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u63d0\u51fa\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u3001\u6ca1\u6536\u3001\u4ee3\u66ff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9274\u522b\u3001\u6ca1\u6536\u3001\u534f\u52a9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9274\u522b\u3001\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u534f\u52a9\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u3001\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u4ee3\u66ff\"}]","id":"511930945","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6d59\u6c5f\u7701\u5b81\u6ce2\u5e02\u5949\u5316\u533a\u516c\u5b89\u5c40\u5411\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u7533\u8bf7\u4e00\u7b14\u603b\u989d10\u4e07\u5143\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\uff0c\u5e94\u7531\uff08 \uff09\u5ba1\u6279\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u603b\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u676d\u5dde\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5b81\u6ce2\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5949\u5316\u652f\u884c\"}]","id":"511930946","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2021\u5e747\u670820\u65e5\uff0c\u6cb3\u5357\u591a\u5730\u51fa\u73b0\u7279\u5927\u66b4\u96e8\uff0c\u4e2a\u522b\u5730\u533a\u505c\u6c34\u65ad\u7f51\uff0c\u7ed9\u4eba\u6c11\u7fa4\u4f17\u751f\u6d3b\u9020\u6210\u4e25\u91cd\u56f0\u6270\u3002\u90e8\u5206\u5e02\u6c11\u65e9\u66686\u70b9\u5192\u96e8\u53bb\u8d85\u5e02\u6392\u961f\u8d2d\u7269\uff0c\u4ed6\u4eec\u5927\u591a\u6570\u4eba\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u4e70\u6c34\u3002\u8fd9\u4f53\u73b0\u4e86\u73b0\u91d1\u8f83\u4e4b\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\u6709\u4f55\u4f18\u52bf\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4fdd\u969c\u516c\u4f17\u652f\u4ed8\u6743\u5229\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5e73\u8861\u533a\u57df\u7ecf\u6d4e\u53d1\u5c55\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4fc3\u8fdb\u6587\u5316\u4f20\u64ad\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5728\u6781\u7aef\u60c5\u51b5\u4e0b\u7a33\u5b9a\u516c\u4f17\u9884\u671f\"}]","id":"511930947","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u900f\u660e\u7a97\u662f\u5229\u7528(   )\u900f\u660e\u7279\u6027\u5f00\u53d1\u51fa\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5851\u6599\u6750\u8d28\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ad8\u5149\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56fa\u5b9a\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"}]","id":"511930948","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u6536\u4ed8\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u673a\u5177\u62a5\u8b66\u7684\u949e\u7968\uff0c\u5e94\u5982\u4f55\u5904\u7406\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u518d\u6b21\u4f7f\u7528\u8be5\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\uff0c\u4e24\u6b21\u7ed3\u679c\u4e00\u81f4\u7684\uff0c\u4f9d\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u7ed3\u679c\u8fdb\u884c\u76f8\u5e94\u5904\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u66f4\u6362\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\uff0c\u4e24\u6b21\u7ed3\u679c\u4e00\u81f4\u7684\uff0c\u4f9d\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u7ed3\u679c\u8fdb\u884c\u76f8\u5e94\u5904\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8fdb\u884c\u4eba\u5de5\u9274\u522b\uff0c\u4e0e\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u7ed3\u679c\u4e0d\u4e00\u81f4\u7684\uff0c\u4ee5\u4eba\u5de5\u9274\u522b\u4e3a\u51c6\"}]","id":"511930949","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u201c\u4e16\u754c\u6587\u5316\u548c\u81ea\u7136\u9057\u4ea7\u201d\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7684\u6750\u8d28\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7d2b\u94dc\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ec4\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\"}]","id":"511930950","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7b2c\u4e00\u6b21\u4f7f\u7528\u5168\u606f\u9632\u4f2a\u6807\u8bc6\u662f\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8fce\u63a5\u65b0\u4e16\u7eaa\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53d1\u884c70\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"}]","id":"511930951","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u6309\u89c4\u5b9a\u4fdd\u5b58\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u3001\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\u7b49\u76f8\u5173\u6750\u6599\uff0c\u4fdd\u5b58\u671f\u9650\u4e3a\uff08   \uff09\u5e74\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30017\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\"}]","id":"511930952","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u989c\u8272\u5728\uff08\uff09\u8272\u548c\uff08\uff09\u8272\u4e4b\u95f4\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\"}]","id":"511930953","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u4e0e\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u53ca\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u901a\u77e5\u4e66\u5e94\u5206\u7c7b\u88c5\u8ba2\u5b58\u653e\uff0c\u4fdd\u5b58\uff08\uff09\u5e74\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511930954","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\u8981\u6c42\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u7528\u65e0\u62d2\u949e\u4ed3\u7684\u73b0\u91d1\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u8bef\u8bfb\u7387\u5e94\u5c0f\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\uff08\uff09%\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30010.01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30010.02\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30010.03\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30010.05\"}]","id":"511930955","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u5173\u4e8e\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7ba1\u7406\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08      \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7ba1\u7406\u4e0d\u5305\u62ec\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5b9e\u884c\u5c5e\u5730\u7ba1\u7406\u3001\u4e00\u4e8b\u4e00\u6279\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5f53\u5730\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9000\u51fa\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4e0d\u53d7\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u7ba1\u7406\"}]","id":"511930956","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u7684\u5e93\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5177\u6709\uff08   \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8367\u5149\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ee5\u4e0a\u90fd\u4e0d\u662f\"}]","id":"511930957","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6545\u610f\u6bc1\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u7531\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08\uff09\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015000\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30013\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930958","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u8981\u6309\u7167\u300a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u73b0\u91d1\u4ece\u4e1a\u4eba\u5458\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u8981\u6c42\u300b\uff0c\u7ec4\u7ec7\u5f00\u5c55\u672c\u8f96\u533a\u5185\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u57f9\u8bad\u5de5\u4f5c\u7684\u76d1\u7763\u68c0\u67e5\u3002\u68c0\u67e5\u91c7\u53d6\u73b0\u573a\u548c\u975e\u73b0\u573a\u65b9\u5f0f\u8fdb\u884c\u3002\u975e\u73b0\u573a\u68c0\u67e5\u6bcf\uff08\uff09\u5e74\u5f00\u5c551\u6b21\uff0c\u7ed3\u5408\u975e\u73b0\u573a\u68c0\u67e5\u60c5\u51b5\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u9009\u62e9\u9700\u91cd\u70b9\u5173\u6ce8\u7684\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u6709\u9488\u5bf9\u6027\u5f00\u5c55\u73b0\u573a\u68c0\u67e5\uff0c\u6bcf\uff08\uff09\u5e74\u81f3\u5c11\u7ec4\u7ec7\u5f00\u5c551\u6b21\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\uff0c1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u534a\uff0c\u534a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u534a\uff0c1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011\uff0c2\"}]","id":"511930959","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5404\u7ea7\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\u5e94\uff08\uff09\u5f00\u5c55\u672c\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u4e0e\u5e93\u5b58\u62a5\u8868\u6838\u5bf9\u68c0\u67e5\u5de5\u4f5c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6bcf\u5b63\u5ea6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6bcf\u534a\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6bcf\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6bcf\u6708\"}]","id":"511930960","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012019\u724850\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u89c4\u683c\u5c3a\u5bf8\u4e3a\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001156mm*66mm\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001155mm*77mm\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001145mm*70mm\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001150mm*70mm\"}]","id":"511930961","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e2d\u7684\u80f6\u5370\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\u5b57\u5f62\uff08\uff09\u51f9\u5370\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5927\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7b49\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c0f\u4e8e\"}]","id":"511930962","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u6388\u6743\u8bc1\u4e66\u5230\u671f\u524d\uff08  \uff09\u4e2a\u6708\uff0c\u88ab\u6388\u6743\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u53ef\u5411\u539f\u6388\u6743\u5355\u4f4d\u7533\u8bf7\u518d\u6b21\u6388\u6743","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30016\"}]","id":"511930963","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u54ea\u679a\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u66fe\u8363\u83b7\u514b\u52b3\u65af\u4e16\u754c\u201c\u6700\u4f73\u6d41\u901a\u5e01\u201d\u5956()\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012016\u5e74\u8d3a\u5c81\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\uff08\u7334\u5e74\uff09\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012020\u5e74\u8d3a\u5c81\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\uff08\u9f20\u5e74\uff09\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e16\u754c\u6587\u5316\u548c\u81ea\u7136\u9057\u4ea7--\u6cf0\u5c71\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u201c\u548c\u201d\u5b57\u4e66\u6cd5--\u6977\u4e66\"}]","id":"511930964","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u4e2d\u5bf9\u67e5\u83b7\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u3001\u6301\u6709\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6848\u4ef6\uff0c\u6700\u9ad8\u5956\u52b1\u6807\u51c6\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u4e07\u5143\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300115\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300118\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300125\"}]","id":"511930965","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u5211\u6cd5\u300b\u4e2d\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u72af\u7f6a\u7684\u7c7b\u578b\u6709\uff08   \uff09\u79cd\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30016\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30017\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30018\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30019\"}]","id":"511930966","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4f7f\u7528\u4e3a\u76ee\u7684\uff0c\u4f2a\u9020\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u5916\u5e01\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u4f7f\u7528\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u7684\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u5916\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4ee5\uff08\uff09\u5b9a\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8bc8\u9a97\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b3a\u8bc8\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511930967","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4f7f\u7528\u4e3a\u76ee\u7684\uff0c\u4f2a\u9020\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u4f7f\u7528\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4f9d\u7167\u5211\u6cd5\u7b2c\u4e8c\u767e\u516d\u5341\u516d\u6761\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4ee5\uff08    \uff09\u5b9a\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8bc8\u9a97\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511930968","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u30015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u6750\u8d28\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e0d\u9508\u94a2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u954d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u91d1\u5c5e\"}]","id":"511930969","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u4ee4\u300b\u30142019\u3015\u7b2c2\u53f7\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u81ea2019\u5e74\uff08\uff09\u670815\u65e5\u8d77\u65bd\u884c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30019\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300111\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300112\"}]","id":"511930970","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u6216\u8005\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u800c\u8fd0\u8f93\uff0c\u6570\u989d\u8f83\u5927\u7684\uff0c\u5904\u4e09\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u6216\u8005\u62d8\u5f79\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08 \uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff08 \uff09\u4e07\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e07\u30015\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011\u4e07\u300110\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u4e07\u300110\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012\u4e07\u300120\u4e07 \"}]","id":"511930971","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u53d6\u6d88\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u662f\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6587\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u63a5\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u63a5\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511930972","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\u6307\u51fa\uff0c\u53ef\u4f9b\u786c\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u8bc6\u522b\u7684\u673a\u8bfb\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\u51e0\u79cd\uff1f\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300112\u79cd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300113\u79cd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\u79cd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300118\u79cd\"}]","id":"511930973","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5177\u6709\u4e2d\u56fd\u4f20\u7edf\u5386\u53f2\u6587\u5316\u7279\u8272\u548c\u6c11\u65cf\u7279\u8272\u7684\uff08\uff09\u7eb9\u9970\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u53e4\u4ee3\u6f06\u5668\u82b1\u7eb9\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c11\u6570\u6c11\u65cf\u7684\u6311\u7ee3\u82b1\u7eb9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9752\u94dc\u5668\u4e0a\u7684\u9955\u992e\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4f20\u7edf\u74f7\u5668\u7684\u82b1\u7eb9\"}]","id":"511930974","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7d2b\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a59\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511930975","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u771f\u4f2a\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u81ea\u6536\u7f34\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08 \uff09\u5185,\u6301\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u76f4\u63a5\u6216\u8005\u901a\u8fc7\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u63d0\u51fa\u4e66\u9762\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\"}]","id":"511930976","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u30012020\u7248\u54ea\u4e2a\u5238\u522b\u6ca1\u6709\u5e94\u7528\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff1f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5143\"}]","id":"511930977","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u822a\u5929\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u7684\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\u4f4d\u4e8e\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u795e\u5dde\u4e5d\u53f7\u98de\u8239\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5ae6\u5a25\u4e00\u53f7\u536b\u661f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e1c\u65b9\u7ea2\u4e00\u53f7\u536b\u661f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511930978","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u4e8e\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u76f8\u5173\u7684\u7f51\u7edc\u6216\u5a92\u4f53\u8206\u60c5\u4ee5\u53ca\u53d7\u7406\u7684\u6295\u8bc9\u3001\u4e3e\u62a5\u7b49\u4e8b\u9879\uff0c \u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u53ca\u65f6\u8fdb\u884c\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8ddf\u8e2a\u7814\u7a76\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6743\u5a01\u5224\u522b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6709\u6548\u53cd\u9988\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8c03\u67e5\u53d6\u8bc1\"}]","id":"511930979","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u800c\u6301\u6709\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\uff0c\u6570\u989d\u5de8\u5927\u7684\uff0c\u59043\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a\u5341\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e07\u300110\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\u4e07\u300120\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u4e07\u300120\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u4e07\u300150\u4e07\"}]","id":"511930980","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u6750\u8d28\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e0d\u9508\u94a2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u954d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u94dc\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u94dd\u5408\u91d1\"}]","id":"511930981","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u5370\u7ae0\u4e3a\u77e9\u5f62\uff0c\u5176\u5177\u4f53\u89c4\u683c\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015cm*2.5cm\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30017cm*3.5cm\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014cm*2.5cm\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30016cm*3.5cm\"}]","id":"511930982","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u7834\u6848\u5355\u4f4d\u7684\u5956\u52b1\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\u8be5\u6848\u4ef6\u7834\u83b7\u4e14\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u89e3\u7f34\uff08   \uff09\u540e\uff0c\u7531\u5047\u5e01\u7834\u6848\u5355\u4f4d\u6309\u7a0b\u5e8f\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5f53\u5730\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7533\u8bf7\u5956\u52b1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f53\u5730\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5f53\u5730\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5f53\u5730\u5de5\u5546\u884c\u653f\u7ba1\u7406\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f53\u5730\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"}]","id":"511930983","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u6700\u9ad8\u4eba\u6c11\u68c0\u5bdf\u9662 \u516c\u5b89\u90e8\u5173\u4e8e\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u7ba1\u8f96\u7684\u5211\u4e8b\u6848\u4ef6\u89c4\u5b9a\uff08\u4e8c\uff09\u300b\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u3001\u4ee5\u5047\u5e01\u6362\u53d6\u8d27\u5e01\u603b\u9762\u989d\u5728\uff08  \uff09\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u6216\u5e01\u91cf\u5728\uff08   \uff09\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u4e88\u7acb\u6848\u8ffd\u8bc9\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30014000\u3001400\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012000\u3001200\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013000\u3001300\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011000\u3001100\"}]","id":"511930984","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff082019\u5e74\u7b2c3\u53f7\uff09\u81ea\uff08 \uff09\u5f00\u59cb\u65bd\u884c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012019\u5e7412\u67081\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012020\u5e741\u67081\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012020\u5e742\u67081\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012020\u5e744\u67081\u65e5\"}]","id":"511930985","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u884c\u653f\u8bb8\u53ef\u6cd5\u300b\u53ca\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u53d7\u7406\u201c\u7533\u8bf7\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u7684\u884c\u653f\u8bb8\u53ef\u7533\u8bf7\u540e\uff0c\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5728\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u4f5c\u51fa\u5ba1\u6279\u51b3\u5b9a\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300115\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300130\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300145\"}]","id":"511930986","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6837\u5e01\u53d1\u81f3\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\uff08    \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5730\u5e02\u7ea7\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8bbe\u6709\u53d1\u884c\u5e93\u7684\u53bf\u5e02\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7701\u4f1a\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53bf\uff08\u5e02\uff09\u652f\u884c\"}]","id":"511930987","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67d0\u516c\u5b89\u90e8\u95e8\u9ad8\u5ea6\u91cd\u89c6\u6253\u51fb\u5047\u5e01\u8fdd\u6cd5\u72af\u7f6a\u5de5\u4f5c\uff0c\u8f96\u5185\u67d0\u516c\u5b89\u5c40\u7ecf\u8fde\u7eed\u591a\u6708\u7684\u8c03\u67e5\u5e03\u63a7\uff0c\u6210\u529f\u6363\u6bc1\u4e00\u4f2a\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5370\u5236\u7a9d\u70b9\uff0c\u73b0\u573a\u67e5\u83b7\u5370\u5237\u5047\u5e01\u76f8\u5173\u8bbe\u5907\u4ee5\u53ca\u539f\u6750\u6599\uff0c\u73b0\u573a\u67e5\u83b7\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u6210\u54c1275\u4e07\u5143\u3001\u534a\u6210\u54c1500\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u5e76\u5f53\u573a\u6293\u83b7\u4e3b\u8981\u6d89\u6848\u4eba\u545825\u540d\u3002\u8bf7\u95ee\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5bf9\u8be5\u516c\u5b89\u5c40\u7ed9\u4e88\uff08  \uff09\u4e07\u5143\u7684\u5956\u52b1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30019\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300117\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300122\"}]","id":"511930988","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7531\u6b27\u6d32\u4e2d\u592e\u94f6\u884c\u7edf\u4e00\u8bbe\u8ba1\uff0c\u7531\uff08 \uff09\u8d1f\u8d23\u5370\u5237\u53d1\u884c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b27\u6d32\u4e2d\u592e\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b27\u5143\u533a\u5404\u6210\u5458\u56fd\u4e2d\u592e\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b27\u6d32\u4e2d\u592e\u94f6\u884c\u7cfb\u7edf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b27\u76df\u59d4\u5458\u4f1a\"}]","id":"511930989","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u5730\u56fe\u3001\u6865\u6881\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5448\u73b0\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u8272","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e0d\u53d1\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6a59\u8272\"}]","id":"511930990","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e5\u672c\u94f6\u884c\u7eb8\u5e01\u9996\u6b21\u4ee5\u5973\u6027\u5f62\u8c61\u4f5c\u4e3a\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001D\u72481000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001D\u72482000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001E\u72482000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001D\u72485000\u65e5\u5143\"}]","id":"511930991","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b,\u5bf9\u8de8\u7701\uff08\u81ea\u6cbb\u533a\u3001\u76f4\u8f96\u5e02\uff09\u5047\u5e01\u6848\u4ef6\u7684\u5956\u52b1\uff0c\u7531\uff08  \uff09\u5ba1\u6279\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6848\u53d1\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u603b\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u63a5\u6536\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e3b\u72af\u6237\u7c4d\u6240\u5728\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"}]","id":"511930992","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5c3a\u5bf8\u5f62\u72b6\u53d1\u751f\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u7968\u5e45\u957f\u8fb9\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u683c\u76f8\u5dee \uff08   \uff09%\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511930993","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7ad6\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u989c\u8272\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ed1\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u672a\u8bbe\u7f6e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"}]","id":"511930994","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u989c\u8272\u5728\uff08  \uff09\u81f3\uff08  \uff09\u95f4\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u54c1\u7ea2\u8272\uff0c\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u54c1\u7ea2\u8272\uff0c\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u54c1\u7ea2\u8272\uff0c\u91d1\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u8272\uff0c\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511930995","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u4e2d\u5bf9\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u7834\u6848\u67e5\u83b7\u7684\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u534a\u6210\u54c1\uff0c\u6309\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u79cd\u65b9\u5f0f\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6309\u9762\u989d\u7684\u4e00\u534a\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6309\u5168\u989d\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6309\u5168\u989d\u4e58\u4ee570%\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e0d\u4e88\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\"}]","id":"511930996","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\u7684\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8367\u5149\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5f02\u578b\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ee5\u4e0a\u90fd\u4e0d\u662f\"}]","id":"511930997","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6d88\u8d39\u53ca\u652f\u4ed8\u65b9\u5f0f\u521b\u65b0\u8981\u575a\u6301\u6709\u5229\u4e8e\u7545\u901a\u652f\u4ed8\u6d41\u901a\u73af\u5883\u3001\u6709\u5229\u4e8e\u4fdd\u969c\u6c11\u751f\u3001\u6709\u5229\u4e8e\u63d0\u5347\u516c\u4f17\u7684\u5e78\u798f\u611f\u548c\u83b7\u5f97\u611f\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u91c7\u53d6\u6b67\u89c6\u6027\u6216\u975e\u4fbf\u5229\u6027\u63aa\u65bd\u6392\u65a5\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\uff0c\u9020\u6210\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u201c\u6570\u5b57\u9e3f\u6c9f\u201d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u201c\u9ad8\u8d28\u91cf\u53d1\u5c55\u6096\u8bba\u201d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u201c\u4fee\u6614\u5e95\u5fb7\u9677\u9631\u201d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u201c\u79d1\u6280\u9e3f\u6c9f\u201d\"}]","id":"511930998","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u89c1\uff08 \uff09\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u00a5100\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001RMB100\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001100\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001CNY100\"}]","id":"511930999","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6309\u7167\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6709\u5173\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\uff08\u00a0 \uff09\u5bf9\u529e\u7406\u8d27\u5e01\u6536\u4ed8\u3001\u6e05\u5206\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u6c34\u5e73\u8fdb\u884c\u8bc4\u4f30\uff0c\u786e\u4fdd\u5176\u5177\u5907\u5224\u65ad\u548c\u6311\u5254\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u4e13\u4e1a\u80fd\u529b\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u529e\u516c\u5ba4\"}]","id":"511931000","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\uff08\uff09\u8272\u81f3\uff08\uff09\u8272\u4e4b\u95f4\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511931001","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6709\u51e0\u79cd\u9762\u989d\uff0c\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30017\u79cd\uff0c5\u300120\u300150\u3001100\u3001200\u3001500\u548c1000\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30018\u79cd\uff0c1\u30015\u300110\u300120\u300150\u3001100\u3001200\u548c500\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30017\u79cd\uff0c5\u300110\u300120\u300150\u3001100\u3001200\u548c500\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30018\u79cd\uff0c1\u30015\u300110\u300120\u300150\u3001100\u3001200\u548c500\u6b27\u5143\"}]","id":"511931002","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\u5bf9\u7ed3\u679c\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\uff0c\u67e5\u8be2\u53d7\u7406\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u544a\u77e5\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\u5728\uff08\uff09\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7533\u8bf7\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30017\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012\"}]","id":"511931003","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53d8\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\uff0c\u6570\u989d\u8f83\u5927\u7684\uff0c\u5904\uff08 \uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u6216\u8005\u62d8\u5f79\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u6216\u8005\u5355\u5904\u4e00\u4e07\u4ee5\u4e0a\u5341\u4e07\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30017\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u5e74\"}]","id":"511931004","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248200\u6b27\u5143\u5728\uff08 \uff09\u7684\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6709\uff08 \uff09\u77ed\u7ebf\u4f5c\u4e3a\u89c6\u969c\u4eba\u58eb\u8bc6\u522b\u949e\u7968\u7684\u6807\u8bb0.","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u8fb9\uff0c1\u7ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u8fb9\uff0c1\u7ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u4e0b\u8fb9\uff0c\u54041\u7ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u4e0b\u8fb9\uff0c2\u7ec4\"}]","id":"511931005","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u91d1\u878d\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c100\u5143\u5f2f\u66f2\u633a\u5ea6\u82e5\uff08    \uff090.05\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5927\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c0f\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5927\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c0f\u4e8e\"}]","id":"511931006","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\u7684\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u4e3a\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8367\u5149\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5f02\u578b\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ee5\u4e0a\u90fd\u4e0d\u662f\"}]","id":"511931007","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u9274\u5b9a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5e94\u5f53\u51fa\u5177\u6309\u7167\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u7edf\u4e00\u89c4\u8303\u5236\u4f5c\u7684\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\uff0c\u5e76\u52a0\u76d6\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e13\u7528\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e13\u7528\u7ae0\u548c\u9274\u5b9a\u4eba\u540d\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u5b9a\u4e13\u7528\u7ae0\u548c\u9274\u5b9a\u4eba\u540d\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u5b9a\u4e13\u7528\u7ae0\"}]","id":"511931008","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u662f\uff08     \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5370\u5237\u533a\u57df\u51fa\u73b0\u591a\u5904\u6c61\u6e0d\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u6c61\u6e0d\u9762\u79ef120mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e00\u5904\u6495\u88c2\uff0c\u6495\u88c2\u957f\u5ea68mm\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5f62\u72b6\u3001\u5c3a\u5bf8\u53d1\u751f\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\u7968\u5e45\u957f\u8fb9\u4ee5\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u683c\u76f8\u5dee1.5%\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e00\u5904\u70ad\u5316\uff0c\u5176\u70ad\u5316\u9762\u79ef12mm\u00b2\"}]","id":"511931009","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u5b8c\u6bd5\u540e\u5e94\u586b\u5236\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u786e\u8ba4\u8868\u300b\u5e76\u59a5\u5584\u4fdd\u7ba1\uff0c\u4fdd\u7ba1\u671f\u9650\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u5e74\"}]","id":"511931010","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u767d\u6c34\u5370\u4f4d\u4e8e\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u5de6\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\"}]","id":"511931011","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u9762\u989d\u4e2d\uff0c\u54ea\u79cd\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u51f9\u5370\u76f2\u6587\u6807\u8bb0\u3002\uff08   \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001100\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001200\u6b27\u5143\"}]","id":"511931012","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e2a\u673a\u6784\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u4e4b\u4e00\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5b81\u6ce2\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6df1\u5733\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53a6\u95e8\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e5d\u6c5f\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"}]","id":"511931013","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5916\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u548c\u5404\u79cd\u786c\u5e01\uff0c\u7ecf\u9274\u5b9a\u4e3a\u771f\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u4ea4\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u9000\u8fd8\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\uff0c\u5e76\u6536\u56de\uff08\uff09\uff1b\u7ecf\u9274\u5b9a\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u9000\u56de\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u4f9d\u6cd5\u6536\u7f34\uff0c\u5e76\u5411\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u51fa\u5177\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u3001\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\u3001\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u3001\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"}]","id":"511931014","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\u7684\u84dd\u8272\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u7167\u5c04\u4e0b\u53ef\u89c1\uff08  \uff09\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u84dd\u8272\u8367\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\u8367\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\u8367\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\u8367\u5149\"}]","id":"511931015","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u4e2d\u6240\u79f0\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u662f\u6307\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u548c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u3001\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u548c\u6d41\u901a\u786c\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u548c\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e3b\u5e01\u548c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u8f85\u5e01\"}]","id":"511931016","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u548c\u4e2d\u94f6\u9999\u6e2f\u4e09\u5bb6\u94f6\u884c\u949e\u7968\u4e0a\u7684\u73e0\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ca4\u9c7c\u3001\u72ee\u5b50\u548c\u884c\u6807\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u795e\u9f9f\u3001\u5efa\u7b51\u548c\u4e2d\u94f6\u5927\u53a6\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u795e\u517d\u3001\u884c\u6807\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7965\u4e91\u3001\u884c\u6807\u548c\u4e2d\u94f6\u5927\u53a6\"}]","id":"511931017","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9999\u6e2f\u76843\u5bb6\u53d1\u949e\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08   \uff09\uff0c\u5176\u4e2d\u53d1\u884c\u91cf\u5360\u6bd4\u6700\u5927\u7684\u94f6\u884c\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u82b1\u65d7\u94f6\u884c\u548c\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u82b1\u65d7\u94f6\u884c\u548c\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\uff0c\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u548c\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\uff0c\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6469\u6839\u5927\u901a\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u82b1\u65d7\u94f6\u884c\u548c\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\uff0c\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\"}]","id":"511931018","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65b0\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u516c\u5e03\u53d1\u884c\u524d\u7684\u6837\u5e01\u5c5e\u4e8e\u56fd\u5bb6\u79d8\u5bc6\uff0c\u4fdd\u5bc6\u7b49\u7ea7\u4e3a\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7edd\u5bc6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u673a\u5bc6\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u79d8\u5bc6\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5de5\u4f5c\u79d8\u5bc6\"}]","id":"511931019","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u80cc\u9762\u4eba\u6c11\u5927\u4f1a\u5802\u5916\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u5177\u6709\uff08\uff09\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8367\u5149\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ea2\u5916\u914d\u5bf9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931020","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6643\u52a82004\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\u65f6\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u89c2\u5bdf\u5230\u58a8\u6c34\u74f6\u91cc\u81ea\u7531\u949f\u548c\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57100\u7684\u989c\u8272\u53d8\u5316\u5206\u522b\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53e4\u94dc\u53d8\u7eff\u3001\u53e4\u94dc\u53d8\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u53d8\u84dd\u3001\u53e4\u94dc\u53d8\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\u53d8\u9ed1\u3001\u7eff\u53d8\u9ed1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53e4\u94dc\u53d8\u7eff\u3001\u7eff\u53d8\u9ed1\"}]","id":"511931021","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5c45\u4f4f\u5728\u5e7f\u5dde\u7684\u5f20\u67d0\u4f2a\u9020\u4e86\u5927\u91cf\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u5077\u8fd0\u81f3\u5317\u4eac\u51fa\u552e\u725f\u5229\u3002\u5f20\u67d0\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u5e94\u5982\u4f55\u5b9a\u7f6a\uff1f(  )","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51fa\u552e\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\u3001\u51fa\u552e\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511931022","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1993\u5e74\u7248\u65e5\u5143\u5e8f\u5217\u53f7\u989c\u8272\u4ece\u9ed1\u8272\u6539\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u68d5\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511931023","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2016\u5e74\uff0c\u72af\u7f6a\u5acc\u7591\u4eba\u5434\u67d0\u3001\u5218\u67d0\u3001\u674e\u67d0\u5408\u4f19\u51fa\u8d44\u4f2a\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u7531\u674e\u67d0\u8d1f\u8d23\u5728\u6e56\u5357\u7701\u5e38\u5b81\u5e02\u7b79\u5efa\u5047\u5e01\u751f\u4ea7\u7a9d\u70b9\uff0c\u8d3e\u67d0\u5236\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7248\u6837\u3002\u4ece2017\u5e743\u6708\u5f00\u59cb\u5434\u67d0\u3001\u5218\u67d0\u3001\u674e\u67d0\u4e09\u4eba\u5206\u522b\u901a\u8fc7\u4e0d\u540c\u9014\u5f84\u628a\u5370\u5237\u597d\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u5206\u5934\u51fa\u552e\uff0c\u6240\u6709\u9500\u552e\u8d27\u6b3e\u5168\u90e8\u4ea4\u7531\u5434\u67d0\u6838\u7b97\uff0c\u6263\u9664\u6210\u672c\u540e\u4ee5\u73b0\u91d1\u5f62\u5f0f\u5206\u8d43\u3002\u8d75\u67d0\u8d2d\u4e70500\u5f20100\u5143\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u901a\u8fc7\u5728\u5c0f\u5e97\u6362\u94b1\u7b49\u65b9\u5f0f\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u4f7f\u7528\u51fa\u53bb\u30022017\u5e744\u6708\uff0c\u5218\u67d0\u8bf7\u670b\u53cb\u5f20\u67d0\u3001\u53f6\u67d0\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u5206\u522b\u5230\u8fd0\u8f93\u5230\u5e7f\u5dde\u3001\u6cf0\u56fd\u65f6\uff0c\u5206\u522b\u88ab\u5e7f\u5dde\u8b66\u65b9\u548c\u6d77\u5173\u6293\u83b7\uff0c\u968f\u540e\u5e7f\u5dde\u8b66\u65b9\u987a\u85e4\u6478\u74dc\uff0c\u76f8\u7ee7\u6293\u83b7\u4e86\u4e0a\u8ff0\u72af\u7f6a\u5acc\u7591\u4eba\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u4e2d\u4e0d\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5434\u67d0\u3001\u5218\u67d0\u3001\u674e\u67d0\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u5e94\u6309\u7167\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8d3e\u67d0\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u5e94\u6309\u7167\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\u5b9a\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8d75\u67d0\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u4f7f\u7528\uff0c\u5e94\u4ee5\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\u5b9a\u7f6a\uff0c\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5f20\u67d0\u3001\u53f6\u67d0\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u5747\u5c5e\u4e8e\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511931024","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9648\u67d0\u5728\u51fa\u552e\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u65f6\u88ab\u5f53\u573a\u6293\u83b7\uff0c\u73b0\u573a\u53d1\u73b0\u5df2\u51fa\u552e\u7ed9\u8d2d\u4e70\u65b9\u5047\u5e011\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u5728\u9648\u67d0\u8eab\u4e0a\u67e5\u83b7\u5047\u5e013\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u540c\u65f6\u5728\u73b0\u573a\u9648\u67d0\u9a7e\u9a76\u7684\u8f7f\u8f66\u5185\u53d1\u73b02\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u5728\u9648\u67d0\u4f4f\u6240\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e015\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u5e94\u8ba4\u5b9a\u9648\u67d0\u51fa\u552e\u5047\u5e01\uff08    \uff09\u4e07\u5143\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30016\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300111\"}]","id":"511931025","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u5177\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8367\u5149\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u7279\u5f81\"}]","id":"511931026","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u7f16\u53f7\u89c4\u5219\u4e3a\u201c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7f16\u7801\u201d+4\u4f4d\u6570\u5b57\u201c\u5e74\u4efd\u201d+\uff08\uff09\u4f4d\uff08\u81f3\u5c11\uff09\u6570\u5b57\u201c\u4e1a\u52a1\u6d41\u6c34\u53f7\u201d\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30016\"}]","id":"511931027","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u7684\u7275\u5934\u5355\u4f4d\u662f\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u53ec\u96c6\u4eba\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\uff0c\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u603b\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u957f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u957f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u5c40\u5c40\u957f\"}]","id":"511931028","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u672a\u7ecf\u8bb8\u53ef\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6216\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u6309\u7167\uff08   \uff09\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u884c\u653f\u8bb8\u53ef\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\"}]","id":"511931029","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u6216\u8005\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u800c\u8fd0\u8f93\uff0c\u6570\u989d\u8f83\u5927\u7684\uff0c\u5904\u4e09\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u6216\u8005\u62d8\u5f79\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08 \uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff08 \uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e07\u30015\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011\u4e07\u300110\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012\u4e07\u300120\u4e07\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u4e07\u300150\u4e07\"}]","id":"511931030","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u63b7\u94c1\u997c\u8005\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8dd1\u6b65\u4eba\u50cf\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u672a\u8bbe\u7f6e\"}]","id":"511931031","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9999\u6e2f\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u7eb8\u5e01\u6709\u51e0\u79cd\u9762\u989d\uff0c\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30016\u79cd\uff0c10\u300120\u300150\u3001100\u3001500\u548c1000\u6e2f\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\u79cd\uff0c20\u300150\u3001100\u3001500\u548c1000\u6e2f\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u79cd\uff0c50\u3001100\u3001200\u3001500\u548c100\u6e2f\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30016\u79cd\uff0c5\u300110\u300120\u300150\u3001100\u548c1000\u6e2f\u5143\"}]","id":"511931032","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5728\u65b0\u4e0a\u5c97\u73b0\u91d1\u4ece\u4e1a\u4eba\u5458\u4e0a\u5c97 \uff08\uff09\u5185\u5b8c\u6210\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u77e5\u8bc6\u4e0e\u6280\u80fd\u57f9\u8bad\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u4e2a\u6708\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u4e2a\u6708\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30016\u4e2a\u6708\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30019\u4e2a\u6708\"}]","id":"511931033","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u4e2d\u5bf9\u6363\u6bc1\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u518d\u52a0\u5de5\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\u3001\u6253\u5370\u6216\u590d\u5370\u7a9d\u70b9\uff0c\u6700\u9ad8\u5956\u52b1\u6807\u51c6\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u4e07\u5143\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300115\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300118\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300125\"}]","id":"511931034","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7684\u73e0\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\"}]","id":"511931035","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u90e8\u5206\u80f6\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5448\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u8367\u5149\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6a59\u8272\"}]","id":"511931036","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u4f5c\u51fa\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u7ed3\u679c\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5728\u6536\u5230\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d7760\u65e5\u5185\uff0c\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5411\u8be5\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u6240\u5728\u5730\u7684\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u63d0\u51fa\u884c\u653f\u590d\u8bae\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5411\u8be5\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u6240\u5728\u5730\u7684\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u63d0\u51fa\u884c\u653f\u8bc9\u8bbc\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5411\u8be5\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u6240\u5728\u5730\u7684\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u63d0\u51fa\u884c\u653f\u590d\u8bae\u6216\u8bc9\u8bbc\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ee5\u4e0a\u8bf4\u6cd5\u90fd\u4e0d\u5bf9\"}]","id":"511931037","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u622a\u81f32021\u5e747\u6708\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u4e00\u5171\u53d1\u884c\u4e86\uff08    \uff09\u5f20\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511931038","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\u5bf9\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u5355\u72ec\u7ba1\u7406\uff0c\u5e76\uff08   \uff09\uff0c\u8d26\u5b9e\u5206\u7ba1\uff0c\u786e\u4fdd\u8d26\u5b9e\u76f8\u7b26\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5efa\u7acb\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4ee3\u4fdd\u7ba1\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5efa\u7acb\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4ee3\u4fdd\u7ba1\u767b\u8bb0\u5236\u5ea6\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5efa\u7acb\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u767b\u8bb0\u5236\u5ea6\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5efa\u7acb\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\"}]","id":"511931039","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65b0\u7248\u82f1\u95515\u5143\u5851\u6599\u949e\uff0c\u53d8\u8272\u7a97\u6846\u53ca\u6587\u5b57\u8f6c\u52a8\u949e\u7968\u65f6\uff0c\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u900f\u660e\u7a97\u6846\u53ca\u91cc\u9762\u7684\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\u201c\u00a3\u201d\uff0c\u989c\u8272\u4f1a\u7531\uff08    \uff09\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\uff08     \uff09\u8272\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\u53d8\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7d2b\u8272\u53d8\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7d2b\u8272\u53d8\u9ed1\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\u8272\u53d8\u6a59\u8272\"}]","id":"511931040","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u72485\u5143\u5238\u5171\u8fd0\u7528\u4e86\uff08 \uff09\u79cd\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u548c\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30014\u548c6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\u548c6\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\u548c7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30016\u548c7\"}]","id":"511931041","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011999\u5e74\u7248\uff08      \uff09\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u53cc\u6c34\u5370","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u5143\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\u30015\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5143\u300150\u5143\"}]","id":"511931042","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u56de\u7b3c\u6b3e\u4e2d\u5939\u6742\u5047\u5e01\u7684,\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e88\u4ee5\uff08 \uff09\uff0c\u5411\u89e3\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u5f00\u5177\uff08 \uff09\uff0c\u5e76\u8981\u6c42\u5176\u8865\u8db3\u7b49\u989d\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56de\u7b3c\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6536\u7f34\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u540e\u6ca1\u6536\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6ca1\u6536\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6ca1\u6536\uff0c\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\"}]","id":"511931043","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u724850\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u5728\uff08\uff09\u8272\u81f3\uff08\uff09\u8272\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u3001\u84dd\"}]","id":"511931044","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdfE\u724810000\u65e5\u5143\uff0c\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u4eba\u50cf\u53f3\u4fa7\u53ef\u89c1\uff08\uff09\u6761\u7ad6\u6761\u578b\u6c34\u5370\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30014\"}]","id":"511931045","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u5728\u5956\u52b1\u8d39\u7528\u5ba1\u6279\u5b8c\u6210\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08  \uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\uff0c\u5c06\u5ba1\u6279\u7ed3\u679c\u53cd\u9988\u7533\u8bf7\u5956\u52b1\u5355\u4f4d\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300115\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130\"}]","id":"511931046","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6e2f\u5e01\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u6807\u51c6\u4ee3\u7801\u4e3a\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001CNY\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001EUR\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001HKD\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001JPY\"}]","id":"511931047","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u8425\u4e1a\u7f51\u70b9\u4e34\u67dc\u4eba\u5458\u76f4\u63a5\u529e\u7406\u7279\u6b8a\u6b8b\u7f3a\u3001\u6c61\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5151\u6362\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u5171\u5151\u63622005\u7248100\u5143\u5168\u989d\u4e00\u5f20\u3001\u534a\u989d\u4e00\u5f20\uff0c2005\u724850\u5143\u5168\u989d\u4e00\u5f20\u3001\u534a\u989d\u4e00\u5f20\uff0c\u7ecf\u590d\u6838\u3001\u4e1a\u52a1\u4e3b\u7ba1\u786e\u8ba4\u65e0\u8bef\u540e\uff0c\u5e94\u5982\u4f55\u4f7f\u7528\u4e13\u7528\u888b\u5bc6\u5c01\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5168\u90e8\u5c01\u88c5\u52301\u4e2a\u4e13\u7528\u888b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001100\u5143\u5c01\u88c5\u52301\u4e2a\u4e13\u7528\u888b\uff0c50\u5143\u5c01\u88c5\u52301\u4e2a\u4e13\u7528\u888b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5168\u989d\u5c01\u88c5\u52301\u4e2a\u4e13\u7528\u888b\uff0c\u534a\u989d\u5c01\u88c5\u52301\u4e2a\u4e13\u7528\u888b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c01\u88c5\u52304\u4e2a\u4e13\u7528\u888b\"}]","id":"511931048","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u654f\u611f\u4fe1\u606f\u5305\u62ec\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e00\u6b21\u6027\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff08\uff09\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u3001\u5047\u5916\u5e01\uff08\uff09\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c\u5bf9\u793e\u4f1a\u516c\u4f17\u4ed8\u51fa\u5047\u5e01\u6216\u53d1\u751f\u5047\u5e01\u6d41\u5931\u4e8b\u4ef6\uff0c\u5a92\u4f53\u53d1\u5e03\u7684\u6d89\u53ca\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u4fe1\u606f\u7b49\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\uff0c20\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\uff0c10\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\uff0c10\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\uff0c5\"}]","id":"511931049","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e8c\u4ee3\u8d27\u5e01\u53d1\u884c\u7ba1\u7406\u7cfb\u7edf\u53cd\u5047\u5b50\u7cfb\u7edf\u4ece\u4ec0\u4e48\u65f6\u5019\u8d77\u72ec\u7acb\u8fd0\u884c\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012019\u5e7410\u67081\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012019\u5e7412\u67081\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012020\u5e742\u67081\u65e5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012020\u5e745\u67081\u65e5\"}]","id":"511931050","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u65e5\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5171\u6709\u51e0\u79cd\u9762\u989d\uff0c\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012\u79cd\uff0c1000\u65e5\u5143\u548c10000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\u79cd\uff0c5000\u65e5\u5143\u548c10000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u79cd\uff0c1000\u65e5\u5143\u30012000\u65e5\u5143\u548c5000\u65e5\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30014\u79cd\uff0c1000\u65e5\u5143\u30012000\u65e5\u5143\u30015000\u65e5\u5143\u548c10000\u65e5\u5143\"}]","id":"511931051","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\u8981\u6c42\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u7528\u65e0\u62d2\u949e\u4ed3\u7684\u73b0\u91d1\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u8bef\u8bc6\u7387\u5e94\u5c0f\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\uff08\uff09%\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30010.01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30010.02\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30010.03\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30010.05\"}]","id":"511931052","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u5176\u5728\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u56fd\u5bb6\u6216\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u7f5a\u6b3e\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a1\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511931053","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u6bcf\u534a\u5e74\u5bf9\u5728\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u5904\u7406\u8bbe\u5907\u8fdb\u884c\u4e00\u6b21\u9274\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u62bd\u6837\u68c0\u6d4b\uff0c\u62bd\u68c0\u7387\u4e0d\u5f97\u4f4e\u4e8e\u73b0\u91d1\u5904\u7406\u673a\u5177\u603b\u91cf\u7684\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015%\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110%\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120%\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130%\"}]","id":"511931054","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u72485\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u7f29\u5fae\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001RMB\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u00a5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u2605\"}]","id":"511931055","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5c0f\u5f20\u662f\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u8425\u4e1a\u7f51\u70b9\u7684\u67dc\u5458\u3002\u4e00\u5929\uff0c\u5c0f\u5f20\u5728\u529e\u7406\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u7684\u5b58\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u53d1\u73b0\u5176\u4e2d\u4e00\u5f20\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7591\u4f3c\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u4e8e\u662f\uff0c\u5c0f\u5f20\u53eb\u6765\u8425\u4e1a\u7f51\u70b9\u53e6\u4e00\u540d\u67dc\u5458\uff0c\u5171\u540c\u5bf9\u8be5\u8d27\u5e01\u8fdb\u884c\u9274\u522b\u3002\u7ecf\u53cd\u590d\u9a8c\u770b\uff0c\u4ed6\u4eec\u8ba4\u5b9a\u8be5100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u4e8e\u662f\uff0c\u5c0f\u5f20\u544a\u8bc9\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u8fd9\u5f20\u94b1\u662f\u4e00\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e76\u5f53\u7740\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u7684\u9762\u52a0\u76d6\u4e86\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5370\u7ae0\u3002\u4f46\u662f\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u5fc3\u5b58\u7591\u8651\uff0c\u8981\u6c42\u5c0f\u5f20\u5c06\u8fd9\u5f20\u94b1\u518d\u7ed9\u56de\u81ea\u5df1\u597d\u597d\u770b\u770b\u3002\u5c0f\u5f20\u505a\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5c06\u8be5\u5047\u5e01\u4ece\u7a97\u53e3\u9012\u8fd8\u7ed9\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u8ba9\u5176\u4ed4\u7ec6\u67e5\u770b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c06\u8be5\u5047\u5e01\u5148\u7ed9\u5927\u5802\u7ecf\u7406\uff0c\u7531\u5927\u5802\u7ecf\u7406\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u4ea4\u7ed9\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u67e5\u770b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u9012\u7ed9\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\uff0c\u540c\u65f6\u5631\u5490\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u4e00\u5b9a\u8981\u8fd8\u56de\u6765\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9694\u7740\u67dc\u53f0\u7a97\u53e3\uff0c\u5c06\u8be5\u5047\u5e01\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u771f\u5e01\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u5730\u65b9\u4e00\u4e00\u6307\u7ed9\u9b4f\u5927\u7237\u770b\uff0c\u5e76\u544a\u8bc9\u4ed6\u82e5\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\u53ef\u7533\u8bf7\u9274\u5b9a\"}]","id":"511931056","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6848\u4ef6\u7c7b\u5047\u5e01\u5e94\u9009\u53d6\u6bcf\u4e2a\u5238\u522b\u4e0d\u540c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\uff08   \uff09\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\u8f6c\u5165\u5173\u6ce8\u7c7b","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130\"}]","id":"511931057","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7ecf\u7504\u522b\uff0c\u7ebf\u7d22\u5185\u5bb9\u6d89\u53ca\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u76f8\u5173\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u5728\u53d1\u73b0\u6216\u6536\u5230\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u7ebf\u7d22\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d77\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5b8c\u6210\u5ba1\u67e5","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30017\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300115\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300130\"}]","id":"511931058","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u5bf9\u5916\u8bef\u4ed8\u4e863\u5f20100\u5143\u9762\u989d\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ef\u5bf9\u8be5\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5904\u4ee5\uff08    \uff09\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a1\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\"}]","id":"511931059","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6d41\u901a\u949e\u6700\u65e9\u5f00\u59cb\u5e94\u7528\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012019\u5e74\u724850\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011999\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012015\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\"}]","id":"511931060","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e3b\u666f\u4eba\u50cf\u7684\u56fe\u7eb9\u7ebf\u6761\u7279\u5f81\u5177\u6709\uff08\uff09\u7684\u7279\u70b9\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u548c\u9ad8\u5ea6\u5747\u76f8\u7b49\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u4e0d\u540c\uff0c\u9ad8\u5ea6\u76f8\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u76f8\u540c\uff0c\u9ad8\u5ea6\u4e0d\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u4e0d\u540c\uff0c\u9ad8\u5ea6\u4e5f\u4e0d\u540c\"}]","id":"511931061","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2003\u7cfb\u5217\u6e2f\u5e01\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u52381000\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7684\u5f00\u7a97\u90e8\u4f4d\u5370\u6709\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\uff08\u00a0\u00a0\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001HK1000\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001HK1000\u548c\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\u00a0\"}]","id":"511931062","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e13\u7528\u7ae0\u4e3a\u5706\u5f62\uff0c\u5176\u76f4\u5f84\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u5398\u7c73\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013.5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013.8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30014.8\"}]","id":"511931063","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u724810\u3001 20\u6b27\u5143\u589e\u52a0\u7684\u91cd\u8981\u89c6\u89c9\u7279\u5f81\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8096\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\u3001\u8096\u50cf\u5168\u606f\u6761\u548c\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u6570\u5b57\u548c\u8096\u50cf\u5168\u606f\u6761\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8096\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\u3001\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u548c\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u6570\u5b57\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\u548c\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931064","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7ea2\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u7b2c1\u7248\u548c\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u53ef\u89c1\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u4e0a\u534a\u90e8\u6d88\u5931\uff0c\u4e0b\u534a\u90e8\u53ef\u89c1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u53f3\u534a\u90e8\u6d88\u5931\uff0c\u5de6\u534a\u90e8\u53ef\u89c1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u5de6\u534a\u90e8\u6d88\u5931\uff0c\u53f3\u534a\u90e8\u53ef\u89c1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u4e0b\u534a\u90e8\u6d88\u5931\uff0c\u4e0a\u534a\u90e8\u53ef\u89c1\"}]","id":"511931065","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u7b2c\u4e00\u5957\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u897f\u85cf\u81ea\u6cbb\u533a\u6210\u7acb20\u5468\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u65b0\u7586\u7ef4\u543e\u5c14\u81ea\u6cbb\u533a\u6210\u7acb30\u5468\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u6210\u7acb35\u5468\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6210\u7acb40\u5468\u5e74\"}]","id":"511931066","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u7684\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u4e2d\u53ea\u6709\u54ea\u79cd\u9762\u989d\u7684\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u542b\u6709\u767d\u6c34\u5370\uff1f","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511931067","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u6c34\u5370\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u548c\u50cf\u7d20\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u884c\u6807\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3001\u50cf\u7d20\u6c34\u5370\u548c\u72ee\u5934\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u548c\u50cf\u7d20\u6c34\u5370\"}]","id":"511931068","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7528\u65e0\u62d2\u949e\u4ed3\u7684\u7eb8\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\uff0c\u8bef\u8bc6\u7387\u5c0f\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\uff08    \uff09\u7b26\u5408\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u8981\u6c42\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30010.01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30010.02\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30010.03\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30010.05\"}]","id":"511931069","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u6700\u9ad8\u4eba\u6c11\u68c0\u5bdf\u9662 \u516c\u5b89\u90e8\u5173\u4e8e\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u7ba1\u8f96\u7684\u5211\u4e8b\u6848\u4ef6\u89c4\u5b9a\uff08\u4e8c\uff09\u300b\uff0c\u8d70\u79c1\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\uff0c\u603b\u9762\u989d\u57282000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e0d\u6ee12\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u5e01\u91cf\u5728200\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e0d\u6ee12000\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u7684\uff0c\u5904\uff08    \uff09\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30013\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a7\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a10\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a\"}]","id":"511931070","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5728\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u53f3\u4fa7\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u5f02\u578b\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511931071","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u6807\u51c6\u4ee3\u7801\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001USD\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001USA\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001$\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001DOLLAR\"}]","id":"511931072","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01 \u7eb8\u5e01\u300b\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c100\u5143\u7684\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u82e5\uff08    \uff090.23\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5927\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c0f\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5927\u4e8e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c0f\u4e8e\"}]","id":"511931073","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"100\u7f8e\u5143\u4ece\u54ea\u4e00\u7248\u5f00\u59cb\u91c7\u7528\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u5176\u989c\u8272\u53d8\u5316\u4e3a\uff1f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011990\u7248\uff0c\u91d1\u53d8\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011996\u7248\uff0c\u7eff\u53d8\u9ed1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012004\u7248\uff0c\u7eff\u53d8\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012006\u7248\uff0c\u53e4\u94dc\u53d8\u7eff\"}]","id":"511931074","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u786e\u8ba4\u8bef\u6536\u6216\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u89e3\u7f34\u81f3\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511931075","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7968\u9762\u5171\u6709\uff08\uff09\u4e2a\u51f9\u5370\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff08\u963f\u62c9\u4f2f\u6570\u5b57\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30013\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30014\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30016\"}]","id":"511931076","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e0150\u300120\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7684\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u5448\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u8272\u8367\u5149\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"D","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6a59\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\"}]","id":"511931077","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2017\u5e746\u670819\u65e5\uff0c\u8b66\u65b9\u63a5\u4e3e\u62a5\u540e\u6363\u6bc1\u4e00\u5904\u5047\u5e01\u518d\u52a0\u5de5\u7a9d\u70b9\uff0c\u6293\u83b7\u4e3b\u8981\u6d89\u6848\u4eba\u5458\u5f20\u67d0\u67d0\u7b492\u4eba\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u5f20\u67d0\u67d0\u4f4f\u5904\u67e5\u83b7\u5927\u91cf\u5047\u5e01\u5171840\u5f20\uff0c\u9762\u989d\u5171\u8ba115000\u5143\uff08\u5176\u4e2d\u6210\u54c1\u5047\u5e01\u5171\u8ba1240\u5f20\uff0c\u9762\u989d\u5171\u8ba15000\u5143\uff0c\u534a\u6210\u54c1\u5047\u5e01\u5171\u8ba1600\u5f20\uff0c\u9762\u989d\u5171\u8ba110000\u5143\uff09\uff0c\u540c\u65f6\u5728\u73b0\u573a\u8fd8\u67e5\u83b7\u5047\u5e01\u518d\u52a0\u5de5\u6240\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u5370\u5237\u8bbe\u5907\u3001\u6a21\u5177\u3001\u88c1\u526a\u5de5\u5177\u82e5\u5e72\u3002\u7ecf\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u9274\u5b9a\uff0c\u67e5\u83b7\u7684840\u5f20\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u4e3a\u4f2a\u9020\u5e01\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001A.\u67e5\u83b7\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u534a\u6210\u54c1\u6309\u5176\u9762\u989d\u7684\u4e00\u534a\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u67e5\u83b7\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u534a\u6210\u54c1\u6309\u5176\u9762\u989d\u7684\u5168\u989d\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6848\u4ef6\u5ba1\u7ed3\u540e\uff0c\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8ba1\u7b97\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u989d\u5e94\u4e3a1500\u5143\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6848\u4ef6\u5ba1\u7ed3\u540e\uff0c\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8ba1\u7b97\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u989d\u5e94\u4e3a51500\u5143\u3002\"}]","id":"511931078","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u622a\u6b622020\u5e74\u672b\uff0c\u5df2\u53d1\u884c\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u548c\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u6ca1\u6709\u7684\u9762\u989d\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"1","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"C","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011\u89d2\"}]","id":"511931079","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u6307\u51fa\uff0c\u73b0\u91d1\u5904\u7406\u673a\u5177\u4e3b\u8981\u6307\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u3001\u7b26\u5408\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u9700\u8981\u7684 \uff08\uff09\u7b49\u8bbe\u5907\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u70b9\u9a8c\u949e\u673a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6e05\u5206\u673a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u73b0\u91d1\u5904\u7406\u81ea\u52a9\u8bbe\u5907\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6346\u949e\u673a\"}]","id":"511931080","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u53d8\u5316\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u76f4\u5f84\u51cf\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u589e\u52a0\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9020\u578b\u8c03\u6574\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u82b1\u5349\u7f29\u5c0f\"}]","id":"511931081","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff0c\u5b83\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u7279\u70b9\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\uff1b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u5177\u6709\u95f4\u65ad\u6548\u679c\u7684\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff1b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6574\u4e2a\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5747\u5177\u6709\u78c1\u6027\uff1b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53ef\u4f9b\u8bbe\u5907\u8bfb\u53d6\u4ee5\u5224\u5b9a\u8be5\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u771f\u4f2a\u3002\"}]","id":"511931082","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u7684\u8c03\u8fd0\uff0c\u53ef\u91c7\u7528\uff08\uff09\u7684\u65b9\u5f0f\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u62bc\u8fd0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011\u4eba\u4e13\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u673a\u8981\u5bc4\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5feb\u9012\u90ae\u5bc4\"}]","id":"511931083","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u8be5\u8425\u4e1a\u7f51\u70b9\u914d\u5907\u4e0b\u5217\u8d44\u6599\u548c\u8bbe\u5907\uff1a","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\u6295\u8bc9\u7535\u8bdd\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6295\u8bc9\u7535\u8bdd\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7b26\u5408\u8d28\u91cf\u6807\u51c6\u7684\u70b9\u9a8c\u949e\u673a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5ba3\u4f20\u8d44\u6599\"}]","id":"511931084","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\uff0c\uff08   \uff09\u7968\u9762\u5177\u6709\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300150\u6b27\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001100\u6b27\u5143\"}]","id":"511931085","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u5c5e\u4e8e\u5851\u6599\u949e\u7968\u7684\u6709\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012016\u5e74\u72485\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012007\u5e74\u724810\u5143\u6e2f\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012000\u5e74\u8fce\u63a5\u65b0\u4e16\u7eaa\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5f69\u724810\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511931086","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f69\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u81ea\u7531\u6807\u8bc6\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u91d1\u5c5e\u6cb9\u58a8\u7684\u662f\uff08     \uff09\u7f8e\u5143","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\"}]","id":"511931087","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5916\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u548c\u5404\u79cd\u786c\u5e01\uff0c\u7ecf\u9274\u5b9a\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u8be5\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u4ea4\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u4f9d\u6cd5\u6536\u7f34\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u4e88\u4ee5\u6ca1\u6536\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5411\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u51fa\u5177\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5411\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u51fa\u5177\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\"}]","id":"511931088","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7684\u54ea\u4e9b\u4f4d\u7f6e\u5177\u6709\u8367\u5149\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002\uff08   \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5e74\u7248\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u884c\u540d\u6587\u5b57\"}]","id":"511931089","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2019\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\uff08\uff09\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\u589e\u52a0\u88c5\u9970\u7eb9\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u589e\u52a0\u5168\u57cb\u78c1\u6027\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\u589e\u52a0\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\u589e\u52a0\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931090","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u7684\u5149\u8272\u63a5\u7ebf\u8367\u5149\u5f02\u5f62\u53f7\u7801\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\uff08   \uff09\u8272\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ec4\"}]","id":"511931091","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u522b\u6280\u672f\u7684\u5206\u7c7b\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e13\u5bb6\u9632\u4f2a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u592e\u884c\u9632\u4f2a\"}]","id":"511931092","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51fa\u4e8e\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5ba3\u4f20\u76ee\u7684\uff0c\uff08\uff09\u53ef\u4ee5\u4e0d\u7ecf\u5ba1\u6279\u76f4\u63a5\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u4f46\u5fc5\u987b\u9075\u5b88\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u7b2c\u4e5d\u6761\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5e76\u968f\u65f6\u63a5\u53d7\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7684\u76d1\u7763\u68c0\u67e5\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8bc1\u5238\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4fdd\u9669\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5370\u5236\u4f01\u4e1a\"}]","id":"511931093","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\uff08    \uff09\u5238\u522b\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u51f9\u5370\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011999\u5e74\u72485\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011999\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012005\u5e74\u724820\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012019\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\"}]","id":"511931094","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u53ef\u4ee5\u4e00\u5f0f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e00\u4efd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e24\u4efd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e09\u4efd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u56db\u4efd\"}]","id":"511931095","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\u8c03\u67e5\u53d6\u8bc1\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\uff0c\u53ef\u91c7\u53d6\u4e0b\u5217\u63aa\u65bd\uff1a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8d70\u8bbf\u3001\u8be2\u95ee\u6709\u5173\u4eba\u5458\uff0c\u4e86\u89e3\u76f8\u5173\u60c5\u51b5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8fdb\u5165\u73b0\u573a\u8fdb\u884c\u52d8\u9a8c\u3001\u68c0\u67e5\u3001\u6444\u50cf\u3001\u7167\u76f8\u7b49\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u67e5\u9605\u6216\u8005\u590d\u5236\u6709\u5173\u6750\u6599\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5411\u6709\u5173\u5355\u4f4d\u4e86\u89e3\u6838\u5b9e\u60c5\u51b5\"}]","id":"511931096","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5c5e\u4e8e2019\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931097","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u4e2d\uff0c\u6309\u5904\u7f6e\u65b9\u5f0f\u7684\u4e0d\u540c\uff0c\u5c06\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5206\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u666e\u901a\u7c7b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5173\u6ce8\u7c7b\"}]","id":"511931098","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u9762\u5355\u4e2a\u8936\u76b1\u957f\u5ea6\u5927\u4e8e10mm\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u70ad\u5316\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u70ad\u5316\u9762\u79ef\u5c0f\u4e8e18mm\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e00\u5904\u6d82\u5199\u4e14\u9762\u79ef\u4e3a180\u5e73\u65b9\u6beb\u7c73\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e00\u5904\u6495\u88c2\u4e14\u957f\u5ea6\u5927\u4e8e10mm\"}]","id":"511931099","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u987b\u5728\u56fe\u6837\uff08\uff09\u660e\u663e\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6807\u6ce8\u6e05\u6670\u53ef\u8fa8\u7684\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u957f\u5ea6\u548c\u5bbd\u5ea6\u5206\u522b\u4e0d\u4f4e\u4e8e\u56fe\u6837\u957f\u5ea6\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u7684\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e0a\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e8c\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e09\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\"}]","id":"511931100","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e8c\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7684\u5168\u606f\u56fe\u542b\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b27\u7f57\u5df4\u5973\u795e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b27\u5143\u6807\u5fd7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u56fe\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511931101","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u968f\u7740\u79fb\u52a8\u4e92\u8054\u4fe1\u606f\u6280\u672f\u7684\u666e\u53ca\u53d1\u5c55\uff0c\u5bf9\u4e8e\u7535\u5546\u5e73\u53f0\u3001\u65e0\u4eba\u9500\u552e\u3001\u81ea\u52a9\u670d\u52a1\u3001\u7f51\u7edc\u653f\u52a1\u7b49\u573a\u666f\uff0c\u4ee5\u7f51\u7edc\u5316\u3001\u65e0\u4eba\u5316\u65b9\u5f0f\u63d0\u4f9b\u5546\u54c1\u548c\u670d\u52a1\u3001\u5c65\u884c\u6cd5\u5b9a\u804c\u8d23\uff0c\u4e5f\u4e0d\u5177\u5907\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u53d6\u6761\u4ef6\uff0c\u4e14\u53c2\u4e0e\u5404\u65b9\u5728\uff08\uff09\u7684\u539f\u5219\u4e0a\u8fbe\u6210\u4e00\u81f4\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u4f7f\u7528\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u5de5\u5177\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u81ea\u613f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5e73\u7b49\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u516c\u5e73\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5ba2\u89c2\"}]","id":"511931102","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u662f\u6307\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\uff08 \uff09\u5047\u5e01\u7b49\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u5904\u7406\u8fc7\u7a0b\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u63a5\u6536\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6ca1\u6536\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4fdd\u7ba1\u3001\u8c03\u8fd0\"}]","id":"511931103","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\uff08  \uff09\u884c\u4e3a\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5728\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u672a\u6309\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u5bf9\u529e\u7406\u8d27\u5e01\u6536\u4ed8\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u6c34\u5e73\u8fdb\u884c\u8bc4\u4f30\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u529e\u7406\u6e05\u5206\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u4e0d\u5177\u5907\u5224\u65ad\u548c\u6311\u5254\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e13\u4e1a\u80fd\u529b\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u672a\u6309\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u5efa\u7acb\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u5185\u90e8\u7ba1\u7406\u5236\u5ea6\u548c\u64cd\u4f5c\u89c4\u8303\u7684\"}]","id":"511931104","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff08\uff09\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u663e\u73b0\u7eff\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5143\"}]","id":"511931105","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"20\u82f1\u9551\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u7a7a\u767d\u5904\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u89c1\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5973\u738b\u5934\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e9a\u5f53\u65af\u5bc6\u5934\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\uffe120\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300120\"}]","id":"511931106","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u76f8\u5bf9\u4e8e\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\uff0c\u73b0\u91d1\u5728\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u65b9\u9762\u5177\u5907\u4e0d\u53ef\u66ff\u4ee3\u7684\u4f18\u52bf\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4fdd\u969c\u516c\u4f17\u652f\u4ed8\u6743\u5229\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5e73\u8861\u533a\u57df\u7ecf\u6d4e\u53d1\u5c55\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4fc3\u8fdb\u6587\u5316\u4f20\u64ad\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4fdd\u969c\u6c11\u751f\u798f\u7949\"}]","id":"511931107","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fa\u5b9a\u82b1\u5349\u6c34\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7261\u4e39\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8377\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6708\u5b63\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6c34\u4ed9\u82b1\"}]","id":"511931108","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u54ea\u4e9b\u5238\u522b\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u767d\u6c34\u5370\u6280\u672f?\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011\u5143\"}]","id":"511931109","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff0c\uff08  \uff09\u5904\u4ee5\u5341\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u3001\u65e0\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u4e94\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e94\u5341\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u91d1\u6216\u8005\u6ca1\u6536\u8d22\u4ea7\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u96c6\u56e2\u7684\u9996\u8981\u5206\u5b50\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u6570\u989d\u7279\u522b\u5de8\u5927\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u5e76\u8fd0\u8f93\u8d29\u5356\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6709\u5176\u4ed6\u7279\u522b\u4e25\u91cd\u60c5\u8282\u7684\"}]","id":"511931110","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2018\u5e7410\u6708\uff0c\u6d59\u6c5f\u7701\u8b66\u65b9\u6210\u529f\u6363\u6bc1\u4e00\u5904\u4f2a\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5370\u5236\u7a9d\u70b9\u3002\u72af\u7f6a\u5acc\u7591\u4eba\u9a6c\u67d0\u4f19\u540c\u4ed6\u4eba\u79df\u8d41\u6c11\u623f\u6210\u7acb\u5236\u5047\u573a\u6240\u5370\u5237\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u6848\u53d1\u65f6\uff0c\u8b66\u65b9\u73b0\u573a\u6293\u83b7\u9a6c\u67d0\u7b49\u4e3b\u8981\u6d89\u6848\u4eba\u5458\uff0c\u67e5\u83b7\u9a6c\u67d0\u7b49\u4eba\u5370\u5236\u7684\u9762\u989d100\u5143\u6210\u54c1\u5047\u5e018\u4e07\u5f20\u3001\u534a\u6210\u54c1\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e014\u4e07\u5f20\uff0c\u5408\u8ba1\u91d1\u989d1200\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u540c\u65f6\u67e5\u83b7\u5370\u5237\u5047\u5e01\u8bbe\u5907\u4e00\u6279\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6839\u636e\u300a\u5211\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4e0a\u8ff0\u60c5\u5f62\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u6570\u989d\u7279\u522b\u5de8\u5927\uff0c\u5e94\u590410\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u6216\u65e0\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u67e5\u83b7\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u534a\u6210\u54c1\u6309\u5176\u9762\u989d\u7684\u4e00\u534a\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u672c\u6848\u4ef6\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u989d\u5e94\u4e3a20\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u672c\u6848\u4ef6\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u91d1\u989d\u5e94\u4e3a25\u4e07\u5143\u3002\"}]","id":"511931111","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u548c1\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u82b1\u5349\u6c34\u5370\u6548\u679c\u660e\u663e\u63d0\u5347\uff0c\u8fd9\u4e09\u79cd\u82b1\u5349\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6708\u5b63\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u83ca\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8377\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5170\u82b1\"}]","id":"511931112","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\uff08  \uff09\u884c\u4e3a\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u7b2c\u56db\u5341\u56db\u6761\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5728\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u56fd\u5bb6\u548c\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d1\u751f\u5047\u5e01\u8bef\u6536\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u672a\u5bf9\u5ba2\u6237\u7b49\u503c\u8d54\u4ed8\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u5bf9\u8d1f\u9762\u8206\u60c5\u5904\u7f6e\u4e0d\u529b\u9020\u6210\u4e0d\u826f\u5f71\u54cd\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u65e0\u6545\u62d2\u7edd\u53d7\u7406\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u6216\u8005\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u63d0\u51fa\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\u3002\"}]","id":"511931113","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5468\u67d0\u4ece\u5f20\u67d0\u5904\u8d2d\u4e70\u4e865000\u5143\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u5728\u6293\u83b7\u524d\u5728\u8d85\u5e02\u3001\u5546\u573a\u7b49\u5730\u4f7f\u7528\u4e862500\u5143\uff0c\u5468\u67d0\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u4ee5\uff08    \uff09\u5b9a\u7f6a\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ece\u91cd\u5904\u7f5a\"}]","id":"511931114","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u8089\u773c\u53ef\u89c1\u7684\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u73e0\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\u6761\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u5168\u606f\u6807\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511931115","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u5904\u7f6e\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u9075\u5faa\u201c\uff08\uff09\u201d \u539f\u5219\uff0c \u4ee5\u4e8b\u5b9e\u4e3a\u4f9d\u636e\uff0c \u4ee5\u6cd5\u5f8b\u4e3a\u51c6\u7ef3\uff0c\u575a\u6301\u5904\u7f5a\u4e0e\u6559\u80b2\u76f8\u7ed3\u5408\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f9d\u6cd5\u5408\u89c4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c5e\u5730\u7ba1\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5782\u76f4\u76d1\u7ba1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u516c\u6b63\u5ba2\u89c2\"}]","id":"511931116","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f90\u5148\u751f\u4e8e7\u67088\u65e5\u5728\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u81ea\u52a9\u67dc\u5458\u673a\u4e0a\u53d6\u6b3e1000\u5143\u3002\u4e00\u5468\u540e\uff0c\u5f90\u5148\u751f\u5728\u8d85\u5e02\u4f7f\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u4ed8\u6b3e\u65f6\u53d1\u73b0\u6709\u4e00\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5f90\u5148\u751f\u5982\u679c\u8981\u7533\u8bf7\u8fdb\u884c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\uff0c\u4ed6\u5e94\u8be5\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8054\u7cfb\u8be5\u81ea\u52a9\u8bbe\u5907\u6240\u5c5e\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u63d0\u4f9b\u8d85\u5e02\u5f55\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u643a\u5e26\u6709\u6548\u8bc1\u4ef6\u3001\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\u7eb8\u5e01\u3001\u529e\u7406\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u8bc1\u660e\u8d44\u6599\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u63d0\u4ea4\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\"}]","id":"511931117","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u63a5\u53d7\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u4e25\u683c\u533a\u5206\uff08\uff09\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d8\u9020\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6848\u4ef6\u67e5\u83b7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u975e\u6848\u4ef6\u67e5\u83b7\"}]","id":"511931118","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u53d8\u5316\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6750\u8d28\u8c03\u6574\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9020\u578b\u8c03\u6574\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u82b1\u5349\u7f29\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u589e\u52a0\u5706\u70b9\"}]","id":"511931119","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u662f\u6307\u901a\u8fc7\u5404\u79cd\u5f62\u5f0f\u5728\u5ba3\u4f20\u54c1\u3001\u51fa\u7248\u7269\u6216\u8005\u5176\u4ed6\u5546\u54c1\u4e0a\u4f7f\u7528\uff08\uff09\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u653e\u5927\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d8\u5f62\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7f29\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u540c\u6837\u5927\u5c0f\"}]","id":"511931120","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5173\u4e8e2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5e94\u7528\u7684\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u4e2d\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e2d\u9542\u7a7a\u7684\uffe5100\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5448\u9ec4\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5177\u6709\u78c1\u6027\uff0c\u53ef\u4f9b\u673a\u8bfb\"}]","id":"511931121","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\uff08  \uff09\u6c34\u5370\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u95e8\u7a97\u56fe\u6848\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u673a\u8bfb\u6c34\u5370\"}]","id":"511931122","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u770b\u5230\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\u6709\u660e\u4eae\u7684\uff08   \uff09\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511931123","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u67dc\u9762\u529e\u7406\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u5bf9\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5f53\u9762\u4ee5\u7edf\u4e00\u683c\u5f0f\u7684\u4e13\u7528\u888b\u52a0\u5c01\uff0c\u5c01\u53e3\u5904\u52a0\u76d6\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u6233\u8bb0","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5916\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5916\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\"}]","id":"511931124","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1990\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u589e\u52a0\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\"}]","id":"511931125","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u53ef\u501f\u52a9\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u4eea\u5668\u8bbe\u5907\u8fdb\u884c\u68c0\u6d4b\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u6e90\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u65e5\u5149\u706f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u68c0\u6d4b\u4eea\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u5916\u68c0\u6d4b\u4eea\"}]","id":"511931126","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e9b\uff08\uff09\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u7acb\u5373\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u62a5\u544a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e00\u6b21\u6027\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e013\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\u548c\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u548c\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u53d1\u6587\u53e6\u6709\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u4e24\u8005\u8f83\u5c0f\u8005\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5229\u7528\u65b0\u7684\u9020\u5047\u624b\u6bb5\u5236\u9020\u5047\u5e01\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u83b7\u5f97\u5236\u9020\u3001\u8d29\u5356\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u3001\u6301\u6709\u6216\u8005\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7ebf\u7d22\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u4e0d\u914d\u5408\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u6536\u7f34\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\"}]","id":"511931127","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u5238\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\u5238\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u5238\u5177\u6709\u8367\u5149\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u90e8\u4f4d\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u673a\u8bfb\u6761\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a2a\u8fde\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ad6\u8fde\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e92\u8865\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931128","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\u662f\u6307\u5728\u771f\u5e01\u7684\u57fa\u7840\u4e0a\uff0c\u5229\u7528\uff08\uff09\u3001\u91cd\u5370\u7b49\u591a\u79cd\u65b9\u6cd5\u5236\u4f5c\uff0c\u6539\u53d8\u771f\u5e01\u539f\u5f62\u6001\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6316\u8865\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u63ed\u5c42\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u62fc\u51d1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u79fb\u4f4d\"}]","id":"511931129","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u53d8\u5316\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6750\u8d28\u8c03\u6574\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9020\u578b\u8c03\u6574\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u82b1\u5349\u7f29\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u5185\u5468\u7f18\u8c03\u6574\u4e3a\u591a\u8fb9\u5f62\"}]","id":"511931130","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5404\u5238\u522b\u7eb8\u5e01\uff0c\u5728\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u8bbe\u7f6e\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7684\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5143\"}]","id":"511931131","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u53d6\u6d88\u4e86\uff08  \uff09\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5168\u57cb\u5f0f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511931132","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5047\u949e\u4e2d\u5370\u5237\u7684\u5047\u6c34\u5370\u901a\u5e38\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u6cb9\u58a8\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u65e0\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7070\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6de1\u9ec4\u8272\"}]","id":"511931133","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u4e86\u822a\u5929\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u56fe\u6848\u6709\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e1c\u65b9\u7ea2\u4e00\u53f7\u536b\u661f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u795e\u5dde\u4e94\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5ae6\u5a25\u4e00\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u63a2\u6708\u6708\u7403\u8f66\"}]","id":"511931134","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u51e0\u4e2a\u573a\u666f\u88ab\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u5c40\u8ba4\u5b9a\u4e3a\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u7684\u91cd\u70b9\u573a\u666f\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6709\u6536\u8d39\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u653f\u5e9c\u90e8\u95e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u65c5\u6e38\u666f\u70b9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u516c\u5171\u4ea4\u901a\u573a\u6240\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u96f6\u552e\u673a\u6784\"}]","id":"511931135","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0a\u4e0b\u6643\u52a8\u65b0\u724850\u82f1\u9551\u65f6\uff0c\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e0a\u7684\u56fe\u6848\u53d8\u5316\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5de6\u53f3\u53d8\u5316\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e0a\u4e0b\u53d8\u5316\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e0e\u5973\u738b\u8096\u50cf\u4ea4\u66ff\u51fa\u73b0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\u4e0e\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4ea4\u66ff\u51fa\u73b0\"}]","id":"511931136","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u51f9\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u4f4d\u7f6e\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0a\u89d2\"}]","id":"511931137","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f53100\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u5927\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e0.23\u65f6\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5f5350\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u5c0f\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e0.24\u65f6\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u9002\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5f5320\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u5927\u4e8e\u7b49\u4e8e0.23\u65f6\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5f5310\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u5c0f\u4e8e0.23\u65f6\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u9002\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"}]","id":"511931138","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u51e0\u4e2a\u673a\u6784\u4e0d\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u798f\u5dde\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u676d\u5dde\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u9752\u5c9b\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53a6\u95e8\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"}]","id":"511931139","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\u4e00\u822c\u7528\u624b\u5de5\u5236\u4f5c\uff0c\u4ee5\u7f8e\u5143\u81ea\u8eab\u4e3a\u5bf9\u8c61\u5927\u591a\u662f\u6d82\u6539\u54ea\u4e9b\u90e8\u4f4d\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5370\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5e74\u7248\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9762\u989d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u949e\u7968\u540d\u79f0\"}]","id":"511931140","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u59572005\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u591a\u5c42\u6b21\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u7248\u5370\u5237\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511931141","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u786c\u5e01\u751f\u4ea7\u5de5\u827a\u4e3b\u8981\u6709\u54ea\u51e0\u4e2a\u8fc7\u7a0b\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u677f\u6750\u8f67\u5236\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u576f\u997c\u5236\u4f5c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u538b\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u629b\u5149\"}]","id":"511931142","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2007\u7248\u6e2f\u5e0110\u5143\u80cc\u9762\u7684\u53cd\u5149\u8272\u5e26\uff0c\u659c\u770b\u65f6\u80fd\u770b\u5230\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9a8f\u9a6c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001HK10\"}]","id":"511931143","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u4fe1\u606f\u7cfb\u7edf\u5e94\u5b9e\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u548c\uff08\uff09\u4e24\u79cd\u67e5\u8be2\u65b9\u6cd5\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7cbe\u786e\u67e5\u8be2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a21\u7cca\u67e5\u8be2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b63\u5411\u67e5\u8be2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cd\u5411\u67e5\u8be2\"}]","id":"511931144","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u90e8\u5206\u6216\u5168\u90e8\u892a\u8272\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff1a(    )","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e00\u5904\u8131\u58a8\uff0c\u8131\u58a8\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e100mm2\u7684\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u591a\u5904\u8131\u58a8\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u8131\u58a8\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e60mm2\u7684\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u591a\u5904\u8131\u58a8\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u8131\u58a8\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e80mm2\u7684\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u8131\u58a8\u9762\u79ef\u867d\u672a\u8d85\u8fc7\u4ee5\u4e0a\u6807\u51c6\uff0c\u4f46\u91cd\u8981\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e4b\u4e00\u8131\u58a8\u4e25\u91cd\uff0c\u5f71\u54cd\u9632\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u7684\u3002\"}]","id":"511931145","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u91d1\u878d\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a,\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3b\u8981\u5305\u62ec\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5916\u89c2\u3001\u8d28\u5730\u3001\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u53d7\u635f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d8\u8272\u53d8\u5f62\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56fe\u6848\u6a21\u7cca\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c3a\u5bf8\u3001\u91cd\u91cf\u53d1\u751f\u53d8\u5316\"}]","id":"511931146","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u5f20\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5f00\u7a97\u5728\u6b63\u9762\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53d1\u884c70\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u822a\u5929\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7b2c29\u5c4a\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514b\u8fd0\u52a8\u4f1a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5e86\u795d\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u6210\u7acb\u4e94\u5341\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\"}]","id":"511931147","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9648\u5c0f\u59d0\u63a5\u5230\u67d0\u5546\u4e1a\u94f6\u884c\u7684\u7535\u8bdd\u901a\u77e5\uff1a\u544a\u77e5\u9648\u5c0f\u59d0\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u5df2\u7ecf\u6709\u7ed3\u679c\u4e86\u3002\u7ecf\u6838\u67e5\uff0c\u6ca1\u6709\u53d1\u73b0\u738b\u5148\u751f\u8981\u6c42\u67e5\u8be2\u7684\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u56e0\u6b64\u8fd9\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\u4e0d\u662f\u8be5\u5546\u4e1a\u94f6\u884c\u4ed8\u51fa\u7684\uff0c\u9648\u5c0f\u59d0\u4e0d\u8981\u518d\u6765\u94f6\u884c\u4e86\u3002\u5bf9\u4e8e\u8be5\u5546\u4e1a\u94f6\u884c\u7684\u505a\u6cd5\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u4e2d\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5e94\u901a\u8fc7\u73b0\u573a\u6216\u90ae\u5bc4\u7684\u65b9\u5f0f\u5c06\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u901a\u77e5\u4e66\u300b\u9001\u8fbe\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u7684\u505a\u6cd5\u662f\u6b63\u786e\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5e94\u5c06\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u901a\u8fc7\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u544a\u77e5\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5e94\u544a\u77e5\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\u53ef\u57283\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u6709\u5173\u673a\u6784\u7533\u8bf7\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\"}]","id":"511931148","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\uff08    \uff09\u9762\u989d\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u91d1\u5c5e\u6cb9\u58a8\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\u5143\"}]","id":"511931149","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53d1\u884c70\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u4e2d\u52a8\u611f\u5149\u53d8\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5f00\u521b\u5904\u53ef\u89c1\uff08   \uff09\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300170\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u201c\u53e4\u94b1\u5e01\u201d\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300150\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u201c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u201d\u5b57\u6837\"}]","id":"511931150","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ece\u7968\u5e45\u770b\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5404\u5238\u522b\u7684\u7968\u5e45\u5bbd\u5ea6\u6709\uff08\uff09\u6beb\u7c73\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300156\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300163\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300170\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300177\"}]","id":"511931151","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u662f\u6307\uff08\uff09.","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5916\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u786c\u5e01\"}]","id":"511931152","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\u4e2d\u62df\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u4ea7\u54c1\u7c7b\u522b\u53ef\u4ee5\u5206\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u5238\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5ba3\u4f20\u54c1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51fa\u7248\u7269\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5546\u54c1\"}]","id":"511931153","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\uff0c\u54ea\u4e9b\u9762\u989d\u80cc\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u7ea2\u5916\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011\u5143\"}]","id":"511931154","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u724820\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\uff08   \uff09\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u5f02\u5f62\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511931155","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u4e0a\u54ea\u4e9b\u4f4d\u7f6e\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u5370\uff08 \uff09\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u56fd\u5fbd\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u56e2\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u80cc\u9762\u884c\u957f\u5370\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\u884c\u540d\u62fc\u97f3\"}]","id":"511931156","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u76f8\u6bd4\u4e8e\u539f\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c2019\u5e74\u9881\u5e03\u7684\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6709\u54ea\u4e9b\u6539\u8fdb\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d6\u6d88\u521d\u5ba1\u73af\u8282\uff0c\u63d0\u9ad8\u4e86\u5ba1\u6279\u6548\u7387\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c06\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7eb3\u5165\u7ba1\u7406\uff0c\u6269\u5927\u4e86\u7ba1\u7406\u534a\u5f84\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u63d0\u51fa\u7981\u6b62\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u3001\u53ef\u4e0d\u7ecf\u8bb8\u53ef\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u60c5\u5f62\uff0c\u7ec6\u5316\u4e86\u4f7f\u7528\u89c4\u5219\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u660e\u786e\u68c0\u67e5\u6743\u548c\u5904\u7f5a\u6743\uff0c\u8fdb\u4e00\u6b65\u52a0\u5f3a\u4e86\u4e8b\u4e2d\u4e8b\u540e\u7ba1\u7406\u3002\"}]","id":"511931157","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u8c03\u8fd0\u53ef\u91c7\u53d6\u54ea\u4e9b\u65b9\u5f0f\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u62bc\u8fd0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53cc\u4eba\u4e13\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e13\u8f66\u4e13\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u673a\u8981\u5bc4\u9001\"}]","id":"511931158","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u65e5\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6709\uff08   \uff09\u79cd\u9762\u989d\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011000\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012000\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30015000\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110000\u5143\"}]","id":"511931159","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u6c34\u5370\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u72ee\u5934\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u50cf\u7d20\u6c34\u5370\"}]","id":"511931160","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8f9b\u4ea5\u9769\u547d90\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u4e3a\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300190\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8f9b\u4ea5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9769\u547d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511931161","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u6574\u6cbb\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u5178\u578b\u6848\u4f8b\u7f16\u5199\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\uff0c\u5178\u578b\u6848\u4f8b\u91c7\u96c6\u4e3b\u8981\u9075\u5faa\u5982\u4e0b\u539f\u5219\uff1a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u771f\u5b9e\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6743\u5a01\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5b8c\u6574\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5178\u578b\u6027\"}]","id":"511931162","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6211\u56fd\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u4e3b\u8981\u5305\u62ec\uff1a\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53cc\u91d1\u5c5e\u786c\u5e01\u6280\u672f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\u590d\u5408\u9020\u5e01\u6750\u6599\u6280\u672f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6848\u96d5\u523b\u6280\u672f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7f29\u5fae\u56fe\u7eb9\u6280\u672f\"}]","id":"511931163","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5305\u542b\u9762\u989d\u4fe1\u606f\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931164","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u724850\u300120\u300110\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u56e2\u82b1\u5206\u522b\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u54ea\u4e9b\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6708\u5b63\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u83ca\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8377\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5170\u82b1\"}]","id":"511931165","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u4e2d\u8bbe\u7f6e\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5149\u706f\u4e0b\u5448\uff08    \uff09\u8272\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\"}]","id":"511931166","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6e2f\u5e01\u7684\u53d1\u949e\u94f6\u884c\u6709\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u82b1\u65d7\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\"}]","id":"511931167","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u8c03\u8fd0\u5e94\u91c7\u7528","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u62bc\u8fd0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53cc\u4eba\u4e13\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u673a\u8981\u5bc4\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5355\u4eba\u4e13\u9001\"}]","id":"511931168","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0a\u7684\uff08\t\t\uff09\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u53ef\u4f9b\u673a\u8bfb\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6a2a\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931169","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u54ea\u4e9b\u9762\u989d\u8bbe\u7f6e\u4e86\u78c1\u6027\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30011\u5143\"}]","id":"511931170","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u8f832005\u5e74\u7248\u53d6\u6d88\u4e86\uff08  \uff09\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931171","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u6d41\u901a\u82f1\u9551\u7eb8\u5e01(    )\u9762\u989d\u6709\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u82f1\u9551\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\u82f1\u9551\"}]","id":"511931172","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u674e\u67d0\u624b\u4e2d\u6301\u6709\u591a\u5e74\u524d\u88ab\u9a97\u65f6\u522b\u4eba\u627e\u7ed9\u4ed6\u76842\u5f20100\u5143\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u603b\u60f3\u7740\u628a\u5b83\u82b1\u51fa\u53bb\u624d\u4e0d\u5403\u4e8f\uff0c\u4e8e\u662f\u6765\u5230\u6c34\u679c\u644a\u524d\u4e70\u4e86150\u5143\u7684\u6c34\u679c\uff0c\u5e76\u628a2\u5f20100\u5143\u5047\u5e01\u9012\u7ed9\u4e86\u6c34\u679c\u644a\u4e3b\u5218\u67d0\uff0c\u7ed3\u679c\u88ab\u5218\u67d0\u53d1\u73b0\u5e76\u62a5\u8b66\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u674e\u67d0\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u4f2a\u9020\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u8fd8\u6301\u6709\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u5e94\u4ee5\u6301\u6709\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\u5b9a\u7f6a\uff0c\u4f9d\u6cd5\u8ffd\u7a76\u5211\u4e8b\u8d23\u4efb\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u5e94\u5bf9\u674e\u67d0\u590415\u65e5\u4ee5\u4e0b\u62d8\u7559\u30011\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u5e94\u5c062\u5f20100\u5143\u5047\u5e01\u4e88\u4ee5\u6ca1\u6536\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u5e94\u5c062\u5f20100\u5143\u5047\u5e01\u4e88\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\u3002\"}]","id":"511931173","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5bf9\u949e\u7968\u5904\u7406\u90e8\u95e8\u6e05\u5206\u53d1\u73b0\u7684\uff08\uff09\u9762\u989d\u4f2a\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u8f6c\u5165\u5173\u6ce8\u7c7b\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u5143\"}]","id":"511931174","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0a\u7684\uff08 \uff09\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u53ef\u4f9b\u673a\u8bfb\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931175","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u6a21\u7cca\u67e5\u8be2\u662f\u8f93\u5165\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u4e0d\u5b8c\u6574\u4fe1\u606f\u6216\u6a21\u7cca\u4fe1\u606f\uff0c\u4ece\u67e5\u8be2\u5230\u7684\u7ed3\u679c\u4e2d\u518d\u641c\u7d22\u662f\u5426\u5305\u542b\u5f85\u67e5\u73b0\u949e\u7684\u67e5\u8be2\u65b9\u5f0f\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f85\u67e5\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u5168\u90e8\u5b57\u7b26\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5f85\u67e5\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u90e8\u5206\u5b57\u7b26\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53d6\u6b3e\u65f6\u95f4\u70b9\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53d6\u6b3e\u65f6\u95f4\u6bb5\"}]","id":"511931176","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e1999\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2019\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u54ea\u4e9b\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511931177","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5230\u76ee\u524d\u4e3a\u6b62\u65e5\u5143\u5238\u4e0a\u6ca1\u6709\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u662f\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9632\u590d\u5370\u6807\u8bb0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u900f\u660e\u89c6\u7a97\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931178","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9999\u6e2f\u4e09\u5bb6\u53d1\u949e\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\uff0c\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u54ea\u4e9b\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff08   \uff09\u3002\u00a0","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5168\u606f\u8d34\u6761\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u73e0\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931179","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5236\u4f5c\u5546\u54c1\u65f6\uff0c\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\u4ea7\u54c1\u9762\u5e02\u524d\u5c06\uff08  \uff09\u7b49\u60c5\u51b5\u7684\u6750\u6599\u62a5\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u5907\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ea7\u54c1\u7167\u7247\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8bf4\u660e\u4ea7\u54c1\u5236\u4f5c\u5355\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u89c4\u683c\u6750\u8d28\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5ba3\u4f20\u65b9\u5f0f\"}]","id":"511931180","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6768\u5148\u751f\u5230\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u529e\u7406\u7f8e\u5143\u5b58\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u50a8\u84c4\u67dc\u5458\u5c0f\u738b\u5728\u4e3a\u5176\u529e\u7406\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\u53d1\u73b010\u5f20100\u5143\u9762\u503c\u7684\u7f8e\u5143\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5c0f\u738b\u4e0e\u4e00\u540d\u540c\u4e8b\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u6b63\u9762\u6c34\u5370\u7a97\u53ca\u80cc\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\u4f4d\u7f6e\u52a0\u76d6\u4e86\u5047\u5e01\u5370\u7ae0\uff0c\u5411\u6768\u5148\u751f\u51fa\u5177\u4e86\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u5173\u4e0a\u8ff0\u6848\u4f8b\u4e2d\uff0c\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u5728\u53d1\u73b010\u5f20\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7684\u60c5\u51b5\u4e0b\uff0c\u672a\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u548c\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u62a5\u544a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u4e0d\u5e94\u5f53\u9762\u52a0\u76d6\u5047\u5e01\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u6233\u8bb0\uff0c\u5e94\u653e\u5165\u7edf\u4e00\u7684\u4e13\u7528\u888b\u52a0\u5c01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u5e94\u5411\u5ba2\u6237\u5f00\u5177\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u6ca1\u6709\u5411\u5ba2\u6237\u5c65\u884c\u544a\u77e5\u7a0b\u5e8f\"}]","id":"511931181","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e3a\u89c4\u8303\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u4fdd\u62a4\u8d27\u5e01\u6301\u6709\u4eba\u7684\u5408\u6cd5\u6743\u76ca\uff0c\u6839\u636e\uff08 \uff09\uff0c\u5236\u5b9a\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u5316\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u5546\u4e1a\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u5168\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u4ee3\u8868\u5927\u4f1a\u5e38\u52a1\u59d4\u5458\u4f1a\u5173\u4e8e\u60e9\u6cbb\u7834\u574f\u91d1\u878d\u79e9\u5e8f\u72af\u7f6a\u7684\u51b3\u5b9a\u300b\"}]","id":"511931182","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\uff08  \uff09\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e\u73b0\u91d1\u6e05\u5206\u4e1a\u52a1\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e34\u67dc\u4eba\u5458\u5bf9\u6536\u5165\u73b0\u91d1\u8fdb\u884c\u624b\u5de5\u6311\u5254\u3001\u9274\u4f2a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6e05\u5206\u673a\u6784\u7ec4\u7ec7\u4e13\u95e8\u4eba\u5458\uff0c\u5bf9\u73b0\u91d1\u8fdb\u884c\u6e05\u70b9\u5904\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u6e05\u5206\u8bbe\u5907\u6311\u5254\u5047\u5e01\u5e76\u6309\u7167\u6807\u51c6\u8fdb\u884c\u8d28\u91cf\u5206\u7c7b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7528A\u7c7b\u70b9\u949e\u673a\u8ba1\u6570\u5e76\u8bb0\u5f55\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511931183","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u529e\u7406\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u9002\u7528\u573a\u666f\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8d27\u5e01\u5151\u6362\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u73b0\u91d1\u5b58\u53d6\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u73b0\u91d1\u6e05\u5206\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\"}]","id":"511931184","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u4e8e\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u76f8\u5173\u7684\u7f51\u7edc\u6216\u5a92\u4f53\u8206\u60c5\u4ee5\u53ca\u53d7\u7406\u7684\u6295\u8bc9\u3001\u4e3e\u62a5\u7b49\u4e8b\u9879\uff0c \u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u53ca\u65f6\u8fdb\u884c\u8c03\u67e5\u53d6\u8bc1\u3002\u8c03\u67e5\u53d6\u8bc1\u7684\u57fa\u672c\u5185\u5bb9\u5305\u62ec\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f53\u5730\u8425\u5546\u73af\u5883\u548c\u98ce\u571f\u4eba\u60c5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5f53\u4e8b\u4eba\u8eab\u4efd\u7b49\u57fa\u672c\u60c5\u51b5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u53d1\u751f\u7684\u65f6\u95f4\u3001\u5730\u70b9\u3001\u7ecf\u8fc7\u3001\u65b9\u5f0f\u3001\u540e\u679c\u7b49\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u7ecf\u884c\u653f\u4e3b\u7ba1\u90e8\u95e8\u6216\u76f8\u5173\u90e8\u95e8\u5ba1\u6279\u60c5\u51b5\"}]","id":"511931185","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u91d1\u878d\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5f62\u72b6\u3001\u5c3a\u5bf8\u53d1\u751f\u53d8\u5316\uff0c\uff08   \uff09\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u5e45\u957f\u8fb9\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u683c\u76f8\u5dee2%\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u5e45\u5bbd\u8fb9\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u683c\u76f8\u5dee4%\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u5e45\u957f\u8fb9\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u683c\u76f8\u5dee4%\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u5e45\u5bbd\u8fb9\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u89c4\u683c\u76f8\u5dee2%\u4ee5\u4e0a\"}]","id":"511931186","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u542b\uff08    \uff09\u7ea4\u7ef4\u4e1d\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5149\u706f\u4e0b\u65e0\u8367\u5149\u53cd\u5e94\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\"}]","id":"511931187","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"6\u670815\u65e5\uff0c\u5ba2\u6237\u5218\u5148\u751f\u63011\u5f20100\u5143\u5047\u5e01\u5230\u67d0\u5546\u4e1a\u94f6\u884c\u8425\u4e1a\u7f51\u70b9\u53cd\u6620\uff1a5\u5929\u524d\u5728\u8be5\u8425\u4e1a\u7f51\u70b9\u53d6\u6b3e5000\u5143\uff0c\u5176\u4e2d\u67091\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u73b0\u5728\u8981\u6c42\u94f6\u884c\u9000\u8d54\u3002\u67dc\u9762\u4eba\u5458\u5c0f\u674e\u5728\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u63d0\u4f9b\u8eab\u4efd\u8bc1\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u540e\uff0c\u53d7\u7406\u4e86\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u7684\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u540c\u65f6\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u6309\u7167\u89c4\u5b9a\u529e\u7406\u4e86\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u624b\u7eed\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u7eb8\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u4e0a\u52a0\u76d6\u5370\u7ae0\u3002\u8bf7\u95ee\u67dc\u5458\u5c0f\u674e\u672c\u5e94\u5982\u4f55\u64cd\u4f5c\uff1f\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u56e0\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u63d0\u4f9b\u7684\u8d44\u6599\u4e0d\u5168\uff0c\u5c0f\u674e\u5e94\u62d2\u7edd\u53d7\u7406\u8be5\u7533\u8bf7\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c0f\u674e\u5e94\u5f53\u9762\u544a\u77e5\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u8865\u9f50\u76f8\u5173\u6750\u6599\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5f53\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u8865\u9f50\u6750\u6599\u540e\uff0c\u5e94\u6bd4\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u4e2d\u5bf9\u4e8e\u5047\u786c\u5e01\u3001\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7684\u5904\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u4e88\u4ee5\u5c01\u5b58\uff0c\u6682\u4e0d\u5728\u7eb8\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u4e0a\u52a0\u76d6\u5370\u7ae0\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5728\u67e5\u8be2\u5de5\u4f5c\u5904\u7406\u5b8c\u7ed3\u540e\uff0c\u4f9d\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u5173\u4e8e\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u7a0b\u5e8f\u8fdb\u884c\u6536\u7f34\"}]","id":"511931188","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u670d\u52a1\u4e3b\u4f53\u5305\u62ec\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u975e\u94f6\u884c\u652f\u4ed8\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u81ea\u52a9\u670d\u52a1\u673a\u5177\u5382\u5546\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\"}]","id":"511931189","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\uff08\uff09\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u8bb8\u53ef\u6279\u51c6\u6587\u4ef6\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6d82\u6539\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5012\u5356\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51fa\u79df\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u51fa\u501f\"}]","id":"511931190","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u72481000\u65e5\u5143\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u9762\u989d\u9690\u50cf\u80fd\u770b\u5230\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001NIPPON\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011000\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5343\u5186\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6a31\u82b1\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931191","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u91d1\u878d\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u7f3a\u635f\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff08   \uff09\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u9762(\u4e0d\u542b4\u4e2a\u89d2\u53ca\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff09\u7f3a\u5931\uff0c\u5355\u5904\u7f3a\u5931\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e10 mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u591a\u5904\u7f3a\u5931\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u7f3a\u5931\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e10mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u5355\u4e2a\u7f3a\u89d2\uff0c\u7f3a\u89d2\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e20mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u591a\u4e2a\u7f3a\u89d2\uff0c\u7f3a\u89d2\u9762\u79ef\u7d2f\u8ba1\u5927\u4e8e30mm\u00b2\"}]","id":"511931192","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e9b\u5c5e\u4e8e\u654f\u611f\u4fe1\u606f\u3002\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e00\u6b21\u6027\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0110\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff0c\u5047\u5916\u5e0120\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5bf9\u5916\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4fdd\u7ba1\u4e0d\u5f53\uff0c\u81f4\u4f7f\u5047\u5e01\u6d41\u51fa\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5a92\u4f53\u53d1\u5e03\u7684\u4e0e\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\u76f8\u5173\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u4fe1\u606f\u8206\u60c5\"}]","id":"511931193","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u8d39\u7528\u6309\u7167\u201c\u5b9a\u5411\u5956\u52b1\uff0c\u4e13\u6b3e\u4e13\u7528\uff0c\u7edf\u4e00\u5ba1\u6838\uff0c\u76f4\u63a5\u62e8\u4ed8\u201d\u539f\u5219\u8fdb\u884c\u53d1\u653e\u4e0e\u7ba1\u7406\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u6363\u6bc1\u4f2a\u9020\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5370\u5236\u7a9d\u70b9\u7684\u6700\u9ad8\u5956\u52b125\u4e07\u5143\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5bf9\u67e5\u83b7\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u3001\u6301\u6709\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u5e76\u6293\u83b7\u4e3b\u8981\u6d89\u6848\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u6700\u9ad8\u5956\u52b118\u4e07\u5143\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u67e5\u83b7\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u534a\u6210\u54c1\u6309\u5176\u9762\u989d\u7684\u534a\u989d\u8ba1\u7b97\u6536\u7f34\u91cf\u3002\"}]","id":"511931194","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u53d8\u5316\u6709\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u76f4\u5f84\u7f29\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u8c03\u6574\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u82b1\u5349\u7f29\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u589e\u52a0\u5706\u70b9\"}]","id":"511931195","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e2019\u5e74\u7248\u30012020\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff0c\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u4e2d\u90e8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e0b\u65b9\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u5185\u542b\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u84dd\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012019\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53ea\u572850\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\u8bbe\u7f6e\u4e86\u8be5\u9879\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012020\u5e74\u72485\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\u9ec4\u8272\"}]","id":"511931196","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u6307\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5b8c\u6574\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u90e8\u5206\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c40\u90e8\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2a\u522b\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931197","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5ba2\u6237\u624b\u6301\u4e00\u5f20\u88ab\u8001\u9f20\u54ac\u8fc7\u76842005\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5230\u67d0\u519c\u5546\u884c\u8425\u4e1a\u7a97\u53e3\u8981\u6c42\u5151\u6362\u3002\u7f51\u70b9\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u674e\u67d0\u628a100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u62ff\u5230\u67dc\u9762\u540e\u770b\u4e86\u51e0\u773c\uff0c\u4ee5\u8be5\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u7279\u6b8a\u6b8b\u635f\u5e01\u65e0\u6cd5\u5151\u6362\u4e3a\u7531\uff0c\u628a\u7eb8\u5e01\u8fd8\u7ed9\u5ba2\u6237\uff0c\u8981\u6c42\u5ba2\u6237\u8981\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5151\u6362\u3002\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6536\u5230\u5ba2\u6237100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u540e\uff0c\u53d1\u73b0\u8be5\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u6309\u6d41\u7a0b\u8fdb\u884c\u4e86\u6ca1\u6536\u3002\u8bf7\u95ee\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u7f51\u70b9\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u54ea\u4e9b\u505a\u6cd5\u662f\u9519\u8bef\u7684\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8ba9\u516c\u4f17\u6301\u7279\u6b8a\u6b8b\u7f3a\u6c61\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5230\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5151\u6362\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c06\u4e0d\u5151\u6362\u7684\u7279\u6b8a\u6b8b\u7f3a\u6c61\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u9000\u56de\u5ba2\u6237\u624b\u4e2d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56e0\u4e3a\u6301\u6709\u4eba\u6ca1\u6709\u8981\u6c42\uff0c\u4e0d\u51fa\u5177\u8ba4\u5b9a\u8bc1\u660e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u56e0\u6ca1\u6709\u53d1\u751f\u5b9e\u9645\u5151\u6362\uff0c\u4e0d\u5bf9\u5ba2\u6237\u7684\u8981\u6c42\u5151\u6362\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u8fdb\u884c\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u522b\"}]","id":"511931198","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u529e\u7406\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u7ecf\u9274\u5b9a\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u51fa\u5177\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"}]","id":"511931199","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u300150\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5bf9\uff08  \uff09\u7b49\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u8fdb\u884c\u4e86\u8c03\u6574\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6284\u7eb8\u5de5\u827a\"}]","id":"511931200","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e9b\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u673a\u6784\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e0a\u6d77\u603b\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5b81\u6ce2\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u676d\u5dde\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6df1\u5733\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"}]","id":"511931201","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u7f51\u70b9\u4e8e\u8fd1\u671f\u5bf9\u5176\u5b58\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e00\u4f53\u673a\u8fdb\u884c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u529f\u80fd\u5347\u7ea7\uff0c\u901a\u8fc7\u672c\u673a\u6216\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u8f6f\u4ef6\u7cfb\u7edf\u53ef\u5b9e\u73b0\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u4fe1\u606f\u4e0e\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u8bb0\u5f55\u7684\u5173\u8054\uff0c\u80fd\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u7ea0\u7eb7\u4e2d\u5411\u5ba2\u6237\u63d0\u4f9b\u51fa\u73b0\u949e\u7684\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u3002\u4e14\u63d0\u4f9b\u7684\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u4e0e\u73b0\u949e\u80fd\u4e00\u4e00\u5bf9\u5e94\u3002\u5347\u7ea7\u5de5\u4f5c\u5b8c\u6210\u540e\uff0c\u67d0\u5ba2\u6237\u6301\u76f8\u5173\u6750\u6599\u81f3\u7f51\u70b9\u6295\u8bc9\u79f0\u5728\u53d6\u8be5\u5b58\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e00\u4f53\u673a\u4e2d\u53d6\u51fa\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u56e0\u53d6\u6b3e\u65f6\u770b\u4e0a\u770b\u89c1\u9ec4\u8272\u6807\u8bc6\u4e0a\u201c\u67e5\u8be2\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u89e3\u51b3\u5047\u5e01\u7ea0\u7eb7\u201d\u5b57\u6837\uff0c\u6545\u524d\u6765\u7533\u8bf7\u67e5\u8be2\u3002\u7f51\u70b9\u8981\u6c42\u5ba2\u6237\u586b\u5199\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\uff0c\u5e76\u544a\u77e5\u4e94\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u529e\u7ed3\u3002\u7f51\u70b9\u540e\u5c31\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u586b\u5236\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u901a\u77e5\u4e66\u300b\uff0c\u5e76\u5c06\u7b2c\u4e00\u8054\u4ea4\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\u3002\u8be5\u6848\u4f8b\u4e2d\u54ea\u4e9b\u73af\u8282\u5b58\u5728\u8fdd\u89c4\u95ee\u9898\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u5206\u7c7b\u8d34\u6807\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u53d7\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u5904\u7406\u65f6\u9650\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u53cd\u9988\"}]","id":"511931202","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u56e0\u53d7\u9ad8\u6e29\u4f5c\u7528\uff0c\u5f62\u6210\u7968\u9762\u5c40\u90e8\u7eb8\u5f20\u70ad\u5316\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u54ea\u4e9b\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e00\u5904\u70ad\u5316\uff0c\u70ad\u5316\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e10mm\u00b2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e24\u5904\u4ee5\u4e0a\u70ad\u5316\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u70ad\u5316\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e15mm\u00b2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u4e24\u5904\u4ee5\u4e0a\u70ad\u5316\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u70ad\u5316\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e18mm\u00b2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u70ad\u5316\u9762\u79ef\u867d\u672a\u8d85\u8fc7\u89c4\u5b9a\u6807\u51c6\uff0c\u4f46\u906e\u76d6\u4e86\u91cd\u8981\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u5f71\u54cd\u9632\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u7684\"}]","id":"511931203","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2021\u5e74\u8d3a\u5c81\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u4e0a\u8fd0\u7528\u4e86\u54ea\u4e9b\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53cc\u91d1\u5c5e\u7ed3\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6587\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5916\u7f18\u4e1d\u9f7f\"}]","id":"511931204","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5ba2\u6237\u624b\u6301\u4e00\u5f20\u88ab\u8001\u9f20\u54ac\u8fc7\u76842005\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5230\u67d0\u519c\u5546\u884c\u8425\u4e1a\u7a97\u53e3\u8981\u6c42\u5151\u6362\u3002\u7f51\u70b9\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u674e\u67d0\u628a100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u62ff\u5230\u67dc\u9762\u540e\u770b\u4e86\u51e0\u773c\uff0c\u4ee5\u8be5\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u7279\u6b8a\u6b8b\u635f\u5e01\u65e0\u6cd5\u5151\u6362\u4e3a\u7531\uff0c\u628a\u7eb8\u5e01\u8fd8\u7ed9\u5ba2\u6237\uff0c\u8981\u6c42\u5ba2\u6237\u8981\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5151\u6362\u3002\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6536\u5230\u5ba2\u6237100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u540e\uff0c\u53d1\u73b0\u8be5\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u6309\u6d41\u7a0b\u8fdb\u884c\u4e86\u6ca1\u6536\u3002\u8be5\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u8fdd\u53cd\u4e86\u76f8\u5173\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u6839\u636e\u73b0\u884c\u6cd5\u89c4\u53ef\u4ee5\u5bf9\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u673a\u6784\u91c7\u53d6\u54ea\u4e9b\u5904\u7f5a\u63aa\u65bd\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5904\u4ee51000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u76f4\u63a5\u8d1f\u8d23\u7684\u4e3b\u7ba1\u4eba\u5458\u548c\u5176\u4ed6\u76f4\u63a5\u8d23\u4efb\u4eba\u5458\uff0c\u4f9d\u6cd5\u7ed9\u4e88\u7eaa\u5f8b\u5904\u5206\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u59041000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u59041000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\"}]","id":"511931205","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff08\uff09\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u663e\u73b0\u7eff\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\"}]","id":"511931206","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff08  \uff09\u7eb8\u5e01\u5728\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u4e0b\u65b9\u65b0\u589e\u4e86\u767d\u6c34\u5370\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u5143\"}]","id":"511931207","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e7410\u670820\u65e5\uff0c\u4e00\u5ba2\u6237\u6301\u4e00\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\u5230\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u7f51\u70b9\uff0c\u58f0\u79f0\u6240\u6301\u5047\u5e01\u662f\u517610\u670812\u65e5\u5728\u8be5\u7f51\u70b9\u5b58\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e00\u4f53\u673a\u6240\u63d0\u53d6\u76842\u4e07\u5143\u73b0\u91d1\u4e2d\u5939\u5e26\u7684\uff0c\u8981\u6c42\u66f4\u6362\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8be5\u7f51\u70b9\u8d1f\u6709\u544a\u77e5\u5ba2\u6237\u901a\u8fc7\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u529f\u80fd\u5224\u522b\u5047\u5e01\u662f\u5426\u7531\u5176\u4ed8\u51fa\u7684\u4e49\u52a1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5ba2\u6237\u7533\u8bf7\u8d85\u8fc7\u65f6\u6548\uff0c\u8be5\u7f51\u70b9\u4e0d\u4e88\u53d7\u7406\u67e5\u7533\u8bf7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8be5\u7f51\u70b9\u4e00\u65e6\u53d7\u7406\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u5e94\u57283\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u529e\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8be5\u7f51\u70b9\u5f53\u9762\u544a\u77e5\u5ba2\u6237\u7533\u8bf7\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u5e94\u5907\u9f50\u7684\u76f8\u5173\u6750\u6599\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u65e0\u6545\u62d2\u7edd\u53d7\u7406\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\"}]","id":"511931208","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u751f\u6001\u9700\u8981\u4ee5\u4e0b\u591a\u65b9\u529b\u91cf\u5171\u540c\u7ef4\u62a4\uff1a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u7ecf\u8425\u4e3b\u4f53\u7684\u884c\u4e1a\u4e3b\u7ba1\u90e8\u95e8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u57fa\u5c42\u793e\u533a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u516c\u6c11\"}]","id":"511931209","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u8bef\u6536\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u62a5\u9001\u9014\u5f84\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f53\u5730\u672a\u8bbe\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u7684\uff0c\u5411\u6240\u5728\u5730\u4e0a\u4e00\u7ea7\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8bef\u6536\u5047\u5e01\u7531\u8bef\u6536\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u7531\u8bef\u4ed8\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u9001\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u7531\u4ed6\u884c\u6536\u7f34\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u62a5\u9001\"}]","id":"511931210","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u5370\u7684\u90e8\u5206\u5305\u62ec\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u201c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u201d\u884c\u540d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u88c5\u9970\u56e2\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u76f2\u6587\u9762\u989d\u6807\u8bb0\"}]","id":"511931211","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u7684\u6b27\u6d32\u5730\u56fe\u4e0e\u7b2c1\u7248\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u54ea\u4e24\u4e2a\u56fd\u5bb6\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5723\u9a6c\u529b\u8bfa\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9a6c\u8033\u4ed6\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u68b5\u8482\u5188\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u585e\u6d66\u8def\u65af\"}]","id":"511931212","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2003\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5404\u9762\u989d\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u53f3\u4e0b\u4fa7\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u540d\u79f0\u548c\u56fe\u6848\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u73e0\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u884c\u6807\"}]","id":"511931213","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ece\u76ee\u524d\u5df2\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u770b\uff0c\u5e38\u7528\u6750\u8d28\u6709\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u954d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e0d\u9508\u94a2\"}]","id":"511931214","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8fce\u63a5\u65b0\u4e16\u7eaa\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u7684\u52a8\u6001\u5168\u606f\u56fe\u4e2d\u5305\u542b\uff08     \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u706f\u7b3c\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9f99\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5343\u5e74\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012000\"}]","id":"511931215","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2021\u5e747\u67081\u65e5\uff0c\u67dc\u5458\u5c0f\u674e\u4e3a\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u529e\u7406\u7684\u5b58\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u53d1\u73b0\u5176\u4e2d\u6709\u4e00\u5f20\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7591\u4f3c\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u4ed6\u5c06\u8fd9\u5f20100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u62ff\u52302\u697c\u529e\u516c\u5ba4\u548c\u4e3b\u7ba1\u4ed4\u7ec6\u8fa8\u522b\uff0c\u786e\u8ba4\u662f\u5047\u5e01\u540e\uff0c\u56de\u5230\u67dc\u53f0\u544a\u77e5\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u8be5\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u6c34\u5370\u7a97\u548c\u80cc\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\u5904\u52a0\u76d6\u4e86\u5047\u5e01\u5370\u7ae0\uff0c\u5e76\u5f00\u5177\u4e86\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u3002\u5728\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u6781\u529b\u8981\u6c42\u4e0b\uff0c\u67dc\u5458\u5c0f\u674e\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u9012\u51fa\u8ba9\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u4ed4\u7ec6\u8fa8\u522b\u540e\u91cd\u65b0\u53c8\u6536\u56de\u3002\u4e0a\u8ff0\u6848\u4f8b\u4e2d\uff0c\u8fdd\u53cd\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u6709\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6536\u7f34\u8fc7\u7a0b\u79bb\u5f00\u4e86\u6301\u6709\u4eba\u89c6\u7ebf\u8303\u56f4\uff0c\u6ca1\u6709\u505a\u5230\u5f53\u9762\u52a0\u76d6\u5047\u5e01\u6233\u8bb0\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u67dc\u53f0\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u53c8\u9012\u7ed9\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u5e94\u5f00\u5177\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u800c\u975e\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u67dc\u5458\u6ca1\u6709\u5411\u5ba2\u6237\u5c65\u884c\u544a\u77e5\u4e49\u52a1\"}]","id":"511931216","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2020\u5e74\u72485\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3b\u8981\u53d6\u6d88\u4e86\uff08 \uff09\u7b49\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931217","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u89c4\u8303\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\u57fa\u672c\u539f\u5219\u5305\u62ec\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ef4\u62a4\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\u5730\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9f13\u52b1\u652f\u4ed8\u65b9\u5f0f\u548c\u8c10\u53d1\u5c55\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c0a\u91cd\u516c\u4f17\u81ea\u4e3b\u9009\u62e9\u6743\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4fdd\u969c\u4e2d\u5c0f\u5546\u6237\u5229\u76ca\"}]","id":"511931218","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\u4ea7\u54c1\u9762\u5e02\u524d\u5c06\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u60c5\u51b5\u7684\u6750\u6599\u62a5\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u5907\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ea7\u54c1\u7167\u7247\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u89c4\u683c\u6750\u8d28\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5ba3\u4f20\u65b9\u5f0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ea7\u54c1\u4ef7\u683c\"}]","id":"511931219","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u4e2a\u4eba\u9500\u552e\u975e\u6cd5\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u5ba3\u4f20\u54c1\u3001\u51fa\u7248\u7269\u6216\u8005\u5176\u4ed6\u5546\u54c1\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6216\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e88\u4ee5\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\uff08\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30015000\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30013\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u4e07\u5143\"}]","id":"511931220","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\u4ea7\u54c1\u9762\u5e02\u524d\u5c06\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u60c5\u51b5\u7684\u6750\u6599\u62a5\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u5907\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ea7\u54c1\u7167\u7247\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4ea7\u54c1\u5236\u4f5c\u5355\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4ea7\u54c1\u89c4\u683c\u6750\u8d28\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4ea7\u54c1\u4ef7\u683c\"}]","id":"511931221","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5c0f\u738b\u4e8e2014\u5e746\u67084\u65e5\u5728\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u53d6\u6b3e500\u5143\uff0c\u5e76\u4e8e6\u670815\u65e5\u5728\u6d88\u8d39\u65f6\u53d1\u73b0\u4e00\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5c0f\u738b\u7acb\u5373\u53bb\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u63d0\u51fa\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u5c0f\u738b\u63d0\u4f9b\u4e86\u53d6\u6b3e\u8bc1\u660e\u6750\u6599\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u4e88\u4ee5\u53d7\u7406\uff0c\u5f53\u65e5\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u5c06\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u544a\u77e5\u5c0f\u738b\uff0c\u8be5\u5047\u5e01\u4e0d\u662f\u94f6\u884c\u4ed8\u51fa\uff0c\u5c0f\u738b\u4e0d\u4fe1\u94f6\u884c\u7684\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u5f00\u5177\u4e86\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\uff0c\u5e76\u544a\u77e5\u5c0f\u738b\u53ef\u4ee5\u5411\u4e0a\u7ea7\u884c\u6216\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u63d0\u51fa\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u8fd9\u4e2a\u6848\u4f8b\u4e2d\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u6709","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u63d0\u51fa\u7533\u8bf7\u8d85\u8fc7\u7533\u8bf7\u65f6\u6548,\u94f6\u884c\u4e0d\u5e94\u53d7\u7406\u8be5\u7533\u8bf7\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u63d0\u51fa\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u672a\u63d0\u4f9b\u6709\u6548\u8eab\u4efd\u8bc1\u4ef6\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u672a\u544a\u77e5\u5c0f\u738b\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\u65f6\u6548\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u672a\u5411\u5c0f\u738b\u51fa\u5177\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u901a\u77e5\u4e66\u300b\"}]","id":"511931222","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f9d\u636e\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u4e8e2020\u5e744\u670815\u65e5\u5236\u5b9a\u5e76\u5b9e\u65bd\u4e86\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\"}]","id":"511931223","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u53d1\u73b0\u65b0\u7684\u9020\u5047\u624b\u6bb5\u5236\u4f5c\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u7acb\u5373\u5411\uff08\uff09\u62a5\u544a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u603b\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5f53\u5730\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u5370\u949e\u9020\u5e01\u603b\u516c\u53f8\"}]","id":"511931224","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\u5728\u6d41\u901a\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u76f4\u5f84\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u503c\u76f8\u5dee\u5927\u4e8e5%\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u91cd\u91cf\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u503c\u76f8\u5dee\u5927\u4e8e5%\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8fb9\u90e8\u539a\u5ea6\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u503c\u76f8\u5dee\u5927\u4e8e10%\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8fb9\u90e8\u539a\u5ea6\u4e0e\u6807\u51c6\u503c\u76f8\u5dee\u5927\u4e8e5%\"}]","id":"511931225","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f69\u949e\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u5728\uff08 \uff09\u6b63\u9762\u5e94\u7528\u4e86\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001100\u5143\"}]","id":"511931226","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u6c34\u5370\u4e3a\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9e1f\u5de2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u201c10\u201d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u201c\u7b2c29\u5c4a\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514b\u8fd0\u52a8\u4f1a\u201d\u5b57\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6c34\u7acb\u65b9\"}]","id":"511931227","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u51fa\u73b0\u4eba\u4e3a\u7684\u6587\u5b57\u3001\u56fe\u753b\u3001\u7b26\u53f7\u6216\u5176\u4ed6\u6807\u8bb0\uff0c\u6709(  )\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e00\u5904\u6d82\u5199\uff0c\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e200mm\u00b2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e00\u5904\u6d82\u5199\uff0c\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e20 mm\u00b2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u591a\u5904\u6d82\u5199\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e80 mm\u00b2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6d82\u5199\u9762\u79ef\u867d\u672a\u8d85\u8fc7\u89c4\u5b9a\u6807\u51c6\uff0c\u4f46\u906e\u76d6\u4e86\u91cd\u8981\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u5f71\u54cd\u9632\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u7684\"}]","id":"511931228","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u56de\u7b3c\u6b3e\u4e2d\u5939\u6742\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6b63\u89e3\u5904\u7406\u4e3a\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u884c\u4e88\u4ee5\u6ca1\u6536\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u9000\u56de\u89e3\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8981\u6c42\u5176\u8865\u8db3\u7b49\u989d\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56de\u7b3c\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001.\u5411\u89e3\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u5f00\u5177\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\u300b\"}]","id":"511931229","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0e2019\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u54ea\u4e9b\u76f8\u540c\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u78c1\u6027\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\"}]","id":"511931230","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5fc5\u987b\u9075\u5b88\u4e0b\u5217\u89c4\u5b9a\uff1a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5355\u9762\u4f7f\u7528\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e0d\u635f\u5bb3\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5f62\u8c61\u3001\u4e0d\u635f\u5bb3\u56fd\u5bb6\u5229\u76ca\u548c\u793e\u4f1a\u516c\u5171\u5229\u76ca\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e0d\u4f7f\u516c\u4f17\u8bef\u8ba4\u4e3a\u662f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4fdd\u8bc1\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4e2d\u4eba\u7269\u5934\u50cf\u3001\u56fd\u5fbd\u7684\u539f\u6709\u6bd4\u4f8b\uff0c\u4e0d\u53d8\u5f62\u3001\u5931\u771f\u3001\u7834\u574f\u6216\u88ab\u66ff\u6362\"}]","id":"511931231","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u59572019\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\u4e2d\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u5e01\u6750\u6709\uff08   \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u954d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u94dc\u950c\u5408\u91d1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e0d\u9508\u94a2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\"}]","id":"511931232","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5c0f\u5f20\u4e0e\u5c0f\u738b\u662f\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u7f51\u70b9\u81ea\u52a9\u8bbe\u5907\u7684\u7ba1\u7406\u5458\u3002\u67d0\u65e5\uff0c\u4e24\u4eba\u5728\u5bf9\u6240\u5728\u7f51\u70b9\u7684\u53d6\u6b3e\u673a\u6e05\u673a\u65f6\uff0c\u5c06\u67dc\u53f0\u6536\u5165\u7684\u73b0\u91d1\u7528A\u7c7b\u70b9\u949e\u673a\u6e05\u70b9\u540e\u52a0\u5165\u949e\u7bb1\u5185\u3002\u5f53\u65e5\uff0c\u5ba2\u6237\u5218\u5148\u751f\u5728\u8be5\u8bbe\u5907\u53d6\u6b3e\u540e\uff0c\u5bf9\u5176\u4e2d\u4e00\u5f20\u7eb8\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u5b58\u5728\u6000\u7591\uff0c\u6545\u5230\u8be5\u884c\u67dc\u9762\u8fdb\u884c\u54a8\u8be2\uff0c\u7ecf\u67dc\u9762\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u9274\u522b\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u67dc\u9762\u4eba\u5458\u4e3a\u907f\u514d\u5ba2\u6237\u6295\u8bc9\uff0c\u7528\u81ea\u5df1\u7684\u94b1\u6362\u4e0b\u4e86\u5ba2\u6237\u624b\u4e2d\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e76\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u505a\u6495\u6bc1\u5904\u7406\u3002\u8be5\u6848\u4f8b\u4e2d\uff0c\u8fdd\u53cd\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u6709\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u81ea\u52a9\u8bbe\u5907\u52a0\u949e\u73b0\u91d1\u672a\u7ecf\u8fc7\u6e05\u5206\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5ba2\u6237\u5e94\u9996\u5148\u5230\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5f53\u5730\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u8fdb\u884c\u67e5\u8be2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u63a5\u5230\u5ba2\u6237\u5173\u4e8e\u81ea\u52a9\u8bbe\u5907\u53d6\u51fa\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u6295\u8bc9\u540e\u672a\u6309\u7167\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7a0b\u5e8f\u8fdb\u884c\u67e5\u8be2\u5904\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u67dc\u9762\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u5bf9\u4e8e\u53d1\u73b0\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u672a\u6309\u89c4\u5b9a\u7a0b\u5e8f\u8fdb\u884c\u6536\u7f34\"}]","id":"511931233","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a(\u00a0 )","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b27\u6d32\u4e0d\u540c\u65f6\u671f\u7684\u95e8\u7a97\u5efa\u7b51\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b27\u6d32\u4e0d\u540c\u65f6\u671f\u7684\u6865\u6881\u5efa\u7b51\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6b27\u6d32\u7684\u5730\u56fe\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6b27\u76df\u65d7\u5e1c\"}]","id":"511931234","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u67dc\u9762\u529e\u7406\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e9b\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5f53\u9762\u4ee5\u7edf\u4e00\u683c\u5f0f\u7684\u4e13\u7528\u888b\u52a0\u5c01\uff0c\u5c01\u53e3\u5904\u52a0\u76d6\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u6233\u8bb0\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7b2c\u56db\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7334\u5e74\u751f\u8096\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e0110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u65e5\u514310000\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u822a\u5929\u949e100\u5143\"}]","id":"511931235","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5c5e\u4e8e2019\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u7684\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u591a\u5c42\u6b21\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9632\u590d\u5370\u6807\u8bb0\"}]","id":"511931236","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\u6309\u7167\uff08\uff09\u7684\u76f8\u5173\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5efa\u7acb\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u5185\u90e8\u7ba1\u7406\u5236\u5ea6\u548c\u64cd\u4f5c\u89c4\u8303\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\"}]","id":"511931237","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u30011\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u53ef\u89c1\uff08\uff09\u8272\u548c\uff08\uff09\u8272\u7684\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\"}]","id":"511931238","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u5171\u4ea7\u515a\u6210\u7acb100\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u662f\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u659c\u5168\u9f7f\u95f4\u9694\u534a\u9f7f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6587\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5fae\u7f29\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cc\u91d1\u5c5e\u7ed3\u6784\u548c\u5185\u82af\u590d\u5408\u6750\u6599\"}]","id":"511931239","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u5904\u7f6e\uff0c\u662f\u6307\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u6536\u5230\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u7ebf\u7d22\uff0c\u7504\u522b\u7ebf\u7d22\u5185\u5bb9\uff0c\u8ba4\u5b9a\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u5e76\u8fdb\u884c\u76f8\u5e94\u5904\u7406\u6216\u5904\u7f5a\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5f53\u4e8b\u4eba\u6295\u8bc9\u6216\u4e3e\u62a5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u672c\u884c\u91d1\u878d\u6d88\u8d39\u6743\u76ca\u4fdd\u62a4\u90e8\u95e8\u5206\u529e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7f51\u7edc\u6216\u5a92\u4f53\u8206\u60c5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e0a\u7ea7\u884c\u4ea4\u529e\u6216\u5176\u4ed6\u673a\u5173\u79fb\u9001\"}]","id":"511931240","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u5173\u4e8e2019\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff0c\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u6709\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u57282019\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u4e0a\u5747\u6709\u4f7f\u7528\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u89c2\u5bdf\u65b9\u5f0f\u548c\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u7279\u5f81\u76f8\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4f4d\u7f6e\u548c2005\u5e74\u7248\u76f8\u540c\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6709\u53d8\u8272\u548c\u52a8\u611f\u6548\u679c\"}]","id":"511931241","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\uff08\uff09\u884c\u4e3a\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\u7b2c\u56db\u5341\u516d\u6761\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5bf9\u8d1f\u9762\u8206\u60c5\u5904\u7f6e\u4e0d\u529b\u9020\u6210\u4e0d\u826f\u5f71\u54cd\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8bef\u6536\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u544a\u800c\u4e0d\u62a5\u544a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5411\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u62a5\u544a\u800c\u4e0d\u62a5\u544a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u672a\u516c\u793a\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u6388\u6743\u8bc1\u4e66\u6216\u8005\u9274\u5b9a\u4e1a\u52a1\u8303\u56f4\u7684\"}]","id":"511931242","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u662f\u6307\u901a\u8fc7\u5404\u79cd\u5f62\u5f0f\u5728\u5ba3\u4f20\u54c1\u3001\u51fa\u7248\u7269\u6216\u8005\u5176\u4ed6\u5546\u54c1\u4e0a\u4f7f\u7528\uff08 \uff09\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u653e\u5927\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7f29\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u540c\u6837\u5927\u5c0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u90e8\u5206\"}]","id":"511931243","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\uff08\uff09\u884c\u4e3a\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5728\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u56fd\u5bb6\u6216\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u672a\u6309\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u5bf9\u529e\u7406\u8d27\u5e01\u6536\u4ed8\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u6c34\u5e73\u8fdb\u884c\u8bc4\u4f30\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u73b0\u91d1\u4ece\u4e1a\u4eba\u5458\u4e0d\u5177\u5907\u5224\u65ad\u548c\u6311\u5254\u5047\u5e01\u4e13\u4e1a\u80fd\u529b\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u672a\u6309\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u5efa\u7acb\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u5185\u90e8\u7ba1\u7406\u5236\u5ea6\u548c\u64cd\u4f5c\u89c4\u8303\u7684\"}]","id":"511931244","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\uff08\uff09\u884c\u4e3a\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5728\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u56fd\u5bb6\u6807\u51c6\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u672a\u6309\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u91c7\u96c6\u3001\u5b58\u50a8\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u548c\u4e3b\u8981\u5916\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53d1\u751f\u5047\u5e01\u8bef\u4ed8\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53d1\u751f\u5047\u5e01\u8bef\u6536\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\"}]","id":"511931245","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"7\u670823\u65e5\uff0c\u5c0f\u674e\u53bb\u5de5\u884cB\u7f51\u70b9\u5b58\u6b3e10000\u5143\u3002\u529e\u7406\u5b58\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\uff0cB\u7f51\u70b9\u67dc\u5458\u5c0f\u5218\u544a\u8bc9\u5c0f\u674e\uff0c10000\u5143\u4e2d\u6709\u4e00\u5f20100\u5143\u662f\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u5c0f\u5218\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\uff0c\u5e76\u5f00\u5177\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\uff0c\u7b49\u5c0f\u674e\u79bb\u5f00\u540e\uff0c\u5728\u76f8\u5e94\u4f4d\u7f6e\u52a0\u76d6\u4e86\u5047\u5e01\u5370\u7ae0\u3002\u56de\u5bb6\u8def\u4e0a\uff0c\u5c0f\u674e\u60f3\u8d77\u8fd9\u5047\u5e01\u5e94\u8be5\u662f\u4ece\u519c\u884cA\u7f51\u70b9\u53d6\u51fa\uff0c\u4e8e\u662f\u53bbA\u7f51\u70b9\u8981\u6c42\u529e\u7406\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u4ee5\u6c42\u8bc1\u662f\u5426\u662f\u4eceA\u7f51\u70b9\u53d6\u51fa\u3002A\u7f51\u70b9\u67dc\u5458\u5c0f\u738b\u542c\u4e86\u5c0f\u674e\u7684\u8bc9\u6c42\u540e\uff0c\u4fbf\u4e3a\u5176\u67e5\u8be2\u3002\u7ecf\u67e5\u8be2\u540e\uff0c\u8be5\u5047\u5e01\u786e\u5b9e\u662f\u4eceA\u7f51\u70b9\u4ed8\u51fa\u7684\u3002\u968f\u540e\uff0cA\u7f51\u70b9\u5411\u5c0f\u674e\u9053\u6b49\uff0c\u5e76\u8d54\u507f\u4e86100\u5143\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5c0f\u5218\u672a\u6309\u89c4\u5b9a\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u5e94\u5bf9B\u7f51\u70b9\u59041\u5343\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c0f\u674e\u672a\u63d0\u4f9b\u8eab\u4efd\u8bc1\u3001\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u8bc1\u660e\u7b49\u8d44\u6599\uff0c\u5c0f\u738b\u4e0d\u5e94\u8be5\u4e3a\u5c0f\u674e\u529e\u7406\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u4e1a\u52a1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u5e94\u5bf9A\u7f51\u70b9\u59041\u5343\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\"}]","id":"511931246","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u8c03\u6574\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9634\u9633\u4e92\u8865\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931247","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6768\u5148\u751f\u5230\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u529e\u7406\u7f8e\u5143\u5b58\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u50a8\u84c4\u67dc\u5458\u5c0f\u738b\u5728\u4e3a\u5176\u529e\u7406\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\u53d1\u73b011\u5f20100\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7f8e\u5143\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5c0f\u738b\u4e0e\u4e00\u540d\u540c\u4e8b\u5728\u8be5\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u6b63\u9762\u6c34\u5370\u7a97\u53ca\u80cc\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\u4f4d\u7f6e\u52a0\u76d6\u4e86\u5047\u5e01\u5370\u7ae0\uff0c\u5411\u6768\u5148\u751f\u51fa\u5177\u4e86\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u5173\u4e0a\u8ff0\u6848\u4f8b\u4e2d\uff0c\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u5728\u53d1\u73b011\u5f20\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7684\u60c5\u51b5\u4e0b\uff0c\u672a\u7acb\u5373\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u62a5\u544a\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u4e0d\u5e94\u5f53\u9762\u52a0\u76d6\u5047\u5e01\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u6233\u8bb0\uff0c\u5e94\u653e\u5165\u7edf\u4e00\u7684\u4e13\u7528\u888b\u52a0\u5c01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u6ca1\u6709\u5c06\u8be5\u60c5\u51b5\u53ca\u65f6\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u62a5\u544a\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c0f\u738b\u6ca1\u6709\u5411\u5ba2\u6237\u5c65\u884c\u544a\u77e5\u7a0b\u5e8f\"}]","id":"511931248","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u9274\u522b\u3001\u6536\u7f34\u548c\u9274\u5b9a\u4e2d\u672a\u6309\u89c4\u5b9a\u5c65\u884c\u5411\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u62a5\u544a\u4e49\u52a1\u7684\uff0c\u5c06\u7ed9\u4e88\u7684\u5904\u7f5a\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5bf9\u5355\u4f4d\u8b66\u544a\u3001\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u4e2a\u4eba\u884c\u653f\u8b66\u544a\u3001\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\u5355\u4f4d\u6700\u9ad8\u7f5a\u6b3e5\u4e07\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7684\u5355\u4f4d\u6700\u9ad8\u7f5a\u6b3e3\u4e07\u5143\"}]","id":"511931249","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u900f\u5149\u4e0b\u89c2\u5bdf\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\uff0c\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u662f\u4e00\u6761\u8fde\u7eed\u7684\u9ed1\u8272\u7ebf\u6761\uff0c\u5728\u9ed1\u8272\u7ebf\u6761\u4e2d\u53ef\u770b\u89c1\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e00\u6247\u95e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b27\u5143\u7b26\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u8272\u7684\u949e\u7968\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8096\u50cf\"}]","id":"511931250","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u8f832005\u5e74\u7248\u5728\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e0a\u8865\u5145\u4e86\uff08   \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u5916\u914d\u5bf9\u56fe\u6848\u4e2d\u7684\u90e8\u5206\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931251","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u9002\u7528\u4e8e\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5883\u5185\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7684\u5883\u5916\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u9274\u522b\u8d27\u5e01\u884c\u4e3a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5883\u5185\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7684\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u884c\u4e3a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u9274\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u884c\u4e3a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6388\u6743\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u9274\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u884c\u4e3a\"}]","id":"511931252","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2021\u5e745\u67081\u65e5\uff0c\u67d0\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u7684\u73b0\u91d1\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u5fc3\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u674e\u67d0\u5728\u6e05\u5206\u7f51\u70b9\u7f34\u5b58\u7684\u73b0\u91d1\u65f6\uff0c\u53d1\u73b0\u4e863\u5f20100\u5143\u9762\u989d\u7684\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u674e\u67d0\u5e94\u8be5\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u7a0b\u5e8f\u6536\u7f34\u8be53\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5e76\u52a0\u76d6\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u6233\u8bb0\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5e94\u5f53\u6bd4\u7167\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u53ca\u5404\u79cd\u5047\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u6536\u7f34\u65b9\u5f0f\uff0c\u75312\u540d\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u4e88\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5e94\u5f53\u57283\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u4e0a\u8ff0\u671f\u9650\u5185\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u89e3\u7f34\u81f3\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u6240\u5728\u5730\u6ca1\u6709\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7684\uff0c\u7531\u8be5\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5411\u5176\u6240\u5728\u5730\u4e0a\u4e00\u7ea7\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u544a\u53ca\u89e3\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\"}]","id":"511931253","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u5c5e\u4e8e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u529e\u7406\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u5047\u5e01\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u4e13\u7528\u51ed\u8bc1\u7684\u662f\uff1a","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u6ca1\u6536\u6536\u636e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u4e66\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\"}]","id":"511931254","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e2019\u5e74\u7248\u786c\u5e01\u4e3b\u8981\u53d8\u5316\u60c5\u51b5\u7684\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u5143\u6750\u8d28\u4e0d\u53d8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011\u5143\u76f4\u5f84\u4e0d\u53d8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011\u89d2\u76f4\u5f84\u3001\u6750\u8d28\u4e0d\u53d8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u89d2\u6750\u8d28\u6539\u53d8\"}]","id":"511931255","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u5f53\u5177\u5907\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e9b\u6761\u4ef6\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5177\u67092\u540d\u4ee5\u4e0a\u5177\u5907\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u80fd\u529b\u7684\u4e13\u4e1a\u4eba\u5458\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6ee1\u8db3\u9274\u5b9a\u9700\u8981\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u5206\u6790\u6280\u672f\u6761\u4ef6\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5177\u6709\u56fa\u5b9a\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u573a\u6240\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8981\u6c42\u7684\u5176\u4ed6\u6761\u4ef6\"}]","id":"511931256","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u7533\u8bf7\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5f53\u5730\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u63d0\u4f9b\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6750\u6599\uff1a\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\u8eab\u4efd\u8bc1\u4ef6\u3001\u8425\u4e1a\u6267\u7167\u6216\u8005\u6cd5\u4eba\u767b\u8bb0\u8bc1\u4e66\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u62df\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4ea7\u54c1\u7684\u8bbe\u8ba1\u7a3f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u62df\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4ea7\u54c1\u7684\u5e7f\u544a\u5ba3\u4f20\u6587\u6848\"}]","id":"511931257","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6536\u7f34\uff08\u6ca1\u6536\uff09\u5047\u5e01\u4e13\u7528\u5c01\u88c5\u888b\u7531\uff08   \uff09\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5173\u4e8e\u5370\u53d1\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u4e1a\u52a1\u4e13\u7528\u51ed\u8bc1\u5370\u7ae0\u7b49\u6837\u5f0f\u6709\u5173\u4e8b\u9879\u7b49\u901a\u77e5\u300b\u8981\u6c42\u548c\u6240\u9644\u6837\u5f0f\u81ea\u884c\u5236\u4f5c\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u949e\u7968\u5904\u7406\u4e2d\u5fc3\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u529e\u7406\u5b58\u53d6\u6b3e\u548c\u8d27\u5e01\u5151\u6362\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u73b0\u91d1\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u5fc3\"}]","id":"511931258","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u5b9e\u73b0\u5168\u989d\u6e05\u5206\u7684\u65b9\u5f0f\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u81ea\u5efa\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u5fc3\u5b9e\u884c\u96c6\u4e2d\u6e05\u5206\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7f51\u70b9\u914d\u5907\u6e05\u5206\u673a\u72ec\u7acb\u6e05\u5206\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u94f6\u884c\u5171\u5efa\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u5fc3\u8fdb\u884c\u5408\u4f5c\u6e05\u5206\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u9a7b\u573a\u5f0f\u6216\u79bb\u573a\u5f0f\u6e05\"}]","id":"511931259","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\uff08    \uff09\u662f\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u5956\u52b1\u5bf9\u8c61\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6d77\u5173\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u56fd\u5bb6\u5b89\u5168\u90e8\u95e8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5de5\u5546\u884c\u653f\u7ba1\u7406\u90e8\u95e8\"}]","id":"511931260","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3b\u8981\u53d6\u6d88\u4e86\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9632\u590d\u5370\u6807\u8bb0\"}]","id":"511931261","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u529e\u516c\u5385\u5173\u4e8e\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5bf9\u5916\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u4e13\u9879\u6cbb\u7406\u5de5\u4f5c\u7684\u6307\u5bfc\u610f\u89c1\u300b\uff08\u94f6\u529e\u53d1\u30142013\u301514\u53f7\uff09\u548c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u529e\u516c\u5385\u5173\u4e8e\u8fdb\u4e00\u6b65\u660e\u786e\u5168\u989d\u6e05\u5206\u548c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u5de5\u4f5c\u6709\u5173\u4e8b\u9879\u7684\u901a\u77e5\u300b\uff08\u94f6\u529e\u53d1\u30142013\u3015197\u53f7\uff09\u8981\u6c42\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u5e94\u8bb0\u5f55\u4ee5\u4e0b\u4fe1\u606f\uff1a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7f51\u70b9\u540d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e1a\u52a1\u7c7b\u578b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u949e\u7968\u72b6\u6001\uff08\u771f\u5047\u6b8b\u65e7\uff09\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7248\u522b\"}]","id":"511931262","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u6d88\u8d39\u8005\u5728\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u529e\u7406\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u540e\uff0c\u5bf9\u73b0\u91d1\u771f\u4f2a\u5b58\u5728\u5f02\u8bae\uff0c\u7ecf\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u8fdb\u884c\u771f\u4f2a\u8bc6\u522b\u786e\u8ba4\u662f\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u75312\u540d\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u5f53\u9762\u4e88\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5f53\u9762\u52a0\u76d6\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u6233\u8bb0\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u544a\u77e5\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5982\u5bf9\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u5224\u65ad\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5411\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u7533\u8bf7\u9274\u5b9a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u544a\u77e5\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u53ef\u4ee5\u901a\u8fc7\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u529f\u80fd\u5224\u522b\u5047\u5e01\u662f\u5426\u7531\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4ed8\u51fa\"}]","id":"511931263","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5c5e\u4e8e2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0a\u5e94\u7528\u7684\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4eba\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931264","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u4e2d\u54ea\u4e9b\u9762\u989d\u6ca1\u6709\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u5370\u76f2\u6587\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001500\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001200\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001100\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\"}]","id":"511931265","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u4f9d\u636e\uff08\uff09\u5236\u5b9a\u4e86\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6b8b\u7f3a\u6c61\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5151\u6362\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6311\u5254\u6807\u51c6\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\"}]","id":"511931266","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u5f69\u949e\u7684\u8367\u5149\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e2d\uff0c\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u89c1\uff08  \uff09\u9762\u989d\u6709\u201c\u661f\u6761\u65d7\u201d\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511931267","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u54ea\u4e9b\u5238\u522b\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u63aa\u65bd\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5143\"}]","id":"511931268","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5c0f\u674e\u5927\u5b66\u6bd5\u4e1a\u540e\uff0c\u987a\u5229\u88ab\u67d0\u94f6\u884c\u5f55\u7528\u4e3a\u50a8\u84c4\u67dc\u5458\u30026\u670830\u65e5\u5c0f\u674e\u521a\u4e0a\u73ed\uff0c\u5ba2\u6237\u5f20\u5148\u751f\u62ff\u6765\u4e00\u5f20\u949e\u7968\uff0c\u8bf4\u662f6\u670828\u65e5\u5728\u8be5\u884cATM\u53d6\u7684\u6b3e\uff0c\u56de\u53bb\u540e\u53d1\u73b0\u662f\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u5bf9\u5047\u5e01\u7565\u6709\u6240\u77e5\u7684\u5c0f\u674e\u53d1\u73b0\u786e\u5b9e\u662f\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u5c31\u5f53\u7740\u5ba2\u6237\u9762\u52a0\u76d6\u4e86\u5047\u5e01\u5370\u7ae0\uff0c\u5e76\u529e\u7406\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u7a0b\u5e8f\u3002\u7136\u540e\u518d\u901a\u8fc7\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7cfb\u7edf\u4e3a\u5ba2\u6237\u8fdb\u884c\u67e5\u8be2\uff0c\u540c\u65f6\u6253\u5370\u5f53\u5929\u52a0\u949e\u8bb0\u5f55\u7ed9\u5ba2\u6237\u770b\uff0c\u6700\u540e\u586b\u5199\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u901a\u77e5\u4e66\uff0c\u8868\u660e\u5047\u5e01\u975e\u8be5\u884c\u6d41\u51fa\u3002\u8bf7\u6307\u51fa\u8fd9\u4e2a\u6848\u4f8b\u4e2d\u8fdd\u53cd\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u5305\u62ec\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u7ea0\u7eb7\u672a\u7ed3\u675f\u524d\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u89c6\u540c\u201c\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u3001\u5047\u786c\u5e01\u201d\u4e13\u7528\u4fe1\u5c01\u5c01\u5b58\u5904\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8d85\u8fc7\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u671f\u9650\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8fdb\u884c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u65f6\u5e94\u8981\u6c42\u5ba2\u6237\u63d0\u4f9b\u6709\u6548\u8bc1\u4ef6\u53ca\u53d6\u6b3e\u8bc1\u660e\uff0c\u5e76\u586b\u5199\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u5e94\u5728\u67e5\u8be2\u5de5\u4f5c\u5904\u7406\u5b8c\u7ed3\u540e\u529e\u7406\"}]","id":"511931269","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u987b\u5728\u56fe\u6837\u6307\u5b9a\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6807\u6ce8\u6e05\u6670\u53ef\u8fa8\u7684\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u957f\u5ea6\u548c\u5bbd\u5ea6\u5206\u522b\u4e0d\u4f4e\u4e8e\u56fe\u6837\u957f\u5ea6\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u6bd4\u4f8b\u3002\u4ee5\u4e0b\u60c5\u5f62\u9664\u5916\uff1a\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53cc\u9762\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5355\u9762\u9762\u79ef\u5c0f\u4e8e\u539f\u5927\u5c0f\u768450%\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5728\u6709\u5f62\u8f7d\u4f53\u4e0a\u4f7f\u7528\u5404\u8fb9\u957f\u653e\u5927\u548c\u7f29\u5c0f\u6bd4\u4f8b\u8d85\u8fc7\u539f\u8fb9\u957f\u768450%\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\"}]","id":"511931270","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e2d\uff0c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u91c7\u7528\u53cc\u8272\u5f02\u5f62\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u5238\u522b\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012005\u7248100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012015\u7248100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012005\u724850\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012019\u724850\u5143\"}]","id":"511931271","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u5c65\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u4e49\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u5e94\u91c7\u53d6\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e9b\u63aa\u65bd\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u786e\u4fdd\u5728\u7528\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u7684\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u7b26\u5408\u56fd\u5bb6\u548c\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ec4\u7ec7\u5f00\u5c55\u673a\u6784\u5185\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u77e5\u8bc6\u4e0e\u6280\u80fd\u57f9\u8bad\uff0c\u786e\u4fdd\u73b0\u91d1\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u5177\u5907\u5224\u65ad\u548c\u6311\u5254\u5047\u5e01\u4e13\u4e1a\u80fd\u529b\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6309\u7167\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u91c7\u96c6\u3001\u5b58\u50a8\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u548c\u4e3b\u8981\u5916\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5efa\u7acb\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u672c\u7cfb\u7edf\u5185\u73b0\u91d1\u4ece\u4e1a\u4eba\u5458\u53cd\u5047\u5956\u52b1\u5236\u5ea6\"}]","id":"511931272","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e8c\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7ea2\u5916\u56fe\u50cf\u53ef\u89c1\u90e8\u5206\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u5927\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\u4e3b\u56fe\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u6c34\u5e73\u5e8f\u5217\u53f7\"}]","id":"511931273","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u76b1\u8936\u3001\u6298\u75d5\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff08    \uff09\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b04\u5904\u4ee5\u4e0a\u76b1\u8936\uff0c\u76b1\u7eb9\u660e\u663e\u3001\u65e0\u6cd5\u590d\u539f\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u76b1\u8936\u957f\u5ea6\u5927\u4e8e20mm\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7968\u9762\u5355\u4e2a\u76b1\u8936\u957f\u5ea6\u5927\u4e8e10mm\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7968\u9762\u51fa\u73b0\u8d2f\u7a7f\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u660e\u663e\u6298\u75d5\uff0c\u6298\u75d5\u5904\u7eb8\u8d28\u53d8\u8f6f\u3001\u8d77\u6bdb\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7968\u9762\u76b1\u8936\u5f71\u54cd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7f8e\u89c2\u7684\"}]","id":"511931274","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u89c2\u5bdf\u5230\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u968f\u673a\u5206\u5e03\u7684\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\uff0c\u6bcf\u4e00\u6839\u7ea4\u7ef4\u5448\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"}]","id":"511931275","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ec4\"}]","id":"511931276","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e9b\u989c\u8272\u662f\u7f8e\u5143\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u53ef\u80fd\u51fa\u73b0\u7684\u989c\u8272\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7d2b\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"}]","id":"511931277","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u82f1\u9551\u5851\u6599\u949e\u4e0a\u91d1\u5c5e\u56fe\u6848\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u5efa\u7b51\u539f\u578b\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5927\u82f1\u535a\u7269\u9986\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f0a\u4e3d\u838e\u767d\u5854\u697c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6e29\u5f7b\u65af\u7279\u6559\u5802\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4f26\u6566\u5854\u6865\"}]","id":"511931278","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u72485\u300110\u6b27\u5143\u589e\u52a0\u7684\u91cd\u8981\u89c6\u89c9\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08   \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8096\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u5e26\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8096\u50cf\u5168\u606f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6570\u5b57\"}]","id":"511931279","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5305\u542b\u9762\u989d\u4fe1\u606f\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931280","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53d1\u751f\u4ee5\u4e0b\uff08\uff09\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u53ef\u59041000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u30015\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u4e863\u5f20\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e01\u800c\u4e0d\u6536\u7f34\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u56de\u7b3c\u5238\u4e2d\u5939\u6742\u5047\u5e01\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u5b58\u50a8\u65f6\u95f4\u4e0d\u7b26\u5408\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8981\u6c42\"}]","id":"511931281","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"20\u82f1\u9551\u7eb8\u5e01\u5168\u606f\u6761\u56fe\u6848\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e9a\u5f53\u65af\u5bc6\u8096\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5973\u738b\u8096\u50cf\"}]","id":"511931282","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"G\u7cfb\u52175\u82f1\u9551\u5851\u6599\u949e\u6b63\u9762\u8bbe\u7f6e\u6709\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u51e0\u4e2a\u5168\u606f\u56fe\u6848\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u900f\u660e\u89c6\u7a97\u5973\u738b\u5934\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4f0a\u4e3d\u838e\u767d\u5854\u56fe\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u606f3D\u738b\u51a0\u56fe\u50cf\"}]","id":"511931283","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u822a\u5929\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\uff08   \uff09\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u52a8\u611f\u5149\u53d8\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u6280\u672f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u5370\"}]","id":"511931284","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5b9e\u884c\u5c5e\u5730\u7ba1\u7406\u3001\u4e00\u4e8b\u4e00\u6279\u3002\uff08\uff09\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u4e0a\u6d77\u603b\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5404\u5206\u884c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8425\u4e1a\u7ba1\u7406\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u7701\u4f1a\uff08\u7701\u5e9c\uff09\u57ce\u5e02\u4e2d\u5fc3\u652f\u884c\"}]","id":"511931285","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012015\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5e94\u7528\u7684\u53cc\u8272\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7531\u5b57\u6bcd\u548c\u6570\u5b57\u7ec4\u6210\uff0c\u517111\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\u548c\u9ed1\u8272\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u5747\u5177\u6709\u78c1\u6027\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5b9a\u5236\u5b57\u578b\uff0c\u5728\u5e38\u7528\u5b57\u4f53\u4e2d\u65e0\u6cd5\u627e\u5230\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u56fd\u9645\u6807\u51c6\u5b57\u578b\uff0c\u66f4\u52a0\u6613\u4e8e\u88ab\u8bbe\u5907\u8bc6\u522b\"}]","id":"511931286","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\u4e2d\u62df\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u7533\u8bf7\u4eba\u7c7b\u522b\u53ef\u4ee5\u5206\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6cd5\u4eba\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u81ea\u7136\u4eba\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u516c\u6c11\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5176\u4ed6\u7ec4\u7ec7\"}]","id":"511931287","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5bf92010\u7cfb\u5217\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012010\u7cfb\u5217\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u6709\u4e24\u6761\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012010\u7cfb\u5217\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\u90fd\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012010\u7cfb\u5217\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u5728\u7968\u9762\u4e0a\u5370\u5236\u4e86\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012010\u7cfb\u5217\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u9632\u4f2a\"}]","id":"511931288","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5173\u4e8e2019\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7968\u9762\u8c03\u6574\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5747\u8c03\u6574\u88c5\u9970\u56e2\u82b1\u7684\u6837\u5f0f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5747\u8c03\u6574\u6bdb\u6cfd\u4e1c\u5934\u50cf\u6837\u5f0f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5747\u8c03\u6574\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u6837\u5f0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5747\u8c03\u6574\u4e86\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u6837\u5f0f\"}]","id":"511931289","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e9b\u7248\u522b\u5238\u522b\u4e0a\u5e94\u7528\u4e86\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u5238\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012015\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u5238\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012019\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u5238\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012019\u5e74\u724820\u5143\u5238\"}]","id":"511931290","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u54ea\u4e9b\u4f4d\u7f6e\u5177\u6709\u8367\u5149\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5e74\u7248\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931291","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5370\u5236\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff08   \uff09\u7b49\u91cd\u8981\u4e8b\u9879\u5c5e\u4e8e\u56fd\u5bb6\u79d8\u5bc6\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6280\u672f\u4eba\u5458\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7279\u6b8a\u6750\u6599\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5de5\u827a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6280\u672f\"}]","id":"511931292","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5168\u989d\u6e05\u5206\u6307\u94f6\u884c\uff08   \uff09\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u5238\u522b\u7ecf\u8fc7\u6e05\u5206\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u67dc\u53f0\u652f\u4ed8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u81ea\u52a8\u53d6\u6b3e\u673a\u652f\u4ed8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u81ea\u52a8\u5b58\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e00\u4f53\u673a\u652f\u4ed8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7f34\u5b58\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u5e93\u56de\u7b3c\u5238\"}]","id":"511931293","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53d1\u884c\u5e93\u8bbe\u4e13\u67dc\uff08\u7bb1\uff09\u5b58\u653e\u6837\u5e01\uff0c\u5efa\u7acb\u300a\u6837\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\u300b\uff0c\u5b9e\u884c\uff08   \uff09\u5236\u5ea6\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8d26\u5b9e\u517c\u7ba1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5b9a\u671f\u6838\u5bf9\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8d26\u5b9e\u5206\u7ba1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cc\u4eba\u7ba1\u7406\"}]","id":"511931294","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7ecf\u7504\u522b\uff0c \u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u7ebf\u7d22\u4e0d\u6d89\u53ca\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\uff0c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u6309\u4ee5\u4e0b\u60c5\u51b5\u5206\u522b\u5904\u7406\uff1a","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u804c\u8d23\u8303\u56f4\u5185\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u4e0d\u4e88\u5904\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c5e\u4e8e\u672c\u90e8\u95e8\u804c\u8d23\u8303\u56f4\u5185\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u53ca\u65f6\u7ed9\u4e88\u7ebf\u7d22\u6765\u6e90\u65b9\u7b54\u590d\uff0c\u505a\u597d\u76f8\u5e94\u653f\u7b56\u6cd5\u89c4\u7684\u89e3\u91ca\u53ca\u5f15\u5bfc\u5de5\u4f5c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5176\u4ed6\u6267\u6cd5\u804c\u80fd\u90e8\u95e8\u804c\u8d23\u8303\u7574\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u53ca\u65f6\u8f6c\u4ea4\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\u529e\u516c\u5ba4\u8fdb\u884c\u767b\u8bb0\u5e76\u5206\u529e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u804c\u8d23\u8303\u56f4\u5185\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u4ea4\u7531\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\u529e\u516c\u5ba4\u4f9d\u6cd5\u8f6c\u7ed9\u76f8\u5173\u90e8\u95e8\u5904\u7406\"}]","id":"511931295","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u529e\u516c\u5385\u5173\u4e8e\u8fdb\u4e00\u6b65\u660e\u786e\u5168\u989d\u6e05\u5206\u548c\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u5de5\u4f5c\u6709\u5173\u4e8b\u9879\u7684\u901a\u77e5\u300b\uff0c\u7ea0\u7eb7\u89e3\u51b3\u673a\u5236\u4e3b\u8981\u5305\u62ec\u4ee5\u4e0b\u90a3\u51e0\u4e2a\u65b9\u9762\uff08\tABCE \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7533\u8bf7\u53ca\u53d7\u7406\u6761\u4ef6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u67e5\u8be2\u65b9\u5f0f\u53ca\u65f6\u9650\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u67e5\u8be2\u7ed3\u679c\u5904\u7f6e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u518d\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\"}]","id":"511931296","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u5b9a\u4e0e\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\u4e2d\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e9b\u884c\u4e3a\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u4e14\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7684\u5904\u4ee51000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d1\u751f\u5047\u5e01\u8bef\u6536\u884c\u4e3a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u672a\u5bf9\u5ba2\u6237\u7b49\u503c\u8d54\u4ed8\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u5bf9\u8d1f\u9762\u8206\u60c5\u5904\u7f6e\u4e0d\u529b\u9020\u6210\u4e0d\u826f\u5f71\u54cd\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8bef\u6536\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u5e94\u5f53\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u544a\u800c\u4e0d\u62a5\u544a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5e94\u5411\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u62a5\u544a\u800c\u4e0d\u62a5\u544a\u7684\"}]","id":"511931297","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u5238\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e0a\u5206\u522b\u4f7f\u7528\u8fc7\u54ea\u4e9b\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001RMB100\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u00a5100\"}]","id":"511931298","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u8c03\u6574\u4e86\u54ea\u4e9b\u9632\u4f2a\u6807\u8bc6\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d6\u6d88\u53f3\u4fa7\u51f9\u5370\u624b\u611f\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8c03\u6574\u5de6\u4fa7\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u6837\u5f0f\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8c03\u6574\u4e2d\u90e8\u88c5\u9970\u56e2\u82b1\u7684\u6837\u5f0f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8c03\u6574\u53f3\u4fa7\u6bdb\u6cfd\u4e1c\u5934\u50cf\u6837\u5f0f\"}]","id":"511931299","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u542b\u6709\uff08   \uff09\u8272\u5f69\u8272\u7ea4\u7ef4\u4e1d\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9ec4\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u84dd\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7eff\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\"}]","id":"511931300","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9000\u4f11\u8001\u4eba\u90b1\u67d0\u6700\u8fd1\u8ff7\u4e0a\u4e86\u79cd\u82b1\uff0c\u67d0\u65e5\uff0c\u90b1\u67d0\u53d1\u73b0\u949e\u7968\u4e0a\u7684\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u81ea\u5df1\u559c\u6b22\u7684\u5170\u82b1\uff0c\u5728\u67e5\u770b\u4e86\u6240\u6709\u5238\u522b\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u540e\uff0c\u5979\u4f1a\u6709\u4ee5\u4e0b\u53d1\u73b0\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u6708\u5b63\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u5170\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u8377\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300150\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u83ca\u82b1\"}]","id":"511931301","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u884c\u4e3a\u4eba\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u53c8\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\uff0c\u4ee5(    )\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u51fa\u552e\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511931302","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u5bf9\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u8fdb\u884c\u8c03\u67e5\u53d6\u8bc1\u7ec8\u7ed3\u540e\uff0c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u5f53\u64b0\u5199\u8c03\u67e5\u62a5\u544a\uff0c\u4e0a\u62a5\u672c\u5355\u4f4d\u884c\u9886\u5bfc\u5ba1\u9605\u3002\u8c03\u67e5\u62a5\u544a\u5e94\u81f3\u5c11\u5305\u62ec\u4e0b\u5217\u5185\u5bb9\uff1a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u88ab\u8c03\u67e5\u3001\u68c0\u67e5\u5f53\u4e8b\u4eba\u7684\u57fa\u672c\u60c5\u51b5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7ecf\u8c03\u67e5\u6838\u5b9e\u7684\u8fdd\u6cd5\u4e8b\u5b9e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u672a\u67e5\u5b9e\u7684\u8fdd\u6cd5\u4e8b\u5b9e\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u63d0\u51fa\u5904\u7406\u610f\u89c1\"}]","id":"511931303","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u30015\u89d2\u548c1\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u505a\u4e86\u9002\u5f53\u6536\u7f29\uff0c\u8fd9\u4e09\u79cd\u82b1\u5349\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6708\u5b63\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u83ca\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8377\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5170\u82b1\"}]","id":"511931304","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5bf9\u672c\u8f96\u533a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u57f9\u8bad\u5de5\u4f5c\u7684\u73b0\u573a\u68c0\u67e5\u7684\u65b9\u6cd5\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5b9e\u9645\u64cd\u4f5c\u6d4b\u8bd5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e66\u9762\u7b54\u5377\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u67e5\u770b\u76f8\u5173\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u73b0\u573a\u8be2\u95ee\"}]","id":"511931305","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e3a\u8c0b\u53d6\u5229\u76ca\uff0c\u5c0f\u674e\u4ece\u7f51\u4e0a\u4e70\u4e86\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u5de5\u5177\u5f00\u59cb\u5236\u9020\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u30027\u67082\u65e5\uff0c\u5c0f\u5f20\u901a\u8fc7\u7f51\u7edc\u6e20\u9053\u4ece\u5c0f\u674e\u90a3\u8d2d\u4e70\u4f2a\u9020\u768420\u5143\u5238\u522b\uff0c\u4ee5\u6bcf\u5f208\u5143\u7684\u4ef7\u683c\u8d2d\u4e70\u4e865000\u5f2020\u5143\uff0c\u5171\u652f\u4ed8\u4e864\u4e07\u5143\uff0c\u5e76\u4e8e7\u67083\u65e5\u5728\u519c\u8d38\u5e02\u573a\u4f7f\u7528\u4e8620\u5f20\u3002\u8bf7\u95ee\u4ee5\u4e0b\u8bf4\u6cd5\u6b63\u786e\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5c0f\u674e\u72af\u4e86\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\uff0c\u5e94\u5bf9\u5c0f\u674e\u59043\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a10\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5c0f\u674e\u72af\u4e86\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\uff0c\u5e94\u5bf9\u5c0f\u674e\u590410\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u6216\u65e0\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c0f\u5f20\u72af\u4e86\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\uff0c\u5e94\u5bf9\u5c0f\u5f20\u59043\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0a10\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\uff0c\u5e76\u59045\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a50\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c0f\u5f20\u72af\u4e86\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\uff0c\u5e94\u5bf9\u5c0f\u5f20\u59043\u5e74\u4ee5\u4e0b\u6709\u671f\u5f92\u5211\u6216\u62d8\u5f79\uff0c\u5e76\u59042\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a20\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u91d1\u3002\"}]","id":"511931306","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u8bf4\u6cd5\u9519\u8bef\u7684\u662f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u5f53\u81ea\u6536\u5230\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d772\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\uff0c\u901a\u77e5\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u62a5\u9001\u5f85\u9274\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u5f53\u81ea\u6536\u5230\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u901a\u77e5\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d772\u65e5\u5185\uff0c\u5c06\u5f85\u9274\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\u9001\u8fbe\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u65e0\u7279\u6b8a\u60c5\u51b5\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\u81ea\u53d7\u7406\u9274\u5b9a\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d7715\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5b8c\u6210\u9274\u5b9a\u5e76\u51fa\u5177\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u65e0\u7279\u6b8a\u60c5\u51b5\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\u81ea\u53d7\u7406\u9274\u5b9a\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d7715\u65e5\u5185\u5b8c\u6210\u9274\u5b9a\u5e76\u51fa\u5177\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\"}]","id":"511931307","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u5404\u9762\u989d\u949e\u7968\u4e0a\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7684\u4f4d\u7f6e\u5404\u4e0d\u76f8\u540c\uff0c\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5728\u4eba\u50cf\u5de6\u8fb9\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6709\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u7f8e\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u7f8e\u5143\"}]","id":"511931308","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5c5e\u4e8e2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0a\u5e94\u7528\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e2d\uff0c\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248\u548c2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u90fd\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u6709\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7ea2\u5916\u914d\u5bf9\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931309","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u91d1\u878d\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5728\u6d41\u901a\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u56e0\u53d7\u5230\u4fb5\u8680\uff0c\u5f62\u6210\u7968\u9762\u5c40\u90e8\u6c61\u6e0d\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff08    \uff09\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5370\u5237\u533a\u57df\u51fa\u73b0\u591a\u5904\u6c61\u6e0d\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u6c61\u6e0d\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e150mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5370\u5237\u533a\u57df\u5355\u4e2a\u6c61\u6e0d\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e100mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u975e\u5370\u5237\u533a\u57df\u51fa\u73b0\u591a\u5904\u6c61\u6e0d\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u6c61\u6e0d\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e50mm\u00b2\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6c61\u6e0d\u9762\u79ef\u906e\u76d6\u91cd\u8981\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff0c\u5f71\u54cd\u9632\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u7684\u3002\"}]","id":"511931310","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53d1\u884c70\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u4e0a\u5e94\u7528\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u52a8\u611f\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931311","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u56fd\u7eb8\u5f20\u6210\u4efd\u8f83\u4e3a\u7279\u6b8a\uff0c\u4e3b\u8981\u7531\uff08 \uff09\u6df7\u5408\u800c\u6210\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u68c9\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u9ebb\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u805a\u5408\u7269\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e09\u6860\u6811\u76ae\"}]","id":"511931312","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3b\u8981\u53d8\u5316\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u63d0\u9ad8\u4e86\u7968\u9762\u8272\u5f69\u9c9c\u4eae\u5ea6\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f18\u5316\u4e86\u7968\u9762\u7ed3\u6784\u5c42\u6b21\u4e0e\u6548\u679c\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u63d0\u5347\u4e86\u6574\u4f53\u9632\u4f2a\u6027\u80fd\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6539\u5584\u4e86\u949e\u7968\u6d41\u901a\u8010\u6027\"}]","id":"511931313","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\uff08  \uff091000\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u542b\u6709\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c2000\u5e74\u7248\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c1996\u5e74\u7248\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c2001\u5e74\u7248\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c1993\u5e74\u7248\"}]","id":"511931314","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u4ee5\u4e0b\uff08  \uff09\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u56fa\u5b9a\u82b1\u5349\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u767d\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7ea2\u84dd\u5f69\u8272\u7ea4\u7ef4\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"}]","id":"511931315","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5404\u7701\u7ea7\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u6c47\u603b\u5168\u8f96\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u7533\u8bf7\uff0c\u7f16\u5236\uff08\uff09\u53d1\u9001\u81f3\u603b\u884c\u3002\u603b\u884c\u5e94\u53ca\u65f6\u6279\u590d\uff0c\u751f\u6210\uff08\uff09\uff0c\u53cd\u9988\u81f3\u5404\u7701\u7ea7\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6c47\u603b\u8868\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6279\u590d\u8868\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6279\u51c6\u8868\u300b\"}]","id":"511931316","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\uff08\uff09\u884c\u4e3a\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u672a\u6309\u89c4\u5b9a\u65f6\u95f4\u5c06\u67dc\u9762\u548c\u6e05\u5206\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u89e3\u7f34\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e00\u6b21\u6027\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e01 5 \u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\u5e94\u5f53\u5411\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u62a5\u544a\u800c\u4e0d\u62a5\u544a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u65e0\u6545\u62d2\u7edd\u53d7\u7406\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u6216\u8005\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u63d0\u51fa\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e0d\u5f53\u4fdd\u7ba1\u3001\u622a\u7559\u6216\u8005\u79c1\u81ea\u5904\u7406\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u6216\u8005\u4f7f\u5df2\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u6ca1\u6536\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u91cd\u65b0\u6d41\u5165\u5e02\u573a\u7684\"}]","id":"511931317","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u54ea\u4e9b\u5238\u522b\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u56fe\u6848\uff1f\uff08\uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30012019\u5e74\u724850\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30012005\u5e74\u724850\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012019\u5e74\u724820\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012020\u5e74\u72485\u5143\"}]","id":"511931318","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f20\u67d0\u4e3a\u67d0\u516c\u53f8\u4f1a\u8ba1\uff0c\u4e00\u65e5\u5230\u5176\u5f00\u6237\u94f6\u884c\u4ea4\u5b58\u73b0\u91d125\u4e07\u5143\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u5728\u4e3a\u5176\u529e\u7406\u4e1a\u52a1\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\uff0c\u53d1\u73b0\u5176\u4e2d\u67091\u5f20\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u544a\u77e5\u5f20\u67d0\u8981\u8fdb\u884c\u6536\u7f34\u3002\u7531\u4e8e\u5f20\u67d0\u4e0e\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u5458\u5de5\u8f83\u719f\u6089\uff0c\u5f20\u67d0\u63d0\u51fa\u8981\u94f6\u884c\u5458\u5de5\u5c06\u8be5\u5047\u5e01\u9000\u56de\uff0c\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u5458\u5de5\u7ecf\u8fc7\u8003\u8651\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u9000\u7ed9\u4e86\u5f20\u67d0\uff0c\u5f20\u67d0\u8868\u793a\u611f\u8c22\u3002\u5bf9\u4e8e\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u673a\u6784\u5458\u5de5\u7684\u8fd9\u79cd\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u4f9d\u6cd5\u53ef\u91c7\u53d6\u7684\u5904\u7f5a\u63aa\u65bd\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5bf9\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u673a\u6784\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5bf9\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u59041000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5bf9\u8be5\u94f6\u884c\u76f8\u5173\u4e3b\u7ba1\u4eba\u5458\u548c\u5176\u4ed6\u76f4\u63a5\u8d23\u4efb\u4eba\u7ed9\u4e88\u76f8\u5e94\u7eaa\u5f8b\u5904\u5206\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c06\u8be5\u6848\u79fb\u4ea4\u53f8\u6cd5\u90e8\u95e8\u8fdb\u884c\u5904\u7406\"}]","id":"511931319","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u89e3\u51b3\u6d89\u5047\u7ea0\u7eb7\u5de5\u4f5c\u6307\u5f15\u300b\u7684\u5236\u5b9a\u4f9d\u636e\u4e3a\uff08 \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u300a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6311\u5254\u6807\u51c6\u300b\"}]","id":"511931320","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u724820\u5143\u300110\u5143\u30011\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u6c34\u5370\uff0c\u6c34\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5206\u522b\u662f\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8377\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6708\u5b63\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u6c34\u4ed9\u82b1\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5170\u82b1\"}]","id":"511931321","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5173\u4e8e\u8d27\u5e01\u72af\u7f6a\u7684\u8ba4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4e0b\u5217\u54ea\u4e9b\u9009\u9879\u662f\u6b63\u786e\u7684\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4ee5\u4f7f\u7528\u4e3a\u76ee\u7684\uff0c\u5927\u91cf\u5370\u5236\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u7b2c\u4e09\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4e0d\u6210\u7acb\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u6b63\u5728\u6d41\u901a\u4f46\u5728\u6211\u56fd\u5c1a\u65e0\u6cd5\u5151\u6362\u7684\u5883\u5916\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6210\u7acb\u4f2a\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5c06\u767d\u7eb8\u5192\u5145\u5047\u5e01\u5356\u7ed9\u4ed6\u4eba\u7684\uff0c\u6784\u6210\u8bc8\u9a97\u7f6a\uff0c\u4e0d\u6210\u7acb\u51fa\u552e\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5c06\u4e00\u534a\u771f\u5e01\u4e0e\u4e00\u534a\u5047\u5e01\u62fc\u63a5\uff0c\u5236\u9020\u5927\u91cf\u534a\u771f\u534a\u5047\u9762\u989d100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6210\u7acb\u53d8\u9020\u8d27\u5e01\u7f6a\"}]","id":"511931322","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u770b\u5230\u7b2c2003\u5e74\u7248\u30012010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\u6709\uff08   \uff09\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u7ea2\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7eff\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u84dd\u8272\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9ec4\u8272\"}]","id":"511931323","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u516c\u5f00\u53d1\u884c\u76842017\u5e74\u30012018\u5e74\u30012019\u5e74\u8d3a\u5c81\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u4e0a\u5747\u6709\uff08  \uff09\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5bab\u706f\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u82b1\u5349\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u751f\u8096\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5e72\u652f\u7eaa\u5e74\"}]","id":"511931324","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u4e2d\uff0c\u6309\u5904\u7f6e\u65b9\u5f0f\u7684\u4e0d\u540c\uff0c\u5c06\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u5206\u4e3a\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4f2a\u9020\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u7cbe\u81f4\u7248\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u666e\u901a\u7248\"}]","id":"511931325","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0b\u5217\u5238\u522b\u4e2d\uff08    \uff09\u91c7\u7528\u5168\u7248\u80f6\u5370\u5370\u5237\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u30011999\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u30011999\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30011999\u5e74\u724820\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30012019\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\"}]","id":"511931326","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5236\u4f5c\u3001\u4eff\u5236\u3001\u4e70\u5356\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u7531\uff08\uff09\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u6ca1\u6536\u8fdd\u6cd5\u6240\u5f97\u548c\u975e\u6cd5\u8d22\u7269\uff0c\u5e76\u5904\u8fdd\u6cd5\u6240\u5f971\u500d\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u500d\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\uff1b\u6ca1\u6709\u8fdd\u6cd5\u6240\u5f97\u7684\uff0c\u59041000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7684\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5de5\u5546\u884c\u653f\u7ba1\u7406\u673a\u5173\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u94f6\u4fdd\u76d1\u4f1a\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6216\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5176\u4ed6\u6709\u5173\u884c\u653f\u6267\u6cd5\u673a\u5173\"}]","id":"511931327","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u65e5\u5143\u4e0a\u54ea\u4e9b\u4f4d\u7f6e\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u5370\uff08  \uff09\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u884c\u540d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u7269\u8096\u50cf\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u76f2\u6587\u6807\u8bb0\"}]","id":"511931328","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5f00\u5c55\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u548c\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u4e1a\u52a1\uff0c\u6709\u4e0b\u5217\uff08\uff09\u884c\u4e3a\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u4f46\u5c1a\u672a\u6784\u6210\u72af\u7f6a\uff0c\u6d89\u53ca\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7ba1\u7406\u6761\u4f8b\u300b\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d1\u751f\u5047\u5e01\u8bef\u4ed8\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u672a\u6309\u89c4\u5b9a\u9274\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u83b7\u5f97\u5236\u9020\u3001\u8d29\u5356\u3001\u8fd0\u8f93\u3001\u6301\u6709\u6216\u8005\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u7ebf\u7d22\u7684\u5e94\u5f53\u5411\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u62a5\u544a\u800c\u4e0d\u62a5\u544a\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e0e\u5ba2\u6237\u53d1\u751f\u5047\u5e01\u7ea0\u7eb7\uff0c\u5728\u8bb0\u5f55\u4fdd\u5b58\u671f\u9650\u5185\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u672a\u80fd\u63d0\u4f9b\u76f8\u5e94\u5b58\u53d6\u6b3e\u3001\u8d27\u5e01\u5151\u6362\u7b49\u4e1a\u52a1\u8bb0\u5f55\u7684\"}]","id":"511931329","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u51fa\u73b0\u4eba\u4e3a\u7684\u6587\u5b57\u3001\u56fe\u753b\u3001\u7b26\u53f7\u6216\u5176\u4ed6\u6807\u8bb0\uff0c\u6709\uff08\uff09\u60c5\u5f62\u4e4b\u4e00\u7684\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e00\u5904\u6d82\u5199\uff0c\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e200mm2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4e00\u5904\u6d82\u5199\uff0c\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e20mm2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u591a\u5904\u6d82\u5199\uff0c\u7d2f\u8ba1\u9762\u79ef\u5927\u4e8e100mm2\u7684\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6d82\u5199\u9762\u79ef\u867d\u672a\u8d85\u8fc7\u89c4\u5b9a\u6807\u51c6\uff0c\u4f46\u906e\u76d6\u4e86\u91cd\u8981\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e4b\u4e00\uff0c\u5f71\u54cd\u9632\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u7684\u3002\"}]","id":"511931330","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u9500\u6bc1\uff0c\u53ef\u91c7\u53d6\uff08\uff09\u7b49\u65b9\u5f0f\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u673a\u68b0\u9500\u6bc1\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u84b8\u716e\u55b7\u6d46\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u706b\u711a\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7194\u70bc\"}]","id":"511931331","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff08  \uff09\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u80cc\u5f00\u5f0f\u5168\u606f\u78c1\u6027\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u5143\"}]","id":"511931332","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u72481000\u30015000\u300110000\u65e5\u5143\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u6709\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d8\u8272\u6cb9\u58a8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u73e0\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\uff08\u95ea\u5149\u56fe\u5c42\u6761\u5e26\uff09\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5168\u606f\u56fe\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u9762\u989d\u9690\u50cf\"}]","id":"511931333","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u8f832005\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\uff08    \uff09\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u4eba\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u53cc\u8272\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\"}]","id":"511931334","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u68c0\u67e5\u5de5\u4f5c\u7684\u68c0\u67e5\u65b9\u6cd5\u5206\u4e3a_______\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"AB","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u6b63\u67e5\u6cd5\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5012\u67e5\u6cd5\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53cd\u67e5\u6cd5\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u81ea\u67e5\u6cd5\"}]","id":"511931335","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6c47\u4e30\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u548c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4e09\u5bb6\u94f6\u884c2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a(    )\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u72ee\u5934\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u7965\u4e91\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\"}]","id":"511931336","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u5149\u53d8\u5168\u606f\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e24\u4fa7\u6709\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\uff08    \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"BC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5317\u4eac\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001BEIJING\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u30012008\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001BJ\"}]","id":"511931337","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53d1\u751f\u4ee5\u4e0b\uff08\uff09\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5904\u4ee51000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u30015\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"CD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u8bef\u4ed8\u4e861\u5f20\u5047\u6b27\u5143200\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u8bef\u6536\u4e863\u5f20100\u5143\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5728\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u70b9\u9a8c\u949e\u673a\u7684\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u8bef\u8bc6\u522b\u7387\u4e3a0.04%\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6bcf\u5b63\u5ea6\u89e3\u7f34\u81f3\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\"}]","id":"511931338","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d1f\u8d23\u7ec4\u7ec7\u5236\u5b9a\u3001\u5b9e\u65bd\uff08  \uff09\u7b49\u7684\u5236\u5ea6\u89c4\u8303\u3002\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u6709\u6743\u5bf9\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u6267\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u7684\u60c5\u51b5\u5f00\u5c55\u76d1\u7763\u68c0\u67e5\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u7ba1\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u57f9\u8bad\u7ba1\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u6570\u636e\u4fe1\u606f\u7ba1\u7406\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u9274\u5b9a\"}]","id":"511931339","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ee5\u4e0b\u5c5e\u4e8e\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u6210\u5458\u5355\u4f4d\u7684\u6709\uff08  \uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u4e2d\u5ba3\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u8d22\u653f\u90e8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u5efa\u8bbe\u94f6\u884c\"}]","id":"511931340","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u5fc3\u64cd\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u5728\u6e05\u5206\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u53d1\u73b0\u53ef\u7591\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u786e\u8ba4\u4e3a\u5047\u5e01\u540e\uff0c\u586b\u5199\u4e86\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u4ee3\u4fdd\u7ba1\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\u300b\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u4e0a\u52a0\u76d6\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5370\u7ae0\uff0c\u4ea4\u7531\u5047\u5e01\u4fdd\u7ba1\u4eba\u5458\uff0c\u4e0e\u67dc\u9762\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u4e00\u540c\u4fdd\u7ba1\uff0c\u672a\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u62a5\u544a\u3002\u4e0a\u8ff0\u6848\u4f8b\u8fdd\u53cd\u89c4\u5b9a\u7684\u6709\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ACD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5e94\u5411\u73b0\u573a\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\u62a5\u544a\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u5fc3\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5168\u90e8\u8981\u89c6\u4e3a\u8bef\u6536\u5dee\u9519\u5e76\u5411\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u62a5\u544a\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e01\u5e94\u6362\u4eba\u590d\u6838\u4e14\u5e94\u7531\u73b0\u573a\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\u586b\u5199\u76f8\u5173\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u5fc3\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e01\u4e0d\u5e94\u76d6\u5047\u5e01\u7ae0\"}]","id":"511931341","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u4e3b\u4f53\u5305\u62ec\uff08\uff09\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABCD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u884c\u653f\u4e8b\u4e1a\u6027\u6536\u8d39\u5355\u4f4d\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u516c\u5171\u670d\u52a1\u673a\u6784\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u4ea4\u901a\u8fd0\u8f93\u90e8\u95e8\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u5927\u4e2d\u578b\u5546\u4e1a\u673a\u6784\"}]","id":"511931342","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u54ea\u4e9b\u9762\u989d\u5e26\u6709\u91d1\u5c5e\u5149\u6cfd\u56fe\u6848\uff1f","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABC","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300110\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u30015\u5143\"}]","id":"511931343","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011999\u5e74\u7248\uff08\uff09\u9762\u989d\u7684\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u662f\u53cc\u9762\u51f9\u5370\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001100\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u300150\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u300120\u5143\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u300110\u5143\"}]","id":"511931344","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9999\u6e2f\u4e09\u5bb6\u53d1\u949e\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5143\uff0c\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u54ea\u4e9b\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"2","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"ABD","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"A\u3001\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"B\u3001\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"C\",\"Value\":\"C\u3001\u5168\u606f\u8d34\u6761\u56fe\u6848\"},{\"Key\":\"D\",\"Value\":\"D\u3001\u73e0\u5149\u56fe\u6848\"}]","id":"511931345","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f53\u524d\uff0c\u6211\u56fd\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u7684\u786c\u5e01\u5305\u62ec\u7b2c\u4e8c\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e011\u5206\uff0c2\u5206\uff0c5\u5206\uff0c\u4ee5\u53ca\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e011\u89d2\u30015\u89d2\u30011\u5143\uff0c\u51716\u79cd\u9762\u989d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931346","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u65e5\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u76f2\u4eba\u89e6\u6478\u6807\u8bb0\u3002\u5176\u4e2d\uff0c1\u4e07\u65e5\u5143\u4e3a\u9ed1\u8272\u201cL\u201d\u578b\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931347","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f2a\u9020\u5e01\u662f\u6307\u5728\u771f\u5e01\u7684\u57fa\u7840\u4e0a\uff0c\u5229\u7528\u6316\u8865\u3001\u63ed\u5c42\u3001\u6d82\u6539\u3001\u62fc\u51d1\u3001\u79fb\u4f4d\u3001\u91cd\u5370\u7b49\u591a\u79cd\u65b9\u6cd5\u5236\u4f5c\uff0c\u6539\u53d8\u771f\u5e01\u539f\u5f62\u6001\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931348","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u7ea2\u5916\u5149\u706f\u4e0b\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5404\u9762\u989d\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u5efa\u7b51\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u53f3\u534a\u90e8\u5206\u6d88\u5931\uff0c\u5de6\u534a\u90e8\u53ef\u89c1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931349","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u5de5\u4f5c\u8054\u5e2d\u4f1a\u8bae\u529e\u516c\u5ba4\u8d1f\u8d23\u5904\u7406\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u8054\u7edc\u4f1a\u8bae\u65e5\u5e38\u5de5\u4f5c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931350","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53d1\u884c70\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u8bbe\u7f6e\u4e86\u6a2a\u7ad6\u53cc\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u5176\u4e2d\uff0c\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u4e3a\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931351","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u724850\u3001100\u3001200\u3001500\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5728\u8f6c\u52a8\u949e\u7968\u65f6\uff0c\u7531\u7d2b\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u6a44\u6984\u7eff\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931352","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"5\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\u84dd\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931353","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5728\u6b63\u9762\u884c\u540d\u80cc\u666f\u5904\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e2d\u5747\u5370\u6709\u80f6\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931354","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f69\u724820\u7f8e\u5143\u7684\u80cc\u666f\u989c\u8272\u4e3a\u7eff\u8272\u3001\u6843\u8272\u3001\u84dd\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931355","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u672a\u4f7f\u7528\u51f9\u5370\u63a5\u7ebf\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931356","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u53cc\u9762\u51f9\u5370\u5370\u5237\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931357","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u6a2a\u7ad6\u8bbe\u8ba1\u5f62\u5f0f\u4e0e2019\u5e74\u724850\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u540c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931358","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u5f69\u724850\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u84dd\u8272\u548c\u9ec4\u8272\u4f5c\u4e3a\u80cc\u666f\u989c\u8272\uff0c\u5e76\u6709\u4e00\u9762\u98d8\u821e\u7684\u7f8e\u56fd\u56fd\u65d7\u548c\u4e00\u9897\u7070\u84dd\u91d1\u5c5e\u8272\u4e94\u89d2\u661f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931359","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u72485\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5f20\u91c7\u752875%\u68c9\u548c25%\u9ebb\u6284\u9020\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931360","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6539\u53d8\u949e\u7968\u89c2\u5bdf\u89d2\u5ea6\u65f6\uff0c2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u989c\u8272\u5728\u91d1\u8272\u548c\u7eff\u8272\u4e4b\u95f4\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931361","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1.\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e34\u67dc\u4eba\u5458\u5bf9\u6536\u5165\u73b0\u91d1\u8fdb\u884c\u624b\u5de5\u6311\u5254\u3001\u9274\u4f2a\u540e\u4ed8\u51fa\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u662f\u529e\u7406\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u5fc5\u8981\u6b65\u9aa4\uff0c\u5177\u6709\u5c0f\u989d\u3001\u5206\u6563\u7684\u6027\u8d28\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u624b\u5de5\u6e05\u5206\u8303\u56f4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931362","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e3a\u9f13\u52b1\u4e2a\u4eba\u4e3b\u52a8\u4e0a\u4ea4\u8bef\u6536\u7684\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5bf9\u4e3b\u52a8\u4e0a\u4ea4\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u4e2a\u4eba\u4e88\u4ee5\u9002\u5f53\u5956\u52b1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931363","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e5\u5143\u6240\u7528\u7eb8\u5f20\u5448\u6d45\u7070\u8272\uff0c\u9762\u989d\u8d8a\u5927\uff0c\u989c\u8272\u8d8a\u6df1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931364","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5f00\u7a97\u90e8\u5206\u53ef\u89c1\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u201cRMB50\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931365","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842010\u5e74\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u7eb8\u5e01\uff0c\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002\u8f6c\u52a8\u949e\u7968\u65f6\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u4ece\u7eff\u8272\u53d8\u84dd\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931366","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0110\u5143\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u524d\u56db\u4f4d\u6697\u7ea2\u8272\uff0c\u540e\u516d\u4f4d\u9ed1\u8272\uff0c\u7528\u7279\u5b9a\u4eea\u5668\u68c0\u6d4b\u90fd\u6709\u78c1\u6027\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931367","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u5f69\u724810\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u4eba\u50cf\u53f3\u4fa7\u81ea\u7531\u8c61\u5f81\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\u706b\u70ac\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931368","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u529e\u7406\u884c\u653f\u4e8b\u4e1a\u6027\u6536\u8d39\u7684\u6709\u5173\u90e8\u95e8\u6216\u5355\u4f4d\uff0c\u91c7\u53d6\u59d4\u6258\u4ee3\u6536\u65b9\u5f0f\u7684\uff0c\u59d4\u6258\u65b9\u53ef\u901a\u8fc7\u53e3\u5934\u5f62\u5f0f\uff0c\u8981\u6c42\u53d7\u6258\u65b9\u8bbe\u7f6e\u4eba\u5de5\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u901a\u9053\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931369","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011999\u724810\u5143\u7968\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931370","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u76f4\u5f84\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248\u4e00\u81f4\uff0c\u5747\u4e3a19\u6beb\u7c73\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931371","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u529e\u7406\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5b58\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\uff0c\u5e94\u65e0\u507f\u4e3a\u516c\u4f17\u5151\u6362\u6b8b\u7f3a\u3001\u6c61\u635f\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931372","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u5e94\u5f53\u5728\u4ea7\u54c1\u9762\u5e02\u524d\u5c06\u4ea7\u54c1\u7167\u7247\u53ca\u8bf4\u660e\u4ea7\u54c1\u5236\u4f5c\u5355\u4f4d\u3001\u89c4\u683c\u6750\u8d28\u3001\u5ba3\u4f20\u65b9\u5f0f\u7b49\u60c5\u51b5\u7684\u6750\u6599\u62a5\u53d7\u7406\u673a\u6784\u5907\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931373","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u8f7b\u91cd\u7a0b\u5ea6\u548c\u5904\u7f5a\u5e45\u5ea6\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u653f\u5904\u7f5a\u7a0b\u5e8f\u89c4\u5b9a\u300b\u7b2c\u4e5d\u6761\u3001\u7b2c\u5341\u6761\u786e\u5b9a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931374","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u987b\u5728\u56fe\u6837\u4e0a\u90e8\u660e\u663e\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6807\u6ce8\u6e05\u6670\u53ef\u8fa8\u7684\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931375","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u884c\u4e1a\u6807\u51c6\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u6240\u6709\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u6f0f\u8bc6\u7387\u5747\u4e3a\u96f6\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931376","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e92\u8054\u7f51\u65b9\u5f0f\u4e0b\u91c7\u7528\u8d27\u5230\u4ed8\u6b3e\u7269\u6d41\u6a21\u5f0f\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u4e0d\u63a5\u53d7\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931377","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u5e74\u7248\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c1000\u9762\u989d\u6e2f\u5143\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u7aef\u5348\u9f99\u821f\u8d5b\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931378","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u73e0\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\u56fe\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931379","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e0e\u5ba2\u6237\u9762\u5bf9\u9762\u529e\u7406\u91d1\u878d\u4e1a\u52a1\u6d89\u53ca\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u53ca\u8d39\u7528\u7f34\u7eb3\u7684\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u53ef\u4ee5\u4e0d\u5728\u8425\u4e1a\u573a\u6240\u8bbe\u7f6e\u4eba\u5de5\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u901a\u9053\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931380","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u4e16\u754c\u5927\u591a\u6570\u56fd\u5bb6\u5bf9\u8d27\u5e01\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u7684\u5206\u7c7b\uff0c\u8d27\u5e01\u9632\u4f2a\u901a\u5e38\u5212\u5206\u4e3a\u516c\u4f17\u9632\u4f2a\u3001\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u548c\u7279\u79cd\u9632\u4f2a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931381","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7279\u5b9a\u7248\u522b\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\uff0c\u7531\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u6279\u51c6\u5e76\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u516c\u544a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931382","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e0a\u5168\u57cb\u91d1\u5c5e\u78c1\u6027\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e0a\u7684\u56fe\u6587\u4e3a\u201cEURO\u201d\u53ca\u76f8\u5e94\u5238\u522b\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931383","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6574\u6cbb\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u4e13\u9879\u7763\u67e5\u53d1\u73b0\uff0c\u591a\u6570\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u7684\u6295\u8bc9\u662f\u56e0\u4e3a\u5238\u522b\u7ed3\u6784\u3001 \u7eb8\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\u3001 \u627e\u96f6\u3001 \u5bf9\u65e0\u4eba\u9500\u552e\u65b9\u5f0f\u7406\u89e3\u4e0d\u5168\u9762\u7b49\u5bfc\u81f4\u7684\u201c\u8bef\u6295\u8bc9\u201d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931384","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u63aa\u65bd\u4e3b\u8981\u4f53\u73b0\u5728\u6750\u8d28\u3001\u5f62\u72b6\u3001\u548c\u94f8\u9020\u5de5\u827a\u7b49\u65b9\u9762\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931385","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u56e0\u5ba3\u4f20\u9700\u8981\uff0c\u53ef\u63d0\u51fa\u7533\u8bf7\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u8d44\u6599\u6216\u6837\u5f20\u501f\u7528\u671f\u9650\u53ef\u5ef6\u957f\u81f33\u4e2a\u6708\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931386","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e00\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e0150\u3001100\u3001200\u3001500\u6b27\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u4f4d\u4e8e\u949e\u7968\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u65b9\uff0c\u6643\u52a8\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u989c\u8272\u7531\u7d2b\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u6a44\u6984\u7eff\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931387","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u4e8e\u901a\u8fc7\u6765\u8bbf\u65b9\u5f0f\u6295\u8bc9\u3001\u4e3e\u62a5\uff0c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u5f53\u573a\u7b54\u590d\u662f\u5426\u53d7\u7406\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931388","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4f4d\u7f6e\u3001\u7279\u5f81\u90fd\u76f8\u540c","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931389","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7684\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u56fe\u6848\u5747\u4f4d\u4e8e\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\uff0c\u5176\u4e2d\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u4e3a\u72ee\u5b50\u56fe\u53ca\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u4e3a\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u4e2d\u884c\u94f6\u884c\u4e3a\u7d2b\u8346\u82b1\u53ca\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931390","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2003\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u6709\u4e24\u6761\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931391","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u987b\u5728\u56fe\u6837\u4e2d\u90e8\u660e\u663e\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6807\u6ce8\u6e05\u6670\u53ef\u8fa8\u7684\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931392","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53ea\u670920\u5143\u5238\u5728\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u65b9\u5370\u6709\u80f6\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u201cRMB20\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931393","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u59572019\u7248\u7684\u7eb8\u5e01\u9762\u989d\u5305\u62ec50\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u30015\u5143\u548c1\u5143\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931394","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf2015\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7684\u767d\u6c34\u5370\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u900f\u5149\u6027\u5f88\u5f3a\u7684\u6bdb\u6cfd\u4e1c\u5934\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931395","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u724820\u7f8e\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u4eba\u50cf\u53f3\u4fa7\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u81ea\u7531\u8c61\u5f81\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u706b\u70ac\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931396","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u201c\u897f\u85cf\u548c\u5e73\u89e3\u653e50\u5468\u5e74\u201d\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u662f\u6211\u56fd\u5728\u6d41\u901a\u8d27\u5e01\u4e0a\u9996\u6b21\u4f7f\u7528\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u6587\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931397","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6211\u56fd\u51f9\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u5de5\u827a\u9996\u6b21\u662f\u57282019\u72485\u5143\u5238\u4e0a\u5e94\u7528\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931398","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u884c\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53cd\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5956\u52b1\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5956\u52b1\u8d39\u7528\u7eb3\u5165\u884c\u653f\u4e8b\u4e1a\u652f\u51fa\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931399","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u662f\u6307\u4e0d\u7531\u56fd\u5bb6\uff08\u5730\u533a\uff09\u8d27\u5e01\u5f53\u5c40\u53d1\u884c\uff0c\u4eff\u7167\u8d27\u5e01\u5916\u89c2\u6216\u8005\u7406\u5316\u7279\u5f81\uff0c\u8db3\u4ee5\u4f7f\u516c\u4f17\u8bef\u8fa8\u5e76\u53ef\u80fd\u884c\u4f7f\u8d27\u5e01\u804c\u80fd\u7684\u5a92\u4ecb\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931400","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u662f\u6bdb\u6cfd\u4e1c\u5934\u50cf\uff0c\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u662f\u957f\u6c5f\u4e09\u5ce1\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931401","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u5238\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u7b2c4\u4f4d\u53f7\u7801\u5e94\u7528\u4e86\u4e00\u53f7\u53cc\u8272\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931402","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u73b0\u91d1\u4ece\u4e1a\u4eba\u5458\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u8981\u6c42\uff0c\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u73b0\u91d1\u6536\u4ed8\u4eba\u5458\u5e94\u80fd\u719f\u7ec3\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931403","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u4e8e\u4e0d\u4e88\u53d7\u7406\u7684\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u76f8\u5173\u6295\u8bc9\u548c\u4e3e\u62a5\u4e8b\u9879\uff0c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u53ef\u4ee5\u901a\u8fc7\u7535\u8bdd\u7b49\u5f62\u5f0f\u544a\u77e5\u975e\u5b9e\u540d\u4e3e\u62a5\u4eba\u4e0d\u4e88\u53d7\u7406\u7684\u51b3\u5b9a\u548c\u7406\u7531\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931404","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u81ea\u7136\u5149\u4e0b\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u53f7\u7801\u5448\u9ed1\u8272\uff1b\u5728\u7279\u5b9a\u6ce2\u957f\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u7167\u5c04\u4e0b\u53ef\u89c1\u7eff\u8272\u8367\u5149\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931405","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"E\u7248\u65e5\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u4eba\u50cf\u53f3\u4fa7\u7684\u6761\u7801\u6c34\u5370\u5404\u4e2a\u9762\u989d\u6570\u91cf\u4e0d\u540c\uff0c10000\u65e5\u5143\u67093\u6761\uff0c5000\u65e5\u5143\u67092\u6761\uff0c2000\u65e5\u5143\u67091\u6761\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931406","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u82b1\u5349\u6c34\u5370\u4e0e\u4e3b\u666f\u5e95\u7eb9\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\u540c\u79cd\u82b1\u5349\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931407","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e00\u822c\u8ba4\u4e3a\uff0c\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\u7684\u6297\u53d8\u8272\u80fd\u529b\u8981\u597d\u4e8e\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u954d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931408","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u6b27\u76df\u65d7\u5e1c\u548c\u6b27\u592e\u884c \u884c\u957f\u7b7e\u540d\u53d8\u4e3a\u7eff\u8272\uff0c12\u9897\u661f\u7531\u9ec4\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u6a59\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931409","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u56fd\u5fbd\u3001\u884c\u540d\u3001\u5934\u50cf\u3001\u56e2\u82b1\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3001\u76f2\u6587\u548c\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u6842\u6797\u5c71\u6c34\u7b49\u91c7\u7528\u96d5\u523b\u51f9\u7248\u5370\u5237\uff0c\u7528\u624b\u6307\u89e6\u6478\u6709\u660e\u663e\u51f9\u51f8\u611f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931410","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74E\u72481000\u30015000\u30011\u4e07\u65e5\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u6761\u7801\u6c34\u5370\u3002\u5176\u4e2d\uff0c5000\u65e5\u5143\u6761\u7801\u6c34\u5370\u4e3a3\u4e2a\u7ad6\u6761\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931411","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4f5c\u51fa\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u7ed3\u679c\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5728\u6536\u5230\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66\u300b\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d7730\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7684\u4e0a\u4e00\u7ea7\u673a\u6784\u7533\u8bf7\u518d\u9274\u5b9a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931412","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0e2003\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u76f8\u6bd4\uff0c\u4e09\u5927\u53d1\u949e\u673a\u6784\u53d1\u884c\u76842010\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u5404\u5238\u522b\u7684\u6c34\u5370\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e00\u81f4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931413","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u201cF\u201d\u7cfb\u521750\u82f1\u9551\u949e\u7968\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u65b0\u76843D\u52a8\u611f\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931414","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u63a5\u7ebf\u6280\u672f\u662f\u6307\u949e\u5238\u5728\u5370\u5236\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\uff0c\u6b63\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u540c\u4e00\u90e8\u4f4d\u5206\u522b\u5370\u6709\u82b1\u7eb9\u6216\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u8fce\u5149\u900f\u89c6\u4e24\u9762\u82b1\u7eb9\u6216\u56fe\u6848\u5b8c\u5168\u91cd\u5408\u6216\u4e92\u8865\uff0c\u5b83\u662f\u901a\u8fc7\u80f6\u5370\u4e00\u6b21\u5370\u5237\u5b8c\u6210\u7684\uff0c\u5177\u6709\u8f83\u5f3a\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931415","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e00\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u5927\u9762\u989d\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u7684\u5168\u606f\u8584\u819c\u7247\u80fd\u770b\u5230\u7acb\u4f53\u95e8\u7a97\u3001\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3001\u6b27\u5143\u7b26\u53f7\u20ac\u548c\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931416","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5229\u7528\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u89e3\u51b3\u6d89\u5047\u7ea0\u7eb7\u65f6\uff0c\u4e3a\u65b9\u4fbf\u6d88\u8d39\u8005\u67e5\u8be2\uff0c\u539f\u5219\u4e0a\u91c7\u7528\u5728\u4e1a\u52a1\u53d1\u751f\u7f51\u70b9\u67e5\u8be2\u7684\u65b9\u5f0f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931417","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u4e8e\u4e0d\u4e88\u53d7\u7406\u7684\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u76f8\u5173\u6295\u8bc9\u548c\u4e3e\u62a5\u4e8b\u9879\uff0c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5e94\u5f53\u5236\u4f5c\u76f8\u5173\u6587\u4e66\u544a\u77e5\u5b9e\u540d\u6295\u8bc9\u4eba\u6216\u4e3e\u62a5\u4eba\u4e0d\u4e88\u53d7\u7406\u7684\u51b3\u5b9a\u548c\u7406\u7531","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931418","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u884c\u53ef\u5728\u6536\u5230\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6279\u590d\u300b\u540e\uff0c\u8de8\u5e74\u6267\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u9500\u6bc1\u5de5\u4f5c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931419","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2a\u4eba\u8bef\u6536\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u7684\u6b63\u786e\u505a\u6cd5\u662f\u4e3b\u52a8\u4e0a\u7f34\u81f3\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u3001\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u6216\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931420","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842010\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u6807\u5fd7\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931421","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u6536\u96c6\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u7684\u76f8\u5173\u8bc1\u636e\u65f6\uff0c\u5f53\u4e8b\u4eba\u62d2\u7edd\u7b7e\u540d\uff08\u76d6\u7ae0\uff09\u6216\u8005\u4e0d\u80fd\u7b7e\u540d\uff08\u76d6\u7ae0\uff09 \uff0c\u5fc5\u987b\u75313\u540d\uff08\u542b\uff09\u4ee5\u4e0a\u6267\u6cd5\u4eba\u5458\u6ce8\u660e\u60c5\u51b5\u5e76\u7b7e\u540d\u6216\u76d6\u7ae0\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931422","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5404\u7ea7\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5747\u53ef\u7ec4\u7ec7\u5b9e\u65bd\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u5de5\u4f5c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931423","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u5b8c\u6bd5\u5e94\u586b\u5236\u5e76\u6253\u5370\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6e05\u5355\u300b\uff0c\u76f8\u5173\u4eba\u5458\u7b7e\u5b57\u786e\u8ba4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931424","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u8f83\u4e8e1999\u5e74\u7248\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931425","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5e02\u573a\u76d1\u7763\u7ba1\u7406\u90e8\u95e8\u7834\u83b7\u4f7f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u6848\u4ef6\u5e76\u6293\u83b7\u4e3b\u8981\u6d89\u6848\u4eba\u5458\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u6839\u636e\u76f8\u5173\u89c4\u5b9a\u7ed9\u4e88\u5956\u52b1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931426","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5370\u5236\u5de5\u827a\u4e0e2015\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u76f8\u540c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931427","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u76ee\u524d\u5df2\u6210\u529f\u5e94\u7528\u4e8e1999\u5e74\u7248\u30012005\u5e74\u7248\u4ee5\u53ca2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931428","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51fa\u552e\u3001\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u6216\u8005\u660e\u77e5\u662f\u5047\u5e01\u800c\u8fd0\u8f93\uff0c\u603b\u9762\u989d\u57283000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e0d\u6ee150000\u5143\u7684\uff0c\u5c5e\u4e8e\u201c\u6570\u989d\u8f83\u5927\u201d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931429","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u6280\u672f\u89c4\u8303\u300b\u4e2d\u5173\u4e8e\u8bef\u8bc6\u7387\u662f\u6307\u8bbe\u5907\u5728\u89c4\u5b9a\u65f6\u95f4\u5185\u6301\u7eed\u8fd0\u8f6c\uff0c\u6e05\u70b9\u89c4\u5b9a\u6570\u91cf\u7684\u6d4b\u8bd5\u6837\u5f20\u6216\u6d4b\u8bd5\u6837\u5e01\uff0c\u9274\u522b\u6d4b\u8bd5\u6837\u5f20\u6216\u9274\u522b\u6d4b\u8bd5\u6837\u5e01\u8bc6\u522b\u4e3a\u771f\u5e01\u7684\u6570\u91cf\u4e0e\u5b9e\u9645\u6e05\u70b9\u9274\u522b\u6d4b\u8bd5\u6837\u5f20\u6216\u9274\u522b\u6d4b\u8bd5\u6837\u5e01\u6570\u91cf\u7684\u6bd4\u7387\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931430","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u5f69\u72485\u7f8e\u5143\u6709\u4e24\u5904\u6c34\u5370\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u5206\u522b\u662f\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b575\u6c34\u5370\u548c\u6797\u80af\u603b\u7edf\u4eba\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931431","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5411\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u56de\u7b3c\u6b3e\u4e2d\u5939\u6742\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e88\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\uff0c\u5e76\u5f00\u5177\u300a\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931432","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u53ef\u4ee5\u89c6\u60c5\u51b5\u8c03\u6574\u56fe\u6837\u4e2d\u4eba\u50cf\u3001\u56fd\u5fbd\u7684\u539f\u6709\u6bd4\u4f8b\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931433","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u72485000\u65e5\u5143\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u5168\u606f\u8d34\u819c\u6280\u672f\u3002\u4e0d\u540c\u89d2\u5ea6\u89c2\u5bdf\u65f6\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u6a31\u82b1\u3001\u201c5000\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u53ca\u65e5\u672c\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u6807\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931434","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5404\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\u6bcf\u5e74\u5e94\u5bf9\u672c\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u4e0e\u53cd\u5047\u5b50\u7cfb\u7edf\u5047\u5e01\u5e93\u5b58\u62a5\u8868\u8fdb\u884c\u6838\u5bf9\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6838\u5bf9\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\u300b\u8bb0\u5f55\u6838\u5bf9\u60c5\u51b5\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931435","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u5e74\u7248\u30012005\u5e74\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u56fe\u6848\u5916\u56f4\u8fde\u7eed\u5206\u5e03\u51f9\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u201cRMB\u201d\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931436","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5404\u7248\u522b100\u5143\u5238\u6b63\u4e0a\u65b9\u4e00\u5217\u540c\u5fc3\u5706\u5e95\u7eb9\u4e2d\u5747\u6709\u80f6\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u201cRMB\u201d\u8fde\u7eed\u5206\u5e03\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931437","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6cd5\u4eba\u3001\u81ea\u7136\u4eba\u6216\u5176\u4ed6\u7ec4\u7ec7\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5747\u5fc5\u987b\u4e8b\u524d\u7533\u8bf7\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931438","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8bef\u6536\u662f\u6307\u5728\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u529e\u7406\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\uff0c\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u5f53\u505a\u771f\u5e01\u4ed8\u51fa\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931439","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u501f\u7528\u5047\u5e01\u5e94\u7531\u501f\u7528\u5355\u4f4d\u5f00\u5177\u4ecb\u7ecd\u4fe1\uff0c\u7ecf\u501f\u51fa\u5355\u4f4d\u76f8\u5173\u90e8\u95e8\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\u5ba1\u6279\u540c\u610f\u540e\uff0c\u5c06\u501f\u7528\u5355\u4f4d\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u4fe1\u606f\u5f55\u5165\u53cd\u5047\u5b50\u7cfb\u7edf\u5e76\u6253\u5370\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u501f\u7528\u51ed\u8bc1\u201d\u4e8c\u4efd\uff0c\u4e00\u4efd\u5370\u9274\u52a0\u76d6\u9f50\u5168\u540e\u4ea4\u501f\u7528\u4eba\uff0c\u4e00\u4efd\u7ecf\u501f\u7528\u5355\u4f4d\u7ecf\u529e\u4eba\u7b7e\u5b57\u540e\u7559\u5b58\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931440","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u786c\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u8f6e\u5ed3\u7ebf\u5185\uff0c\u6709\u4e00\u7ec4\u9690\u5f62\u56fe\u7eb9\u201cRMB\u201d,\u5728\u8f6e\u5ed3\u7ebf\u5e95\u7aef\u6709\u4e00\u7ec4\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u201c\uffe5\u201d\u548c\u201c1\u201d\u3002\uff08  \uff09","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931441","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\u4e0d\u5b9a\u671f\u5bf9\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u53ca\u76f8\u5173\u5185\u90e8\u7ba1\u7406\u5236\u5ea6\u548c\u64cd\u4f5c\u89c4\u8303\u7684\u6267\u884c\u60c5\u51b5\u8fdb\u884c\u81ea\u67e5\uff0c\u5e76\u63a5\u53d7\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7684\u68c0\u67e5\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931442","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5bf9\u4e8e\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u548c\u5047\u5916\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5f53\u9762\u52a0\u76d6\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u6233\u8bb0\uff1b\u5bf9\u5404\u79cd\u5047\u786c\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5f53\u9762\u4ee5\u7edf\u4e00\u683c\u5f0f\u7684\u4e13\u7528\u888b\u52a0\u5c01\uff0c\u5c01\u53e3\u5904\u52a0\u76d6\u201c\u5047\u5e01\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u6233\u8bb0\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u4e13\u7528\u888b\u4e0a\u6807\u660e\u5e01\u79cd\u3001\u5238\u522b\u3001\u9762\u989d\u3001\u5f20\uff08\u679a\uff09\u6570\u3001\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\uff08\u5982\u6709\uff09\u3001\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u3001\u590d\u6838\u4eba\u540d\u7ae0\u7b49\u7ec6\u9879\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931443","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u662f\u5177\u6709\u7279\u5b9a\u4e3b\u9898\u7684\u9650\u91cf\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\uff0c\u5305\u62ec\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u548c\u7279\u79cd\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931444","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u5206\u4e3a\u80f6\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3001\u51f9\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3001\u51f8\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931445","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u4e3b\u8981\u5305\u62ec\u4f2a\u9020\u5e01\u548c\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931446","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9999\u6e2f\u4e0a\u6d77\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842003\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\u94dc\u72ee\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931447","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u957f\u7684\u4eba\u9009\uff0c\u6839\u636e\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u603b\u7406\u7684\u63d0\u540d\uff0c\u7531\u5168\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u4ee3\u8868\u5927\u4f1a\u51b3\u5b9a\uff1b\u5168\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u4ee3\u8868\u5927\u4f1a\u95ed\u4f1a\u671f\u95f4\uff0c\u7531\u5168\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u4ee3\u8868\u5927\u4f1a\u5e38\u52a1\u59d4\u5458\u4f1a\u51b3\u5b9a\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u4e3b\u5e2d\u4efb\u514d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931448","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u30012019\u5e74\u7248\u30012020\u5e74\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u80cc\u9762\u5927\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e2d\u5747\u5305\u542b\u76f8\u5e94\u5238\u522b\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931449","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"20\u82f1\u9551\u53ea\u67091\u6761\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931450","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u7eb8\u5f20\u5e95\u8272\u4e3a\u6de1\u9ec4\u8272\uff0c\u662f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7b2c\u4e00\u6b21\u4f7f\u7528\u8c03\u8272\u7684\u7eb8\u5f20\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931451","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u622a\u81f32021\u5e746\u670830\u65e5\uff0c\u7b2c\u56db\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u786c\u5e011\u5143\u30015\u89d2\u30011\u89d2\u5747\u5df2\u9000\u51fa\u6d41\u901a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931452","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4f9d\u6cd5\u53d6\u5f97\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u8bb8\u53ef\u4e0d\u5f97\u8f6c\u8ba9\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931453","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u72485\u300110\u300120\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4fa7\u6709\u5168\u606f\u8584\u819c\u6761\uff0c\u53d8\u6362\u89d2\u5ea6\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u660e\u4eae\u7684\u4e3b\u666f\u95e8\u7a97\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u6b27\u5143\u7b26\u53f7\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931454","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u63a5\u7ebf\u6280\u672f\u662f\u6307\u949e\u5238\u5728\u5370\u5236\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\uff0c\u6b63\u3001\u80cc\u9762\u540c\u4e00\u90e8\u4f4d\u5206\u522b\u5370\u6709\u82b1\u7eb9\u6216\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u8fce\u5149\u900f\u89c6\u4e24\u9762\u82b1\u7eb9\u6216\u56fe\u6848\u5b8c\u5168\u91cd\u5408\u6216\u4e92\u8865\uff0c\u5b83\u662f\u901a\u8fc7\u80f6\u5370\u4e00\u6b21\u5370\u5237\u5b8c\u6210\u7684\uff0c\u5177\u6709\u8f83\u5f3a\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u529f\u80fd\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931455","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u4e8e\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u60c5\u8282\u4e25\u91cd\u7684\uff0c\u5904100\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a200\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\uff0c\u5e76\u5bf9\u8d1f\u6709\u76f4\u63a5\u8d23\u4efb\u7684\u8463\u4e8b\u3001\u9ad8\u7ea7\u7ba1\u7406\u4eba\u5458\u548c\u5176\u5b83\u76f4\u63a5\u8d23\u4efb\u4eba\u5458\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u590420\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a50\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931456","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e00\u7248200\u6b27\u5143\u5728\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u4e0b\u8fb9\u7684\u4f4d\u7f6e\u6709\u54041\u7ec4\u77ed\u7ebf\u4f5c\u4e3a\u89c6\u969c\u4eba\u58eb\u8bc6\u522b\u949e\u7968\u7684\u6807\u8bb0\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931457","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u7248\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\u5238\uff08\u6e2f\u5e01\uff09\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u5370\u949e\u9020\u5e01\u603b\u516c\u53f8\u7814\u5236\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931458","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u82b1\u578b\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u53d6\u6d88\u4e86\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931459","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u94f6\u884c\u4e1a\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u3001\u975e\u94f6\u884c\u652f\u4ed8\u673a\u6784\u8bf1\u5bfc\u5176\u5b83\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u4e2a\u4eba\u62d2\u6536\u6216\u8005\u91c7\u53d6\u6b67\u89c6\u6027\u63aa\u65bd\u6392\u65a5\u73b0\u91d1\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u6839\u636e\u60c5\u8282\u8f7b\u91cd\u53ca\u5177\u4f53\u60c5\u51b5\uff0c\u4f9d\u6cd5\u4f5c\u51fa\u884c\u653f\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931460","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2018\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u6a2a\u7ad6\u53cc\u5f02\u578b\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u5de6\u4fa7\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u4ece\u5de6\u5230\u53f3\u9010\u6e10\u53d8\u5927\uff0c\u53f3\u4fa7\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u4ece\u4e0a\u5230\u4e0b\u9010\u6e10\u589e\u5927\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\u7ea2\u8272\u8367\u5149\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931461","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u949e\u7968\u6b63\u9762\u7684\u4eba\u7269\u8096\u50cf\u80cc\u666f\u540e\u53ca\u949e\u7968\u80cc\u9762\u7684\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u540e\u5747\u6709\u7ec6\u7ebf\u5370\u5237\u3002\u6392\u5217\u6574\u9f50\u7684\u7ec6\u5c0f\u7ebf\u6761\u80fd\u6709\u6548\u9632\u6b62\u590d\u5370\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931462","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\u5bf9\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u949e\u7968\u5904\u7406\u4e2d\u5fc3\u6e05\u5206\u4e2d\u53d1\u73b0\u7684\u6240\u6709\u5238\u522b\u5047\u5e01\u90fd\u5e94\u8f6c\u4e3a\u5173\u6ce8\u7c7b\u5047\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931463","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f69\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\u949e\u7968\u80cc\u9762\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u65b0\u7684\u72ec\u7acb\u7eaa\u5ff5\u9986\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u5176\u663e\u793a\u7684\u662f\u7eaa\u5ff5\u9986\u7684\u6b63\u9762\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931464","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u672a\u7ecf\u8bb8\u53ef\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u884c\u653f\u8bb8\u53ef\u6cd5\u300b\u7b2c\u56db\u5341\u56db\u6761\u7684\u89c4\u5b9a\u4e88\u4ee5\u5904\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931465","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u56e2\u82b1\u4e3a\u83ca\u82b1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931466","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7968\u9762\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7f3a\u59319\u6beb\u7c73\u4ee5\u4e0a\u7684\uff0c\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931467","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u724810\u300120\u300150\u3001100\u7f8e\u5143\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\u8f6c\u52a8\u949e\u7968\u65f6\uff0c\u989c\u8272\u7531\u7eff\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u9ed1\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931468","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u8f6c\u52a85\u5143\u82f1\u9551\u5851\u6599\u949e\u65f6\uff0c\u949e\u7968\u6b63\u9762\u900f\u660e\u7a97\u6846\u548c\u82f1\u9551\u7b26\u53f7\u7531\u7d2b\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u7eff\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931469","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u6c34\u5370\u4e3a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5927\u4f1a\u5802\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931470","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u662f\u6307\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u7684\u5b8c\u6574\u56fe\u6848\u6216\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931471","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e5\u672c\u94f6\u884c2014\u5e74\u53d1\u884c\u76845000\u5143\u9762\u989d\u65e5\u5143\u4e0e2004\u5e74\u7248\u76f8\u6bd4\u949e\u7968\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u7684\u5149\u53d8\u8584\u819c\u56fe\u6848\u53ca\u5149\u53d8\u6548\u679c\u4e0d\u53d8\uff0c\u552f\u6709\u5149\u53d8\u8584\u819c\u900f\u660e\u90e8\u5206\u7684\u5f62\u72b6\u7531\u5706\u5f62\u6539\u4e3a\u65b9\u578b\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931472","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4ece\u7968\u5e45\u770b\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5404\u5238\u522b\u7684\u7968\u5e45\u5bbd\u5206\u4e3a3\u6863\uff0c\u7968\u5e45\u957f\u5219\u6309\u7968\u9762\u5927\u5c0f\u4ece100\u5143\u5238\u52305\u5143\u5238\uff0c\u4ee55\u6beb\u7c73\u4e3a\u6781\u5dee\u9012\u51cf\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931473","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1990\u5e74\u7248\u7f8e\u5143\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\uff0c\u5305\u62ec\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff0c\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931474","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5f53\u524d\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u9664\u4e86\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4ee5\u53ca\u7b2c\u56db\u59575\u89d2\u7eb8\u5e01\u5916\uff0c\u5747\u5df2\u5168\u90e8\u9000\u51fa\u6d41\u901a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931475","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"20\u5143\u82f1\u9551\u7eb8\u5e01\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u542b\u6709\u7ea2\u3001\u84dd\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u4e1d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931476","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5370\u5236\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\u539f\u7248\u3001\u539f\u6a21\u4f7f\u7528\u5b8c\u6bd5\u540e\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u5370\u949e\u9020\u5e01\u603b\u516c\u53f8\u5c01\u5b58\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931477","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u72485\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u51f9\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e0e\u51f9\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u5178\u578b\u7279\u70b9\u662f\uff1a\u89e6\u6478\u6709\u51f9\u51f8\u611f\uff0c\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u56fe\u6848\u7ec4\u6210\u5b8c\u6574\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4e0e\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931478","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u8303\u56f4\u4ec5\u9650\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u548c\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\uff0c\u4e0d\u5305\u62ec\u505c\u6b62\u6d41\u901a\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931479","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u89c2\u5bdf\u65b9\u5f0f\u4e0e2005\u5e74\u7248\u76f8\u540c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931480","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u4e8e\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u60c5\u8282\u4e00\u822c\u7684\uff0c\u590450\u4e07\u5143\u7f5a\u6b3e\uff0c\u5e76\u5bf9\u8d1f\u6709\u76f4\u63a5\u8d23\u4efb\u7684\u8463\u4e8b\u3001\u9ad8\u7ea7\u7ba1\u7406\u4eba\u5458\u548c\u76f4\u63a5\u8d23\u4efb\u4eba\u7ed9\u4e88\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u59045\u4e07\u5143\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931481","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u5404\u5238\u522b\u7968\u5e45\u76f8\u540c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931482","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\u5c06\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u6309\u6708\u5168\u989d\u89e3\u7f34\u5230\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931483","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1990\u5e74\u7f8e\u5143\u5f15\u5165\u4e86\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u548c\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7b2c\u4e00\u6b21\u4f7f\u7528\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u4e5f\u662f\u5728\u7b2c\u56db\u59571990\u5e74\u7248\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931484","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff0c\u8fd9\u6761\u7ebf\u7684\u7279\u5f81\u4e0e1999\u5e74\u7248\u548c2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7684\u7279\u5f81\u4e00\u81f4\uff0c\u5177\u6709\u76f8\u540c\u7684\u5916\u89c2\u5f62\u6001\u548c\u78c1\u6027\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931485","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5b9e\u884c\u7efc\u5408\u67dc\u5458\u540e\uff0c\u5728\u529e\u7406\u73b0\u91d1\u4e1a\u52a1\u65f6\uff0c\u53ef\u75311\u540d\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u6536\u7f34\u5ba2\u6237\u6301\u6709\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931486","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u6709\u6743\u5bf9\u7533\u8bf7\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u8fdb\u884c\u76d1\u7763\u68c0\u67e5\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931487","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u6240\u6709\u9762\u989d\u90fd\u5e94\u7528\u4e86\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u4f4d\u4e8e\u7968\u9762\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\uff0c\u968f\u7740\u89c2\u5bdf\u89d2\u5ea6\u7684\u4e0d\u540c\u53ef\u89c1\u4e00\u6761\u4eae\u5e26\u4e0a\u4e0b\u6eda\u52a8\uff0c\u989c\u8272\u7531\u7fe0\u7eff\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u6df1\u84dd\u8272\uff0c200\u548c100\u6b27\u5143\u8fd8\u53ef\u89c1\u6b27\u5143\u7b26\u53f7\u201c\u20ac\u201d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931488","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u57fa\u5c42\u793e\u533a\u662f\u793e\u4f1a\u6cbb\u7406\u7684\u57fa\u672c\u5355\u5143\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u4e3b\u52a8\u5bf9\u63a5\u57fa\u5c42\u793e\u533a\u5f00\u5c55\u5ba3\u4f20\uff0c\u53d1\u6325\u57fa\u5c42\u793e\u533a\u7684\u7ba1\u7406\u670d\u52a1\u529f\u80fd\uff0c\u6784\u5efa\u548c\u8c10\u73b0\u91d1\u6d41\u901a\u73af\u5883\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931489","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1996\u5e74\u724820\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\u9ec4\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931490","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u56fd\u5bb6\u6cd5\u5f8b\u3001\u884c\u653f\u6cd5\u89c4\u89c4\u5b9a\u5e94\u5f53\u4f7f\u7528\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u5de5\u5177\u7684\uff0c\u4e0d\u8ba4\u5b9a\u4e3a\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931491","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u7684\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u3001\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3001\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u5747\u4e3a\u4e13\u4e1a\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931492","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u89c2\u5bdf1999\u5e74\u72481\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u65b9\u6cd5\u4e0e2005\u5e74\u7248\u89c2\u5bdf\u65b9\u5f0f\u76f8\u540c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931493","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2a\u4eba\u6216\u8005\u5355\u4f4d\u4e3b\u52a8\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e0a\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u4e88\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931494","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5404\u5238\u522b\u6b63\u9762\u672a\u91c7\u7528\u80f6\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931495","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9996\u6b21\u4f7f\u7528\u6761\u7801\u6c34\u5370\u9632\u4f2a\u6280\u672f\u7684\u65e5\u5143\u5238\u522b\u662f2000\u5e74\u72482000\u65e5\u5143\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931496","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7eb8\u5f20\u4e2d\u542b\u6709\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\uff0c\u53ef\u89c1\u660e\u4eae\u7684\u7ea2\u3001\u9ec4\u3001\u7eff\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\u4e1d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931497","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u30015\u5143\u4e09\u79cd\u9762\u989d\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u63aa\u65bd\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931498","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5e94\u5f53\u5c06\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u9898\u3001\u9762\u989d\u3001\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u6750\u8d28\u3001\u5f0f\u6837\u3001\u89c4\u683c\u3001\u53d1\u884c\u6570\u91cf\u3001\u53d1\u884c\u65f6\u95f4\u7b49\u4e88\u4ee5\u516c\u544a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931499","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6b27\u5143\u5171\u67098\u79cd\u5238\u522b\u7684\u7eb8\u5e01\u548c7\u79cd\u9762\u989d\u7684\u786c\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931500","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7f8e\u5143\u7684\u53d1\u884c\u4e3b\u7ba1\u90e8\u95e8\u662f\u7f8e\u56fd\u8054\u90a6\u50a8\u5907\u7cfb\u7edf\uff0c\u5177\u4f53\u53d1\u884c\u4e1a\u52a1\u7531\u8054\u90a6\u50a8\u5907\u94f6\u884c\u8d1f\u8d23\u529e\u7406\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931501","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6b8b\u7f3a\u6c61\u635f\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u5151\u6362\u529e\u6cd5\u4e2d\uff0c\u5151\u4ed8\u989d\u4e0d\u8db3\u4e00\u5206\u7684\uff0c\u4e0d\u4e88\u5151\u6362\uff1b\u4e94\u5206\u6309\u534a\u989d\u5151\u6362\u7684\uff0c\u5151\u4ed8\u4e09\u5206\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931502","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u6750\u8d28\u7531\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u954d\u8c03\u6574\u4e3a\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u94dc\u5408\u91d1\u7684\u4e3b\u8981\u539f\u56e0\u662f\u94a2\u82af\u9540\u954d\u6750\u6599\u6839\u636e\u56fd\u5bb6\u4ea7\u4e1a\u653f\u7b56\u5c5e\u4e8e\u62df\u6dd8\u6c70\u7684\u843d\u540e\u5de5\u827a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931503","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u975e\u94f6\u884c\u652f\u4ed8\u673a\u6784\u53ef\u4ee5\u901a\u8fc7\u5404\u79cd\u5f62\u5f0f\u5ba3\u4f20\u65e0\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u6216\u6b67\u89c6\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u6982\u5ff5\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931504","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5b9e\u884c\u5f02\u5730\u7ba1\u7406\u3001\u4e00\u4e8b\u4e00\u6279\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931505","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u8d1f\u8d23\u7ec4\u7ec7\u5236\u5b9a\u3001\u5b9e\u65bd\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u9274\u522b\u80fd\u529b\u7ba1\u7406\u3001\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u57f9\u8bad\u7ba1\u7406\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u6570\u636e\u4fe1\u606f\u7ba1\u7406\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u9274\u5b9a\u7b49\u7684\u5236\u5ea6\u89c4\u8303\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931506","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u59d4\u6258\u4ed6\u884c\u6216\u793e\u4f1a\u6e05\u5206\u673a\u6784\u6e05\u5206\u540e\u8c03\u5165\uff0c\u7531\u672c\u884c\u5bf9\u5916\u652f\u4ed8\u7684\u73b0\u91d1\uff0c\u5fc5\u987b\u7531\u672c\u884c\u8bb0\u5f55\u3001\u5b58\u50a8\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u4fdd\u8bc1\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u53ef\u8ffd\u6eaf\u67e5\u8be2\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931507","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u4e2a\u4eba\u9500\u552e\u975e\u6cd5\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u5ba3\u4f20\u54c1\u3001\u51fa\u7248\u7269\u6216\u8005\u5176\u4ed6\u5546\u54c1\uff0c\u7531\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6216\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e88\u4ee5\u8b66\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u59041\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a3\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931508","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"5\u82f1\u9551\u8367\u5149\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7531\u7ea2\u84dd\u83f1\u5f62\u7ec4\u6210\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931509","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u884c\u4e3a\u5904\u7f6e\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u9075\u5faa\u201c\u4f9d\u6cd5\u5408\u89c4\u3001\u5c5e\u5730\u7ba1\u7406\u3001 \u516c\u6b63\u5ba2\u89c2\u3001 \u7efc\u5408\u6574\u6cbb\u201d \u539f\u5219\uff0c \u4ee5\u4e8b\u5b9e\u4e3a\u4f9d\u636e\uff0c \u4ee5\u6cd5\u5f8b\u4e3a\u51c6\u7ef3\uff0c\u575a\u6301\u5904\u7f5a\u4e0e\u6559\u80b2\u76f8\u7ed3\u5408\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931510","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012005\u5e74\u724850\u5143\u5238\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u7684\u989c\u8272\u53d8\u5316\u662f\u91d1\u53d8\u7eff\u3002\uff08 \uff09","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931511","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u4f4d\u7f6e\u3001\u7279\u5f81\u90fd\u76f8\u540c","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931512","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91c7\u7528\u8fd0\u8f93\u65b9\u5f0f\u5c06\u5927\u91cf\u5047\u5e01\u8fd0\u5230\u56fd\u5916\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u4ee5\u8d70\u79c1\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\u5b9a\u7f6a\u91cf\u5211\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931513","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2007\u5e74\u724810\u5143\u6e2f\u5e01\u5851\u6599\u949e\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\u9a8f\u9a6c\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931514","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u8d35\u91d1\u5c5e\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u72af\u7f6a\u7684\u6570\u989d\uff0c\u6309\u7167\u6848\u53d1\u5f53\u65e5\u5e02\u573a\u4ef7\u683c\u8ba1\u7b97\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931515","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u7531\u8bef\u4ed8\u7684\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5bf9\u5ba2\u6237\u7b49\u503c\u8d54\u4ed8\u3002\u82e5\u53d1\u751f\u8d1f\u9762\u8206\u60c5\uff0c\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5e94\u5f53\u914c\u60c5\u5904\u7406\u7ed9\u4e88\u5ba2\u6237\u53cc\u500d\u8d54\u4ed8\u4ee5\u6d88\u9664\u4e0d\u826f\u5f71\u54cd\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931516","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2012\u5e742\u670810\u65e5\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u5f69\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\u5c06\u80cc\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u75311996\u7248\u7684\u7f8e\u56fd\u72ec\u7acb\u7eaa\u5ff5\u9986\u6b63\u9762\u8c03\u6574\u4e3a\u72ec\u7acb\u7eaa\u5ff5\u9986\u80cc\u9762\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931517","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8bef\u6536\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5916\u5e01\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u544a\u800c\u4e0d\u544a\u7684\uff0c\u5904\u4ee51000\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931518","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u8bef\u6536\u5047\u5e01\u9700\u57283\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u62a5\u544a\u5f53\u5730\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u5e76\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u89e3\u7f34\u81f3\u5176\u4e0a\u7ea7\u884c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931519","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u767d\u6c34\u5370\u4f4d\u7f6e\u8fdb\u884c\u4e86\u8c03\u6574\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931520","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u7684\u4e3b\u9898\u6d89\u53ca\u91cd\u5927\u653f\u6cbb\u3001\u5386\u53f2\u9898\u6750\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u62a5\u5168\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u4ee3\u8868\u5927\u4f1a\u5e38\u52a1\u59d4\u5458\u4f1a\u6279\u51c6\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931521","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u989c\u8272\u4e00\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931522","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u6388\u6743\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u62d2\u7edd\u53d7\u7406\u6301\u6709\u4eba\u3001\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u63d0\u51fa\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ef\u5bf9\u8be5\u6388\u6743\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u673a\u6784\u5904\u4ee51\u5343\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0a5\u4e07\u5143\u4ee5\u4e0b\u7f5a\u6b3e\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931523","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6837\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u6e05\u5355\u4fdd\u5b58\u671f\u9650\u4e3a10\u5e74\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931524","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5904\u7f6e\u89c4\u7a0b\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5047\u5e01\u501f\u7528\u4e0d\u5f97\u8d85\u8fc730\u5929\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931525","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u5238\u6b63\u9762\u5927\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5468\u56f4\u5e95\u7eb9\u4e2d\u6709\u51f9\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u201c50\u201d\u8fde\u7eed\u5206\u5e03\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931526","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4f5c\u4e3a\u5b88\u6cd5\u516c\u6c11\uff0c\u6211\u4eec\u5728\u626b\u5893\u796d\u7940\u3001\u7f05\u6000\u5148\u7956\u65f6\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u505a\u5230\u4e0d\u8d2d\u4e70\u3001\u4e0d\u4f7f\u7528\u5370\u6709\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u796d\u7940\u7528\u54c1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931527","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91c7\u53d6\u9762\u5bf9\u9762\u65b9\u5f0f\u63d0\u4f9b\u5546\u54c1\u53ca\u670d\u52a1\u7684\u5c0f\u578b\u4f01\u4e1a\u3001\u5fae\u578b\u4f01\u4e1a\u3001\u5bb6\u5ead\u4f5c\u574a\u3001\u4e2a\u4f53\u5de5\u5546\u6237\u3001\u6d41\u52a8\u5546\u8d29\u7b49\uff0c\u53ef\u652f\u6301\u591a\u79cd\u652f\u4ed8\u65b9\u5f0f\uff0c\u4f46\u5e94\u63a5\u53d7\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931528","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u6b63\u80cc\u9762\u5185\u5468\u7f18\u75311999\u5e74\u7248\u7684\u5706\u5f62\u8c03\u6574\u4e3a\u591a\u8fb9\u5f62\uff0c\u6709\u5229\u4e8e\u5f31\u89c6\u7fa4\u4f53\u5229\u7528\u89e6\u89c9\u8bc6\u522b\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931529","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u7b2c\u4e09\u65b9\u6e05\u5206\u670d\u52a1\u5916\u5305\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u53cd\u5047\u8d27\u5e01\u57f9\u8bad\u5de5\u4f5c\uff0c\u7531\u7b2c\u4e09\u65b9\u6e05\u5206\u670d\u52a1\u5916\u5305\u516c\u53f8\u81ea\u884c\u5b89\u6392\uff0c\u6e05\u5206\u4eba\u5458\u7684\u57f9\u8bad\u6548\u679c\u3001\u5c97\u4f4d\u8003\u6838\u7531\u5176\u8d1f\u8d23\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931530","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u6240\u6709\u7248\u522b\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u9632\u590d\u5370\u6807\u8bb0\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931531","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u89d2\u786c\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u589e\u52a0\u4e86\u5706\u70b9\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931532","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u975e\u73b0\u91d1\u652f\u4ed8\u662f\u5728\u73b0\u91d1\u57fa\u7840\u4e0a\u7684\u53d1\u5c55\u3002\u4e8c\u8005\u517c\u5bb9\u5171\u751f\uff0c\u548c\u8c10\u53d1\u5c55\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931533","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u662f\u6211\u56fd\u7684\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\uff0c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u73b0\u91d1\u662f\u6211\u56fd\u5883\u5185\u6700\u57fa\u7840\u7684\u652f\u4ed8\u624b\u6bb5\uff0c\u4efb\u4f55\u5355\u4f4d\u548c\u4e2a\u4eba\u4e0d\u5f97\u62d2\u6536\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931534","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5fc5\u987b\u5728\u8425\u4e1a\u573a\u6240\u516c\u793a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e1a\u52a1\u8303\u56f4","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931535","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2000\u65e5\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u53d8\u8272\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002\u8f6c\u52a8\u949e\u7968\u89c2\u5bdf\u65f6\uff0c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u4ece\u7eff\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u7d2b\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931536","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"10\u5143\u82f1\u9551\u5851\u6599\u949e\u6b63\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u91d1\u5c5e\u9690\u5f62\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002\u6b63\u9762\u900f\u660e\u7a97\u4e0b\u65b9\u94f6\u7b94\u6b63\u89c6\u53ef\u89c1\u201cTen\u201d\uff0c\u4fa7\u89c6\u53ef\u89c1\u201cPounds\u201d\uff0c\u5e76\u6709\u5f69\u8679\u53d8\u8272\u6548\u679c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931537","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u67dc\u9762\u53d1\u73b0\u5047\u5e01\u540e\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u75312\u540d\u4ee5\u4e0a\u4e1a\u52a1\u4eba\u5458\u5f53\u9762\u4e88\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\uff0c\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u4e0d\u80fd\u63a5\u89e6\u5047\u5e01\u3002\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\u7684\uff0c\u67dc\u9762\u4eba\u5458\u53ef\u5141\u8bb8\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u63a5\u89e6\u5047\u5e01\uff0c\u672a\u9020\u6210\u5047\u5e01\u6d41\u5931\u7684\uff0c\u4e0d\u6784\u6210\u8fdd\u89c4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931538","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\u662f\u6307\u5728\u771f\u5e01\u7684\u57fa\u7840\u4e0a\uff0c\u5229\u7528\u6316\u8865\u3001\u63ed\u5c42\u3001\u6d82\u6539\u3001\u62fc\u51d1\u3001\u79fb\u4f4d\u3001\u91cd\u5370\u7b49\u591a\u79cd\u65b9\u6cd5\u5236\u4f5c\uff0c\u6539\u53d8\u771f\u5e01\u539f\u5f62\u6001\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931539","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4efb\u4f55\u7269\u54c1\u4e0a\u90fd\u53ef\u4ee5\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931540","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u51fa\u4e8e\u5b66\u672f\u7814\u7a76\u7684\u76ee\u7684\uff0c\u6559\u5b66\u7814\u7a76\u673a\u6784\u53ef\u4ee5\u4e0d\u7ecf\u5ba1\u6279\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u3002\u4f46\u5fc5\u987b\u9075\u5b88\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u7b2c\u4e5d\u6761\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u5e76\u968f\u65f6\u63a5\u53d7\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7684\u76d1\u7763\u68c0\u67e5\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931541","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u662f\u6307\u900f\u5c04\u5149\u5f3a\u5ea6\u4e0e\u5165\u5c04\u5149\u5f3a\u5ea6\u4e4b\u6bd4\u503c\u7684\u5e38\u7528\u5bf9\u6570\u503c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931542","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2020\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e015\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u6297\u810f\u6c61\u4fdd\u62a4\u6d82\u5c42\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931543","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u7248\u548c\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u6240\u6709\u9762\u989d\u90fd\u5e94\u7528\u4e86\u5168\u606f\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931544","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u3001\u5965\u8fd0\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u3001\u822a\u5929\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u4e2d\u5747\u52a0\u5165\u4e86\u65e0\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ea4\u7ef4\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\u9ec4\u3001\u84dd\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931545","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u5238\u5149\u53d8\u9542\u7a7a\u5f00\u7a97\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\u4e0a\u9542\u7a7a\u6587\u5b57\u540c\u671d\u5411\u6392\u5217.","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931546","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u548c\u975e\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5de5\u4f5c\u4eba\u5458\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\u89e6\u72af\u4e86\u540c\u4e00\u79cd\u7f6a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931547","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2a\u4eba\u5bf9\u5bb6\u4e2d\u6536\u85cf\u7684\u94b1\u5e01\u85cf\u54c1\u771f\u4f2a\u6709\u5b58\u6709\u7591\u95ee\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5411\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u53ca\u5176\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u6388\u6743\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u7533\u8bf7\u9274\u5b9a\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u5e94\u53d7\u7406\u8be5\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931548","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5404\u7ea7\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u8d1f\u8d23\u4eba\u6bcf\u534a\u5e74\u5e94\u5bf9\u672c\u884c\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u4e0e\u53cd\u5047\u5b50\u7cfb\u7edf\u5047\u5e01\u5e93\u5b58\u62a5\u8868\u8fdb\u884c\u6838\u5bf9\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u300a\u6838\u5bf9\u767b\u8bb0\u7c3f\u300b\u4e0a\u8bb0\u5f55\u6838\u5bf9\u60c5\u51b5\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931549","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7981\u6b62\u5728\u796d\u7940\u7528\u54c1\u3001\u751f\u6d3b\u7528\u54c1\u3001\u7968\u5238\u4e0a\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931550","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6821\u56ed\u4e5f\u662f\u88ab\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u5c40\u8ba4\u5b9a\u4e3a\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u7684\u91cd\u70b9\u573a\u666f\u4e4b\u4e00\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931551","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2015\u5e74\u7248100\u5143\u5238\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u5927\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5185\u6392\u5217\u7740\u591a\u7ec4\u80f6\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u201c100\u201d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931552","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5149\u5bc6\u5ea6\u662f\u6307\u900f\u5c04\u5149\u5f3a\u5ea6\u4e0e\u5165\u5c04\u5149\u5f3a\u5ea6\u4e4b\u6bd4\u503c\u7684\u5e38\u7528\u5bf9\u6570\u503c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931553","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u672a\u8bbe\u7f6e\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u9632\u4f2a\u63aa\u65bd\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931554","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e0\u4eba\u503c\u5b88\u7684\u505c\u8f66\u573a\u53ef\u5728\u8425\u4e1a\u573a\u6240\u6807\u793a\u201c\u65e0\u73b0\u91d1\u201d\u6807\u8bc6\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931555","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u6b27\u5143\u6240\u6709\u5238\u522b\u4e2d\uff0c100\u3001200\u548c500\u6b27\u5143\u7968\u5e45\u957f\u5ea6\u6709\u522b\uff0c\u5bbd\u5ea6\u76f8\u540c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931556","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842010\u5e74\u724820\u5143\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u5747\u4e3a\u201c20\u201d\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931557","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u4e34\u67dc\u4eba\u5458\u5bf9\u6536\u5165\u73b0\u91d1\u8fdb\u884c\u624b\u5de5\u6311\u5254\u3001\u9274\u4f2a\u540e\u4ed8\u51fa\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u4e0d\u5c5e\u4e8e\u624b\u5de5\u6e05\u5206\u8303\u56f4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931558","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e0d\u540c\u53d1\u949e\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842003\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u5747\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u53d8\u8272\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002\u5176\u4e2d\uff0c\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u4e2d\u56fd\u94f6\u884c\u3001\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u522b\u5c06\u4e0a\u8ff0\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u8bbe\u7f6e\u5728\u949e\u7968\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0a\u89d2\u548c\u6b63\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931559","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53d1\u884c70\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u7684\u6c34\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u957f\u57ce\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931560","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4e2a\u4eba\u53ef\u4ee5\u5728\u751f\u6d3b\u7528\u54c1\u4e0a\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931561","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u67e5\u8be2\u4eba\u5e94\u5728\u529e\u7406\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d7720\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\uff08\u4e0d\u542b\u53d6\u6b3e\u5f53\u65e5\uff09\uff0c\u643a\u5e26\u6709\u6548\u8bc1\u4ef6\u3001\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u6216\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\uff0c\u529e\u7406\u53d6\u6b3e\u4e1a\u52a1\u7684\u8bc1\u660e\u8d44\u6599\uff0c\u5230\u67e5\u8be2\u53d7\u7406\u5355\u4f4d\u586b\u5199\u63d0\u4ea4\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7533\u8bf7\u8868\u300b\uff0c\u7533\u8bf7\u67e5\u8be2\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931562","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c1\u72485\u300110\u300120\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u80cc\u9762\u4e2d\u95f4\u7528\u73e0\u5149\u6cb9\u58a8\u5370\u5237\u4e86\u4e00\u4e2a\u6761\u5e26\uff0c\u989c\u8272\u53ef\u53d8\uff0c\u503e\u659c\u4e00\u5b9a\u89d2\u5ea6\u53ef\u770b\u5230\u6b27\u5143\u7b26\u53f7\u53ca\u76f8\u5e94\u5238\u522b\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931563","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u6e05\u5206\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u53d1\u73b0\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u5747\u53ef\u89c6\u4e3a\u8bef\u6536\u5dee\u9519\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931564","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u786c\u5e01\u7684\u82b1\u5349\u56fe\u6848\u4e3a\u7261\u4e39\u82b1\u3001\u8377\u82b1\u3001\u83ca\u82b1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931565","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u88ab\u8bb8\u53ef\u4eba\u53ef\u4ee5\u4e0e\u540c\u884c\u5171\u4eab\u56fe\u6837\u5236\u4f5c\u6a21\u5177\u548c\u56fe\u6837\u6e90\u4fe1\u606f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931566","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2006\u5e74\uff0c\u6211\u56fd\u5728\u201c\u7b2c29\u5c4a\u5965\u6797\u5339\u514b\u8fd0\u52a8\u4f1a\u201d\uff08\u7b2c\u4e00\u7ec4\uff09\u666e\u901a\u7eaa\u5ff5\u5e01\u4e0a\u6210\u529f\u7814\u53d1\u548c\u5e94\u7528\u659c\u5168\u9f7f\u95f4\u9694\u534a\u9f7f\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931567","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u8d27\u5e01\u91d1\u94f6\u90e8\u95e8\u5728\u63a5\u6536\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u949e\u7968\u5904\u7406\u90e8\u95e8\u89e3\u7f34\u7684\u7591\u4f3c\u5047\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u65f6\uff0c\u76f4\u63a5\u4f5c\u6ca1\u6536\u5904\u7406\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931568","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012005\u724850\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\u53ca\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u201c50\u201d\u5b57\u6837\uff0c\u91c7\u7528\u51f9\u5370\u63a5\u7ebf\u5370\u5237\uff0c\u7d2b\u8272\u548c\u7eff\u8272\u4e24\u79cd\u58a8\u8272\u5bf9\u63a5\u5b8c\u6574\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931569","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u56e0\u9632\u4f2a\u6216\u8005\u5176\u4ed6\u539f\u56e0\uff0c\u9700\u8981\u6539\u53d8\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7684\u5370\u5237\u6750\u6599\u3001\u6280\u672f\u6216\u8005\u5de5\u827a\u7684\uff0c\u9700\u62a5\u56fd\u52a1\u9662\u6279\u51c6\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931570","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6309\u7167\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u9274\u5b9a\u662f\u4e00\u79cd\u5177\u4f53\u7684\u884c\u653f\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4f5c\u51fa\u7684\u9274\u5b9a\u7ed3\u679c\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u5728\u6536\u5230\u300a\u8d27\u5e01\u771f\u4f2a\u9274\u5b9a\u4e66 \u300b\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d7760\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u7684\u4e0a\u4e00\u7ea7\u673a\u6784\u7533\u8bf7\u518d\u9274\u5b9a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931571","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91c7\u7528\u6a2a\u7ad6\u53cc\u53f7\u7801\u7684\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e2d\u7ad6\u6392\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u4e5f\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u51f8\u5370\u6280\u672f\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931572","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"5\u5143\u82f1\u9551\u5851\u6599\u949e\u6b63\u9762\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u8367\u5149\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u3002\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u53ef\u89c1\u884c\u540d\u4e0b\u65b9\u6709\u7ea2\u8272\u548c\u84dd\u8272\u83f1\u5f62\u7ec4\u6210\u7684\u201c5\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931573","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u6240\u6709\u5238\u522b\u90fd\u6709\u80f6\u5370\u5bf9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931574","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e00\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\u7968\u9762\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\uff0c\u4e0d\u540c\u89d2\u5ea6\u89c2\u5bdf\u4f1a\u7531\u7d2b\u8272\u53d8\u6a44\u6984\u7eff\u8272\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u5149\u5f69\u5149\u53d8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\uff0c\u4e0d\u540c\u89d2\u5ea6\u89c2\u5bdf\u4f1a\u7531\u7fe0\u7eff\u8272\u53d8\u6df1\u84dd\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931575","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u5177\u6709\u7ea2\u5916\u56fe\u6848\uff0c\u4e14\u7528\u7279\u5b9a\u7ea2\u5916\u4eea\u5668\u68c0\u6d4b\uff0c\u51f9\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u90e8\u5206\u53ef\u89c1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931576","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u7248\u5f69\u7248100\u7f8e\u5143\u7684\u8367\u5149\u5168\u57cb\u5b89\u5168\u7ebf\uff0c\u900f\u5149\u89c2\u5bdf\u53ef\u89c1\u5b57\u6bcd\u201cUSD\u201d\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u201c100\u201d\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u5448\u7c89\u7ea2\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931577","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5efa\u56fd50\u5468\u5e74\u7eaa\u5ff5\u949e\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u53d8\u8272\u6548\u679c\u4e0e2005\u5e74\u724850\u5143\u5238\u4e00\u81f4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931578","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u5e74\u724810\u7f8e\u5143\u6b63\u9762\u5e95\u7eb9\u56fe\u6848\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u5f69\u8679\u5370\u5237\u6280\u672f\uff0c\u5176\u4e24\u8fb9\u4e3a\u6a59\u8272\uff0c\u4e2d\u95f4\u4e3a\u9ec4\u8272\uff0c\u8272\u5f69\u8fc7\u6e21\u81ea\u7136\u3001\u6e10\u53d8\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931579","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u7248\u5404\u5238\u522b\u80f6\u5370\u63a5\u7ebf\u5370\u5237\u4f4d\u7f6e\u3001\u7279\u5f81\u90fd\u76f8\u540c","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931580","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u51a0\u5b57\u53f7\u7801\u67e5\u8be2\u7cfb\u7edf\u4e0d\u9700\u8981\u4e3a\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u9884\u7559\u6570\u636e\u63a5\u53e3\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931581","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5bf9\u8bc1\u4eba\u8bc1\u8a00\u3001\u5f53\u4e8b\u4eba\u9648\u8ff0\u3001\u73b0\u573a\u7b14\u5f55\u7b49\u8bc1\u636e\u5185\u5bb9\u8fdb\u884c\u4fee\u6539\u3001\u5220\u9664\u3001\u8865\u5145\u7684\uff0c\u6267\u6cd5\u4eba\u5458\u8981\u5728\u6539\u52a8\u5904\u7b7e\u540d\u6216\u8005\u76d6\u7ae0\u786e\u8ba4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931582","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u73b0\u91d1\u673a\u5177\u901a\u8fc7\u5347\u7ea7\u540e\u5c31\u53ef\u4ee5\u8bc6\u522b2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931583","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2019\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u300120\u5143\u300110\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u7684\u7968\u9762\u5bbd\u5ea6\u76f8\u540c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931584","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6c34\u5370\u56fe\u6848\u7531\u6b27\u7f57\u5df4\u4eba\u50cf\u3001\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u53ca\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u6c34\u5370\u7ec4\u6210\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931585","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u5728\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u5883\u5185\u4f9d\u6cd5\u8bbe\u7acb\u7684\u6cd5\u4eba\u3001\u5176\u4ed6\u7ec4\u7ec7\u53ca\u81ea\u7136\u4eba\u4ee5\u5f18\u626c\u6c11\u65cf\u4f18\u79c0\u6587\u5316\u548c\u53cd\u6620\u56fd\u5185\u5916\u79d1\u5b66\u6587\u5316\u6210\u679c\u3001\u5ba3\u4f20\u7231\u62a4\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u548c\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u9632\u4f2a\u77e5\u8bc6\u3001\u5c55\u793a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u8bbe\u8ba1\u827a\u672f\u3001\u4fc3\u8fdb\u94b1\u5e01\u6587\u5316\u5065\u5eb7\u53d1\u5c55\u4e3a\u76ee\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u7533\u8bf7\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931586","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5728\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u9047\u5230\u6781\u7aef\u6761\u4ef6\u65f6\uff0c\u949e\u7968\u4e2d\u7684\u9632\u4f2a\u7279\u5f81\u6709\u53ef\u80fd\u4f1a\u53d1\u751f\u53d8\u5316\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931587","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u5f2f\u66f2\u633a\u5ea6\u68c0\u6d4b\u503c\u4e3a0.05\u725b\uff0c\u5219\u8be5100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u4e3a\u4e0d\u5b9c\u6d41\u901a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931588","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u8d27\u5e01\u9274\u522b\u53ca\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u3001\u9274\u5b9a\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u6240\u79f0\u5916\u5e01\u662f\u6307\u4e2d\u534e\u4eba\u6c11\u5171\u548c\u56fd\u5883\u5185\u53ef\u5b58\u53d6\u3001\u5151\u6362\u7684\u5176\u4ed6\u56fd\u5bb6\uff08\u5730\u533a\uff09\u6d41\u901a\u4e2d\u7684\u6cd5\u5b9a\u8d27\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931589","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5404\u9762\u989d\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0a\u65b9\u5747\u6709\u4e00\u4e2a\u7a7a\u5fc3\u5927\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\uff0c\u5185\u542b\u201cRMB\u201d\u548c\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u80f6\u5370\u7f29\u5fae\u6587\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931590","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6e23\u6253\u94f6\u884c\u53d1\u884c\u76842003\u5e74\u7248\u30012010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u4e0d\u540c\u5238\u522b\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u745e\u517d\u5f62\u8c61\u3002\u5176\u4e2d\uff0c100\u5143\u9762\u989d\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u8d51\u5c43\u56fe\u6848\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931591","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u5bf9\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u8d27\u5e01\u7684\u771f\u4f2a\u6709\u5f02\u8bae\u7684\uff0c\u53ef\u4ee5\u81ea\u6536\u7f34\u4e4b\u65e5\u8d773\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\uff0c\u6301\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u51ed\u8bc1\u300b\u76f4\u63a5\u6216\u8005\u901a\u8fc7\u6536\u7f34\u5355\u4f4d\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u9274\u5b9a\u5355\u4f4d\u63d0\u51fa\u4e66\u9762\u6216\u53e3\u5934\u9274\u5b9a\u7533\u8bf7\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931592","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2010\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u8bbe\u7f6e\u4e86\u6709\u8272\u8367\u5149\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\uff0c\u5728\u7d2b\u5916\u5149\u4e0b\u89c2\u5bdf\uff0c\u7ad6\u53f7\u7801\u53d8\u4e3a\u6a59\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931593","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2007\u5e74\u7248\u6e2f\u5e01\u5851\u6599\u949e\u7684\u5e8f\u5217\u53f7\u662f\u7531\u5b57\u6bcd\u548c\u7f57\u9a6c\u6570\u5b57\u7ec4\u6210\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931594","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5047\u5e01\u6536\u7f34\u7684\u4e3b\u4f53\u662f\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\uff0c\u662f\u884c\u653f\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u5177\u6709\u4e00\u5b9a\u5f3a\u5236\u6027\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931595","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\u89c4\u5b9a\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u5236\u4f5c\u5546\u54c1\u65f6\uff0c\u4e0d\u5f97\u4f7f\u7528\u201c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u201d\u884c\u540d\u548c\u8d27\u5e01\u5355\u4f4d\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931596","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2004\u7248\u5f69\u724810\u7f8e\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u4eba\u50cf\u4e3a\u6797\u80af\u5934\u50cf\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931597","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u5728\u8f6c\u52a8\u949e\u7968\u65f6\u7531\u7fe0\u7eff\u8272\u53d8\u4e3a\u6df1\u84dd\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931598","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e0150\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4fa7\u53ca\u80cc\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u201c50\u201d\u5b57\u6837\uff0c\u91c7\u7528\u51f9\u5370\u63a5\u7ebf\u5370\u5237\uff0c\u7d2b\u8272\u548c\u7eff\u8272\u4e24\u79cd\u58a8\u8272\u5bf9\u63a5\u5b8c\u6574\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931599","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e0\u53d1\u884c\u5e93\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\uff0c\u5e94\u6bcf\u534a\u5e74\u5c06\u5b58\u653e\u5728\u5047\u5e01\u4e13\u7528\u7bb1\uff08\u67dc\uff09\u5185\u5047\u5e01\u8c03\u8fd0\u81f3\u8f96\u5185\u6709\u53d1\u884c\u5e93\u7684\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4fdd\u7ba1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931600","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u65e0\u4eba\u503c\u5b88\u52a0\u6cb9\u7ad9\u3001 \u52a0\u6c14\u7ad9\u3001 \u5145\u7535\u7ad9\u7b49\uff0c \u53ef\u4ee5\u4e0d\u8ba4\u5b9a\u4e3a\u62d2\u6536\u73b0\u91d1\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931601","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"1999\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u7eb8\u5e01\u5747\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u7ea2\u3001\u84dd\u5f69\u8272\u7ea4\u7ef4\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931602","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e012005\u7248100\u5143\u7eb8\u5e01\u6b63\u9762\u5de6\u4e0b\u89d2\u7684\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u201c100\u201d\u5728\u4e0e\u7968\u9762\u5782\u76f4\u89d2\u5ea6\u89c2\u5bdf\u65f6\u662f\u84dd\u8272\uff0c\u503e\u659c\u4e00\u5b9a\u89d2\u5ea6\u53d8\u4e3a\u7eff\u8272\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931603","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"2005\u5e74\u7248\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u53ea\u6709100\u5143\u300150\u5143\u91c7\u7528\u4e86\u53cc\u8272\u5f02\u5f62\u6a2a\u53f7\u7801\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931604","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u53d8\u9020\u5e01\u662f\u6307\u4eff\u7167\u771f\u5e01\u7684\u56fe\u6848\u3001\u5f62\u72b6\u3001\u8272\u5f69\u7b49\uff0c\u91c7\u7528\u5404\u79cd\u624b\u6bb5\u5236\u4f5c\u7684\u5047\u5e01\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931605","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5404\u53bf\u7ea7\u652f\u884c\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7533\u8bf7\u7684\u53d7\u7406\u673a\u6784\uff0c\u4f46\u4e0d\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u7684\u5ba1\u6279\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931606","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6e2f\u5e01\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u5238\u6709\u4e24\u79cd\u6c34\u5370\uff1a\u94dc\u72ee\u5934\u50cf\u6c34\u5370\u548c\u6c47\u4e30\u94f6\u884c\u5927\u53a6\u6c34\u5370","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931607","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e94\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e011\u5143\u7684\u6b63\u9762\u4e3b\u666f\u56fe\u6848\u662f\u4f7f\u7528\u51f9\u5370\u65b9\u5f0f\u5370\u5236\u800c\u6210\u7684\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931608","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u884c\u4e3a\u4eba\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u540e\u4f7f\u7528\u7684\u884c\u4e3a\uff0c\u4ec5\u6210\u7acb\u8d2d\u4e70\u5047\u5e01\u7f6a\uff0c\u4e0d\u5b9e\u884c\u6570\u7f6a\u5e76\u7f5a\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931609","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u5df2\u53d1\u884c\u7684\u7b2c2\u7248\u6b27\u5143\u80cc\u9762\u53f3\u4e0b\u89d2\u4fdd\u7559\u5149\u53d8\u6cb9\u58a8\u9762\u989d\u6570\u5b57\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931610","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e2a\u4eba\u6216\u8005\u5355\u4f4d\u4e3b\u52a8\u5411\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e0a\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u4e88\u4ee5\u6536\u7f34\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931611","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u7b2c\u4e8c\u5957\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u540d\u7531\u8463\u5fc5\u6b66\u540c\u5fd7\u4e66\u5199\uff0c\u5b57\u4f53\u4e3a\u9b4f\u7891\u201c\u5f20\u9ed1\u5973\u201d\u4f53\uff0c\u540e\u6210\u4e3a\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u884c\u540d\u7684\u901a\u7528\u6807\u51c6\u5b57\u4f53\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931612","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u4e3a\u65b9\u4fbf\u9000\u6b3e\uff0c\u91c7\u7528\u4e00\u5361\u901a\u5f62\u5f0f\u7684\u4f1a\u5c55\u4e2d\u5fc3\u53ef\u4ee5\u4e0d\u652f\u6301\u73b0\u91d1\u8d2d\u5361\u5145\u503c\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931613","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u6839\u636e\u300a\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\u4f7f\u7528\u7ba1\u7406\u529e\u6cd5\u300b\uff0c\u5728\u4efb\u4f55\u60c5\u5f62\u4e0b\uff0c\u4f7f\u7528\u4eba\u6c11\u5e01\u56fe\u6837\uff0c\u201c\u56fe\u6837\u201d\u5b57\u6837\u7684\u957f\u5ea6\u548c\u5bbd\u5ea6\u5206\u522b\u4e0d\u4f4e\u4e8e\u56fe\u6837\u957f\u5ea6\u3001\u5bbd\u5ea6\u7684\u4e09\u5206\u4e4b\u4e00\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931614","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u5728\u6536\u7f34\u5047\u5e01\u8fc7\u7a0b\u4e2d\u53d1\u751f\u88ab\u6536\u7f34\u4eba\u4e0d\u914d\u5408\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u6536\u7f34\u884c\u4e3a\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u7acb\u5373\u62a5\u544a\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u548c\u516c\u5b89\u673a\u5173\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931615","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u91d1\u878d\u673a\u6784\u786e\u8ba4\u8bef\u6536\u6216\u8005\u8bef\u4ed8\u5047\u5e01\u7684\uff0c\u5e94\u5f53\u57283\u4e2a\u5de5\u4f5c\u65e5\u5185\u5411\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u62a5\u544a\uff0c\u5e76\u5728\u4e0a\u8ff0\u671f\u9650\u5185\u5c06\u5047\u5e01\u5b9e\u7269\u89e3\u7f34\u81f3\u5f53\u5730\u4e2d\u56fd\u4eba\u6c11\u94f6\u884c\u5206\u652f\u673a\u6784\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"A","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931616","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"},{"chapter":"0","question":"\u300a\u5047\u5e01\u9500\u6bc1\u786e\u8ba4\u8868\u300b\u5e94\u6309\u6863\u6848\u7ba1\u7406\u76f8\u5173\u89c4\u5b9a\u8fdb\u884c\u4fdd\u7ba1\uff0c\u4fdd\u7ba1\u671f\u9650\u4e3a5\u5e74\u3002","qtype":"3","created_at":"2022-06-02 18:25:52","analysis":"","parentid":"0","difficulty":"2","uid":"2119918","path":"","answer":"B","extra":"","options":"[{\"Key\":\"A\",\"Value\":\"\u6b63\u786e\"},{\"Key\":\"B\",\"Value\":\"\u9519\u8bef\"}]","id":"511931617","paperid":"6580222","hash":"","note":"","note_id":"0","self_analysis":"","ptype":"4"}],"time":"1655010517"}
